Kazuto! We're gonna be late!
Onii-chan! Wir kommen zu spät!
Fratellone, faremo tardi!
¡Hermano, que llegamos tarde!
Mano, vamo-nos atrasar!
Okay, okay! I'll be right there!
Ja, ja, bin schon unterwegs.
Sì, arrivo subito!
¡Sí, ya voy!
Sim, já vou!
Sugu, I'm gonna leave you behind!
Sugu, ich lass dich hier stehen.
Dai, Sugu, sbrighiamoci.
Sugu, espabila.
Sugu, anda lá, eu não espero.
Hold up a second, Kazuto!
Warte doch, Onii-chan!
Aspetta, fratellone!
¡Espera!
Espera, mano!
Did you finish your homework?
Schon fertig mit den Hausaufgaben?
Hai già finito i compiti?
¿Has hecho los deberes?
Fizeste o TPC?
What? Not yet.
Äh, noch nicht …
Eh, ancora no...
No, aún no.
Ainda não.
You'd better get it done, or summer vacation
will be over before you know it.
Wenn du sie nicht bald machst,
hast du am Ende alles auf einmal.
Guarda che se non li finisci presto, le vacanze
estive passeranno prima che tu te ne accorga.
Pues date prisa,
las vacaciones pasan volando.
Faz cedo se não
as férias passam num instante.
Hey! Suguha, Kirito!
Oh, Suguha-san und Kirito-san!
Suguha! Kirito!
¡Sugu, Kirito!
Ah, Suguha! Kirito!
Sorry, everybody...
Making you all gather here for me...
Danke, dass ihr extra hergekommen seid.
Scusatemi per avervi fatto
riunire tutte apposta per me.
Me sabe mal que hagáis esto por mí.
Perdão,
terem-se juntado aqui de propósito...
Oh, come on, don't be a stranger!
Ach, kein Ding!
Non essere così formale!
Venga, no seas tan modesta.
Não há problema!
But you know, I was a little surprised.
You seem so athletic, Suguha.
Aber das hätte ich nicht gedacht, Suguha-san.
Du bist doch so sportlich.
Però è abbastanza inaspettato, Suguha, tu
che per gli sport sei così portata!
Aunque me sorprende un poco.
Eres muy ágil.
E eu que pensava
que eras boa com desporto.
Whether it's the real world or virtual reality,
I'm not good at water sports.
Mit Schwimmen komm ich einfach nicht klar.
Sowohl on- als auch offline.
Uh... Sia nel mondo reale che in quello
virtuale non sono a mio agio nell'acqua.
El agua y yo no nos llevamos bien
ni dentro ni fuera del juego.
A desportos aquáticos nem
no mundo real nem no virtual.
But really,
Aber
Certo che,
Por cierto.
Mas...
to have provisional counseling on a perfect
swimming day like this...
du hast auch kein Glück,
dass du bei dem schönen Wetter zur Beratung musst.
avere una seduta di orientamento speciale in un giorno
come questo... Anche tu non hai un attimo di respiro!
Qué mala suerte que justo hoy
tengas que ir a la psicóloga.
Não há aconselhamento nenhum
para uma piscina destas?
How unlucky is that?
Tell me about it!
Das kannst du laut sagen ...
Eh, già.
Eso mismo digo yo.
Achas mesmo...
And after I hit the books fairly seriously
during the first semester...
Dabei hab ich mich im ersten Trimester so ins Zeug gelegt ...
Per quanto io mi sia impegnato
nel primo semestre...
Si este trimestre he estudiado mucho.
E eu que até me tinha esforçado
no 1º semestre...
Too bad for you, missing out
on seeing us in our swimsuits.
Zu schade, dass du uns nicht im Badeanzug sehen kannst.
È un vero peccato che tu non
possa vederci in costume!
Es una pena que no nos veas en bikini.
É uma pena não nos teres visto
de fato de banho.
Oh, but that doesn't give you free rein
to leer at that gorgeous counselor!
Oh, aber werd bei unserer hübschen
Beratungslehrerin bloß nicht schwach!
Ah, però quantomeno te ne starai sdraiato
sotto il naso di quella bella orientatrice!
No adules demasiado
a la psicóloga, ¿eh?
Por isso não te faças à conselheira...
Wh-Where's the harm in that?
Ü... Übertreib doch nicht so!
G-guarda che non me ne importa granché...
Bueno, solo lo justo...
Não sou desses!
Kirito?
Kirito-kun?
¿Kirito?
Kirito...?
Uh, I didn't say anything!
E... Es ist gar nichts!
N-no, non me ne importa nulla!
¡No he dicho nada!
N-não foi nada!
A-All right, I'll be on my way, then...
A... Also, ich muss dann hier lang ...
B-beh, allora io a questo punto...
Bueno, tengo que irme...
Bem, fico-me por aqui...
Sugu, everyone's here to coach you,
so be sure to practice hard!
Sugu, streng dich an.
Sie machen sich extra für dich die Mühe.
Sugu, visto che sono venute apposta per
insegnarti, esercitati come si deve.
Sugu, aprende mucho, ¿eh?
Seguro que te enseñan muy bien.
Bem,
vou treinar! Obrigada por me ensinarem!
Okay!
Ist gut.
Sì...
Que sí.
Sim.
Compared to the sea in ALfheim,
the school pool is really shallow,
Das Schwimmbecken der
Schule ist viel seichter als das Meer in ALfheim.
A differenza del mare di Alfheim, la piscina
di questa scuola non è affatto profonda,
La piscina del instituto es una balsa
comparada con el mar de ALfheim.
A piscina da escola é bem mais rasa
que o mar de Alfheimr.
so just have fun and practice
without stressing out.
Wir können es also ruhig angehen und uns nebenbei amüsieren.
quindi è adatta sia per imparare
sia se ci si vuole divertire.
Relájate y tómatelo como un juego.
Podes treinar lá à vontade!
Kirito, we'll see you later!
Kirito-kun, wir sehen uns später!
Kirito, allora a più tardi!
¡Hasta luego, Kirito!
Kirito, até depois!
Say hi to the gorgeous counselor!
Grüß unsere sexy Lehrerin!
Mi raccomando quella bella dottoressa!
¡Saluda a la "modelo" de mi parte!
Diz olá à professora gira!
Counseling Room
Come in.
Herein.
Avanti.
Adelante.
Entre.
Excuse me.
Entschuldigen Sie.
Permesso.
Con permiso.
Com licença.
M-Mr. Kikuoka?
K... Kikuoka-san?
S-signor Kikuoka?
¿K-kikuoka?
Kikuoka?
Hey there, Kirito. Long time no see.
Hallo, Kirito-kun. Lange nicht gesehen.
Ehilà, Kirito. È parecchio che non ci si vede.
Hola, Kirito.
Cuánto tiempo.
Kirito. Há quanto tempo!
What's an elite bureaucrat of the
Virtual Reality Section doing here, of all places?
Was macht denn ein Elite-Beamter von der Abteilung für
VR des Ministeriums für Telekommunikation hier?
Cosa fa un burocrate d'elite della sezione virtuale
del ministero delle comunicazioni in un posto simile?
¿Qué hace un alto cargo del
Ministerio de Asuntos Internos aquí?
Que faz o burocrata da Secção da Imaginação do
Ministério de Assuntos Internos aqui?
There's something I wanted to ask you.
Ich habe ein paar Fragen an dich.
Ci sono delle cose che vorrei chiederti.
Verás, quería preguntarte algo.
Quero fazer-te umas perguntas.
And so I arranged to have
this meeting set up for us.
Darum habe ich dieses Treffen arrangieren lassen.
Per questo ho fatto in modo di
organizzare questo incontro.
Y he pedido que me dejen este despacho.
Foram eles que construiram este sítio.
Then this whole “provisional counseling” thing...
Dann ist diese Beratung heute ...
Quindi la seduta di orientamento speciale è...
Entonces, la cita con la psicóloga...
Com que então uma conselheira...
Sorry about that. I didn't think you'd show up
unless we used that as a pretext.
Tut mir leid. Ich dachte, du wärst sonst nicht hergekommen.
Mi dispiace. È che ho pensato che se non l'avessi
messa in questo modo, non saresti venuto.
No tenía otra manera de hablar contigo.
Pois. Mas se não tivesse dito assim
não tinhas vindo.
All right, I'll be going now.
Dann verabschiede ich mich jetzt.
Beh, allora io adesso...
Os dejaré a solas.
Bem, fico-me por aqui...
If you need me,
I'll be in the room next door.
Ich bin nebenan, falls etwas sein sollte.
Per qualsiasi cosa,
mi trovi nella stanza accanto.
Si necesitas algo,
estoy aquí al lado.
Qualquer coisa, estou na sala ao lado.
Well, no reason to shoot the breeze
standing up. Why don't you have a seat?
Nun, es könnte eine Weile dauern.Setz dich doch.
Beh, puoi anche parlare stando in piedi,
ma perché non ti accomodi?
Toma asiento y charlemos.
Não te queres sentar?
Let me make one thing clear from the get-go.
Ich sag’s Ihnen gleich: Ich hab noch was vor,
also machen Sie’s bitte kurz.
Prima che dica qualcosa, però, la avviso che dopo
ho un impegno, e quindi vorrei facesse in fretta.
Por favor, no se alargue.
Después tengo una cita.
Depois disto tenho um compromisso,
se pudesse ser breve...
I have somewhere to be after this, so please keep this brief.
I'll do my best.
Ich gebe mir Mühe.
Farò del mio meglio.
Haré lo que pueda.
Farei por isso.
The truth is, now that I'm tying up
the SAO and ALO incidents,
Ehrlich gesagt,
wollte ich dich gerne noch mal direkt zu den Vorfällen
La verità è che, dato che sto cercando di chiudere
la catena di incidenti legata a SAO e ALO,
Quería preguntarte personalmente
sobre...
Como sabes houveram
os incidentes SAO e ALO,...
I wanted to hear your story directly.
in SAO und ALO befragen.
ho pensato di chiedere
direttamente il tuo parere.
...la serie de incidentes de SAO y ALO.
...e queria perguntar-te directamente.
I've already told you
about it numerous times.
Das hab ich doch schon tausend Mal erzählt.
Ho già discusso della questione
non so quante volte.
Creo haberlo explicado bastante.
Já falei disso tantas vezes...
And I'm sure it's all pretty much
right there in the player action logs.
Außerdem sehen Sie doch in den Logs der Spieler,
was passiert ist.
Se osserva il log di gioco dei player, si
farà da sé un'idea generale della cosa.
Basta con mirar el registro de acciones
de los jugadores para entenderlo.
Se virem o registo de acções do jogador,
percebe-se tudo.
All we can deduce from those logs is
who went where on any given day, so...
Aus den Logs lässt sich nur ablesen, wer wann wo gewesen ist.
Dai log di gioco posso capire
quando e dove qualcuno è andato,
Esos datos nos indican los nombres,
tiempos y desplazamientos.
Bem, só mesmo o quem, quanto e onde...
As for what happened there,
we still don't really know.
Das sagt noch nichts darüber aus,was vorgefallen ist.
ma non che cosa gli sia successo.
Pero no sabemos qué han hecho.
Mas o "quê" é que não percebemos.
Even though the SAO incident led
to a whopping 4,000 casualties,
Obwohl der SAO-Vorfall fast 4000 Todesopfer gefordert hat,
Nel caso di SAO, nonostante le
ben quattromila vittime,
A pesar de que han sido
4000 las víctimas en SAO,...
Apesar das 4000 vítimas
do incidente SAO,...
thanks to the death of its mastermind, Akihiko Kayaba,
we still don't have a grasp on the overall picture.
haben wir immer noch keinen Gesamtüberblick über die Ereignisse,
weil der Drahtzieher Akihiko Kayaba gestorben ist.
poiché il colpevole, Akihito Kayaba, è morto, ci è tuttora
impossibile comprendere l'incidente nella sua interezza.
...debido a la muerte de Akihiko Kayaba,
aún no hemos resuelto el caso.
...uma vez que o líder, Akihiko Kayaba,
faleceu, não sabemos tudo...
Most importantly, Kayaba's
motive remains unknown.
Das Wichtigste, Kayabas Motiv,
ist uns noch gänzlich unbekannt.
Anche il principale movente del professor
Kayaba ci è del tutto oscuro.
No sabemos tampoco el móvil de Kayaba.
Nem sequer sabemos os motivos do Kabaya.
His reasons for creating
a death game like SAO...
Um aufzuklären,
warum er dieses Death Game SAO erschaffen hat,
Anche per chiarire il motivo per il quale egli
abbia creato il gioco mortale chiamato SAO,
Quería volver a hablar contigo para
esclarecer por qué Kayaba...
Nem sabemos porque é que ele criou o jogo
da morte SAO, e por essa razão,...
In order to unravel that mystery, I'd like
to hear your story one more time, Kirito.
möchte ich dich nochmals dazu befragen.
ho voluto chiedere di nuovo a te, Kirito.
...creó ese juego mortal.
...te queremos voltar a questionar.
You'll help me out, won't you?
Du wirst doch kooperieren?
Vorresti aiutarmi?
¿Me ayudarás?
Ajudas-nos, certo?
What happens if I refuse?
Und wenn ich ablehne?
E se dicessi di no?
¿Y si me niego?
E se disser que não?
Who was it that granted you permission
to take home a NerveGear slated for disposal,
Hast du schon vergessen,
wer dir die Genehmigung für den NerveGear besorgt hat
Chi è stato a concederti di utilizzare il
Nerve Gear che avrebbe dovuto essere distrutto
¿Quién autorizó que te llevases
el Nerve Gear que debía destruirse?
Posso ordenar a eliminação
do Nerve Gear,...
and told you
which hospital Asuna was in?
und dir verraten hat, in welchem Krankenhaus Asuna-kun lag?
e ti ha parlato dell'ospedale
dove si trovava Asuna?
¿Quién te enseñó el hospital de Asuna?
...e quem mencionou o hospital da Asuna?
And it's actually my department
Auch, dass ihr Rückkehrer aus
SAO nicht von den Medien belagert werdet,
Anche il fatto che i media non si
siano avventati sui ritornati da SAO,
¿Y quién está impidiendo que la prensa
acose a los repatriados del SAO?
E sabias que quem está a tratar das
conferências aos regressados de SAO...
that's working to keep the SAO returnees out of a media circus.
habt ihr meiner Abteilung zu verdanken.
in effetti, è stato tutta opera mia.
Es mi departamento, ¿verdad?
...é um departamento nosso.
It might be too late now, but is it really okay
for me to be using the pool at this school?
Die Frage kommt vielleicht etwas spät, aber darf ich denn das
Schwimmbecken eurer Schule überhaupt benutzen?
Anche in un momento come questo, possiamo davvero
usare la piscina di questa scuola?
¿En serio que puedo bañarme
en esta piscina?
É tarde, mas será
que posso usar a piscina da escola?
It's all good! We have permission!
Kein Problem. Wir haben die Erlaubnis.
È tutto a posto, ho chiesto io il permesso!
Claro, tengo permiso.
Claro, tens a licença e tudo.
Your swimsuit's really cool, Rika!
Du hast ja einen feschen Badeanzug, Rika-san.
Il tuo costume è incredibile, Rika!
Rika, tu traje de baño es impresionante.
O teu fato de banho é tão giro!
Isn't it? The one I used in SAO
just got way too tight for me.
Nicht wahr? Der, den ich vor SAO hatte,
ist inzwischen natürlich zu eng.
Vero? Quello che usavo prima di SAO
era diventato strettissimo,
¿A que sí?
El de antes de SAO me apretaba bastante.
É não é! O que usava antes da SAO
já estava apertado.
So I bought a new one.
Darum hab ich einen neuen gekauft.
così ne ho comprato uno nuovo.
Es nuevo.
Comprei um novo.
Well, I hardly changed in size at all...
Meine Größe hat sich fast gar nicht verändert ...
Io invece non sono
praticamente cambiata di taglia...
Pues mi talla sigue siendo casi la misma.
O tamanho a mim não mudou nada...
Hey, Asuna! Look at you,
rocking that bikini!
Asuna-san, der Bikini ist ja atemberaubend!
Oh! Asuna, stai benissimo in bikini!
Asuna, menudo bikini.
Asuna, fica-te bem o bikini!
You gonna bewitch Kirito
with that daring swimsuit?
Hast du etwa vor, Kirito damit zu betören?
Vuoi affascinare Kirito
con un costumino audace?
¿Quieres seducir a Kirito
con tus encantos?
Será que vai atrair o Kirito?
N-No, that's not what this is about!
S... So ein Unsinn!
A-assolutamente no!
¡C-claro que no!
Não digas coisas dessas?
Uh... what? None of you are
wearing the school swimsuit?
N... Nanu? Ihr tragt ja gar nicht eure Schulbadeanzüge?
E-ecco, ragazze, voi non avete
il costume da bagno scolastico?
¿N-no os habéis puesto
el bañador de clase?
Ah, então não é suposto usar fatos
de banho da escola?
Well, since you said we were going
to swim in the school pool...
Ich dachte,
weil wir im Schwimmbecken der Schule schwimmen wollen ...
È che, visto che si era parlato di
nuotare nella piscina di una scuola...
Como dijisteis que era
la piscina del instituto.
Então mas se é para nadar
na piscina da escola...
Th-The school suit is
totally cute, too, isn't it?
D... Der Schulbadeanzug ist doch auch ganz süß.
B-beh, anche i costumi scolastici sono carini!
¡E-se también es muy bonito!
O fato de banho da escola também é giro!
Y-Yes, it is!
And it's so you, Suguha!
G... Genau! Ich glaube, der passt zu dir, Suguha!
V-vero, vero, Suguha, ti dona molto!
¡Sí, te queda muy bien!
Exacto, e fica-te bem, Suguha!
What do you mean by that?
Was soll das denn heißen?!
Che cosa vorresti dire con questo?!
¡Jolín, qué rabia!
O que significa... isso?
So... Where do you want me to start?
Und wo soll ich anfangen?
Beh, da dove vuole che cominci?
¿Y por dónde empiezo?
Por onde devo começar a falar?
First, I'd like to hear about the first day of the incident.
Erst mal würde ich gerne erfahren,
was am ersten Tag geschah. Das müsste der ...
Prima di tutto, vorrei che mi parlassi del giorno
dell'incidente. Ecco... In pratica, il giorno...
Por el primer día.
La fecha fue un...
Primeiro, gostava de perguntar sobre o primeiro
dia do incidente... Qual era o dia mesmo...?
Let's see... I believe the actual date was....
November 6, 2022.
Der 6. November 2022.
Sei Novembre del 2022.
El 6 de noviembre del 2022.
Dia 6 de Novembro de 2022.
So it's already been
two and a half years since then...
Das ist jetzt zweieinhalb Jahre her.
Ormai sono passati due anni e mezzo...
Ya han pasado dos años y medio...
Já se passaram dois anos...
Attention, players.
Welcome to my world.
Willkommen in meiner Welt, liebe Spieler.
Miei cari giocatori...
Benvenuti nel mio mondo.
Mis saludos, jugadores.
Bienvenidos a mi mundo.
Caros jogadores, bem-vindos ao meu mundo.
"My world"?
„In meiner Welt"?
Ha detto “il mio mondo”?
¿"A mi mundo"?
Meu mundo?
My name is Akihiko Kayaba.
Mein Name ist Akihiko Kayaba.
Il mio nome è Akihiko Kayaba.
Me llamo Akihiko Kayaba.
O meu nome é Akihiko Kabaya.
As of this moment, I am the only person
able to control this world.
Im Moment befindet sich diese Welt allein unter meiner Kontrolle.
E sono l'unico in grado di
controllare questa dimensione.
Soy la única persona
que controla este mundo.
Sou a única pessoa
que consegue controlar este mundo.
Sword Art Online
Development Director
Akihiko Kayaba
"DER ERFINDER DES NERVEGEAR"
"L'UOMO CHE HA COSTRUITO IL NERVE GEAR!"
"EL CREADOR DEL NERVE GEAR"
"O HOMEM QUE CONSTRUIU A NERVE GEAR"
"DER ENTWICKLER VON „SWORD ART ONLINE"
: AKIHIKO KAYABA"
"IL CREATORE DI SWORD ART ONLINE, AKIHIKO KAYABA!"
"AKIHIKO KAYABA, DESARROLLADOR DE
SWORD ART ONLINE".
"SWORD ART ONLINE
CRIADOR AKIHIKO KAYABA"
Is that really him?
- Ernsthaft?
- Ist er das wirklich?
- Sul serio?
- Quel Kayaba?
- ¿En serio?
- ¿Es él de verdad?
- A sério?
- Não!
This is really elaborate!
- Akihiko Kayaba-san?
- Das hat sicher gedauert.
- Lui in persona?
- Avrà lavorato molto per questa entrata!
- ¿Kayaba?
- Pues se ha empleado a fondo.
- Kakiba?
- Mas que é isto?
I'm sure
Ich vermute,
Miei cari giocatori,
Atención, jugadores.
Meus jogadores...
you've already noticed that the logout button
is missing from the main menu.
dass euch allen bereits der fehlende
Logout-Button in eurem Hauptmenü aufgefallen ist.
immagino che ormai avrete notato quasi tutti che
l'opzione di “logout” è scomparsa dal main menu.
Habréis visto que no hay botón
de log out en el menú principal.
...já devem ter reparado
que o botão "Sair" desapareceu.
But this is not a defect in the game.
Dies ist jedoch kein Bug.
Sappiate che non dipende da un errore del gioco.
No es un error del juego.
Mas isto não é erro nenhum...
I repeat...
Ich wiederhole:
Ripeto:
Repito.
Repito,...
This is not a defect in the game,
but a key feature of Sword Art Online.
Das ist kein Bug,
sondern ein essenzielles Feature in Sword Art Online.
non c'è alcun bug nel sistema,
è un requisito di Sword Art Online.
No es un error.
SAO está diseñado para ser así.
...isto não é um defeito.
Sword Art Online é assim mesmo.
A-A feature?
Ein Feature?
Un requisito?
¿En serio?
Assim?
But be sure to keep this in mind.
Seid euch eines jedoch stets bewusst:
Ma ricordate bene.
Prestad, mucha atención.
Mas quero que prestem atenção.
There is no longer any function to
revive someone within the game.
In diesem Spiel könnt ihr euch nicht mehr wiederbeleben.
D'ora in poi, nel MMO, non ci sarà più
alcuna possibilità di resurrezione.
A partir de ahora, dentro del juego
no habrá forma de revivir.
Não dá para usar a função de Reviver...
The instant your HP drops to zero,
your avatars will vanish forever.
Wenn eure Lebenspunkte auf Null sinken,
wird euer Character für immer gelöscht
Nell'istante in cui gli Hit Point arriveranno
a zero, il vostro avatar scomparirà per sempre.
Cuando los PV lleguen a cero,
vuestro avatar será eliminado.
...e quando os Pontos de Danos chegarem
a 0, vocês desaparecerão para sempre.
And simultaneously,
und gleichzeitig
Al tempo stesso,
Al mismo tiempo,...
Ao mesmo tempo,...
you brains will be destroyed by the NerveGear.
zerstört das NerveGear euer Gehirn.
il vostro cervello sarà
distrutto dal Nerve Gear.
...el Nerve Gear destruirá vuestro cerebro
con microondas.
...os seus cérebros serão destruidos
pela Nerve Gear.
The one condition for your escape is
to complete this game.
Ihr müsst nur eine Aufgabe erfüllen, um frei zu sein:
Esiste un unico modo per
riguadagnare la libertà:
Solo tenéis una manera de liberaros.
Para se podem livrar disso,
há uma condição.
Spielt das Spiel durch.
finire Sword Art Online.
Tenéis que completar el juego.
passar o jogo.
You are presently on the lowest floor
of Aincrad, floor one.
Ihr befindet euch momentan auf Ebene 1,
der untersten Ebene von Aincrad.
Vi trovate al primo livello
di Aincrad, il più basso.
Ahora estáis en
el primer nivel de Aincrad.
Vocês estão no 1º andar de Ainkrad.
If you make your way through the dungeon and defeat
the Floor Boss, you may advance to the next level.
Kämpft euch durch alle Dungeons und besiegt den jeweiligen Boss,
um auf die nächste Ebene zu gelangen.
Superate i labirinti e sconfiggete il boss
di ogni piano per passare al successivo.
Para pasar de piso, tenéis que superar
cada calabozo y vencer a su jefe.
Passam os labirintos em cada nível,
lutam com os bosses e avançam o nível seguinte.
Defeat the final boss on floor 100
and you will clear the game.
Besiegt den Endboss auf Ebene 100 und das Spiel ist gewonnen.
Superato l'ultimo livello, il centesimo,
avrete completato il gioco.
Cuando ganéis al jefe final del piso 100,
habréis completado el juego.
Se passarem os 100 bosses passam o jogo.
- Clear?
- What's he talking about?
- „Gewonnen“?
- Was redet er da?
- Completato?
- Che significa?
-¿"Completado"?
-¿De qué habla?
- Passar o jogo?
- Que é isto?
D-Don't just make stuff up!
D... Das ist leichter gesagt, als getan!
Ora basta con queste assurdità!
¡No digas locuras!
Não digas coisas parvas!
Clear all 100 floors?
100 Ebenen schaffen?
Completare tutti e cento i livelli?
¿100 pisos?
Passar? 100 níveis?
That's impossible.
Wie soll das denn gehen?
Ma è una cosa impossibile!
Eso es imposible.
Como é possível?!
Even the beta testers never made it
that high, right?
Die Betatester kamen nicht mal annähernd so weit!
Nei beta test non ci sono
andati nemmeno vicini!
Ni los beta testers han llegado tan alto.
O teste beta não bastou?
Now then, finally,
Und zu guter Letzt,
E per finire,
Ya para acabar.
Por último,...
I've provided you all with a present
in your item storage.
habe ich jedem von euch ein kleines
Geschenk im Inventar hinterlassen.
nel vostro inventario ho depositato
un piccolo regalo da parte mia.
Os he preparado un regalo
en vuestro menú de ítems.
...está um presente meu junto
com os vossos items.
Please see for yourselves.
Bitte vergewissert euch selbst.
Prego, controllate.
Comprobadlo.
Vejam lá.
Mirror
A mirror?
Ein Spiegel?
Uno specchietto?
¿Un espejo?
Espelho de mão?
Klein?
Klein?!
Klein!
¿Klein?
Klein.
You okay, Kirito?
Alles klar, Kirito?
Tutto a posto, Kirito?
¿Todo bien, Kirito?
Estás bem, Kirito?
Y-Yeah...
J... Ja.
Io... sì.
Sí.
Sim.
Who are you?
Nanu? Wer bist du?
Ma tu... chi sei?
¿Y tú quién eres?
Ui, quem és?
And who are you?
Das könnt ich dich auch fragen.
No, piuttosto chi sei tu?
Eso mismo digo yo.
Isso pergunto eu.
- Who are you?
- Why did my face change?
Wieso ist mein Gesicht ...?
Perché mai la mia faccia...
¿Qué le pasa a mi cara?
A minha cara...!
You're a guy?
Du bist ein Kerl?!
In realtà sei un maschio?!
¿Eras un chico?
Tu eras rapaz?
You were lying about being 17?
Und du bist keine 17!
E i tuoi diciassette anni?
Y tú no tienes diecisiete.
Não tinhas 17 anos?!
That means...
Das heißt ...
Questo vuol dire che...
Entonces...
Então isto...
- You're Kirito?
- You're Klein?
- Du bist Klein?!
- Du bist Kirito?!
- Tu sei il vero Klein?!
- Tu sei il vero Kirito?!
-¿Tú eres Kirito?
-¿Tú eres Klein?
- Tu és o Kirito?
- Tu és o Klein?
How?
Hä? Wieso?
Ma come è successo?
Pero, ¿por qué?
Porquê?
That scan...
Der Scan ...
Scanner...
El escáner...
Scan
The NerveGear covers your entire head
with a high-density signaling device.
Das NerveGear tastet das ganze
Gesicht mit hochempfindlichen Sensoren ab.
Per mezzo di un sensore ad alta densità il
Nerve Gear può vedere ogni punto del viso,
...del Nerve Gear emite señales
de alta potencia.
O Navugia tendo a alta intensidade
que tem cobre a cara por completo.
So it can see what your face looks like.
Dadurch weiß es, wie unsere Gesichter aussehen.
e ottenere così il nostro profilo facciale.
Por eso puede capturar
la forma de la cabeza.
Então é por isso.
But our height and body shape...
Aber was ist mit Größe und Körperbau?
Ma altezza e corporatura...?
Pero, ¿y la estatura y la constitución?
Então e a constituição física?
When we first put on the NerveGear,
there was something called calibration...
Bei der ersten Benutzung muss das
NerveGear doch kalibriert werden.
La prima volta che abbiamo indossato il Nerve
Gear, per "calibrarlo" o qualcosa del genere,
¿No calibraste el Nerve Gear
la primera vez?
Não calibraste o Navugia no primeiro uso?
You had to touch your body
all over like this, remember?
Dabei musste man sich doch einmal komplett abtasten?
ci hanno chiesto di tastare
tutto il corpo, ricordi?
Tocándote aquí y allá.
E não tocaste no corpo assim?
O-Oh, right...
It must be basing this on that data....
Stimmt. Daher muss es die ganzen Daten haben.
È vero, non c'era altra scelta...
dev'essersi basato su quei dati.
Claro, lo han hecho con esos datos.
Ah, então isso foi a base...
But... But listen...
Aber ... Aber ...
Eppure... ancora non capisco.
Pero, un momento.
Não, mas, olha lá...
Why? Why do all this, anyway?
Wieso denn? Was ist hier eigentlich los?
Eh? Cosa? Perché mai quel tizio
sta facendo una cosa del genere?
¿Por qué está pasando todo esto?
Eh? Porquê?
Mas porque perguntas?
I'm sure he'll tell us.
Das sagt er uns sicher gleich.
Non credo che ci terrà all'oscuro.
Ahora lo sabremos.
Vamos já saber.
Right now, you must all be wondering, "Why?"
Ihr fragt euch jetzt sicherlich: „Wieso das alles?“
Vi starete chiedendo "Perché?", non è così?
Todos os preguntáis: "¿Por qué?"
Vocês agora perguntam-se, "porquê?"
"Why would Akihiko Kayaba,
Wieso würde Akihiko Kayaba, der Erfinder von Sword Art Online
Perché Akihiko Kayaba, creatore di
Sword Art Online e del Nerve Gear,
¿Por qué Akihiko Kayaba,
creador de SAO y del Nerve Gear...
Porque é que o Akihiko Kayaba,
o criador do Swords Art Online...
developer of Sword Art Online and
the NerveGear, do such a thing?"
und dem NerveGear, das tun?
ha preso un'iniziativa simile.
...haría todo esto?
...e do Navugia, fez isto.
My goal has already been achieved.
Mein Ziel habe ich bereits erreicht.
Il mio obiettivo è stato raggiunto.
Ya he alcanzado mi meta.
Meu objectivo já foi atingido.
I created Sword Art Online for one reason...
Ich wollte meine eigene Welt schaffen und mich an ihr erfreuen.
Ho programmato SAO
solo per creare questo mondo
He creado este mundo
solo para contemplarlo.
Unicamente para o observar,
criei este mundo,...
To create this world and meddle in it.
Aus diesem Grund habe ich Sword Art Online kreiert.
e osservarlo con mia immensa soddisfazione.
Por eso he creado Sword Art Online.
...criei Swords Art Online.
Kayaba...
Kayaba!
¡Kayaba!
And now, all is complete.
Und nun sind alle meine Wünsche in Erfüllung gegangen.
E finalmente ho ottenuto tutto questo.
Y ahora lo he completado del todo.
E está tudo concluído.
“I created SAO in order
to meddle with this world...”
Er hat SAO geschaffen, um sich an dieser Welt zu erfreuen ...
Ha creato SAO per poter osservare un mondo?
¿Kayaba dijo que creo SAO...
Para observar o Mundo criou o SAO...
Those were Kayaba's words, then?
Das hat Kayaba gesagt?
Il professor Kayaba disse questo?
...para contemplar su mundo?
Disse o Prof. Kayaba, certo?
Yes.
Ja.
Sì.
Sí.
Sim.
What did you think
when you heard him say that?
Was hast du davon gehalten?
A questo proposito, tu che cosa pensasti?
¿Y qué pensaste entonces?
O que achaste?
I don't know... at the time, all I could think about
was surviving this sudden death game.
Ich weiß nicht. Ich hatte alle Hände voll damit zu tun,
dieses Death Game zu überleben.
Nella disperazione di dover sopravvivere
a un improvviso gioco mortale,
Lo único que me preocupaba era
sobrevivir a ese juego mortal.
Naquela altura só pensava
em sobreviver ao jogo,...
I had no time to wonder
about Kayaba's intentions.
Ich hatte keine Zeit,
mir über Kayabas Absichten Gedanken zu machen.
non mi preoccupai granché del piano di Kayaba...
No tuve tiempo para pensar
en las intenciones de Kayaba.
...e nem pensei nas intenções do Kayaba...
That's right. In order to survive,
I abandoned Klein.
Genau. Um zu überleben, habe ich Klein zurückgelassen.
Già, per sopravvivere abbandonai Klein...
Y me deshice de Klein
para poder sobrevivir.
Eu abandonei o Klein para viver.
I see.
Verstehe.
Capisco.
Ya veo.
Ai sim...
Then let's say goodbye here.
If something happens, send me a message.
Dann trennen sich hier wohl unsere Wege.
Schreib mir eine Nachricht, falls was passiert.
In questo caso, ci separiamo qui. Mandami un
messaggio in caso di novità importanti, okay?
Bueno, separémonos aquí.
Si te pasa algo, envíame un mensaje.
Então vamo-nos separar aqui.
Alguma coisa manda mensagem.
Sure!
Jep.
Certo!
Vale.
Sim.
Okay. See you around, Klein.
Also, wir sehen uns, Klein.
Bene. Allora ci vediamo presto, Klein.
Hasta luego, Klein.
Então até um dia, Klein.
Kirito!
Kirito.
Hey...
Hey.
Ehi!
¡Escucha!
Hei!
Kirito. The real you is
actually kinda cute, huh?
Kirito, du siehst knuddeliger aus, als ich gedacht hätte.
Il tuo vero volto è meglio di
quanto potessi aspettarmi!
Kirito, eres más guapo
de lo que me esperaba.
Kirito, até depois!
Até tens uma cara fofa.
I like you better this way.
Gefällt mir viel besser.
Davvero, non è niente male!
Me gustas, tío.
Gosto muito.
And that unkempt face of yours
suits you 10 times better.
Dieser zerzauste Look passt auch viel besser zu dir!
Beh, anche tu stai dieci volte meglio,
con quella faccia da samurai errante.
Tú también me gustas más
con esos pelos de guerrero.
A cara de guerreiro também te fica bem!
I'm...
Ich ...
Io...
Yo...
Eu,...
I'm...
Ich werde
Io...
Yo...
Eu,...
I'm going to survive...
in dieser Welt
Riuscirò a sopravvivere...
Os demostraré que puedo sobrevivir...
Vou sobreviver...
In this world!
überleben!
in questo mondo!
...en este mundo.
...neste mundo!
Yippee! Nothing like a reserved pool!
Wah! Es ist toll,
das Schwimmbecken ganz für sich allein zu haben!
Avere la piscina tutta per noi è il massimo!
¡Toda la piscina para nosotras!
Wohoo! Esta piscina alugada é a máxima!
There's something really
refreshing about this, huh?
Und es ist ganz neu!
L'acqua sembra davvero fresca!
¡Qué limpia!
Tão fresca e pura!
I'm first!
Ich bin die Erste!
Io mi butto per prima!
¡Yo la primera!
Sou a primeira!
Hey, no fair, Liz!
Ah, das ist fies, Liz-san!
Ah, non è giusto, Liz!
¡Lis eres una pilla!
Oh então, Rizu?!
Hey, you two! You have to stretch
before going in, remember?
Hey ihr beiden! Ihr müsst euch erst aufwärmen!
Ehi, voi due, se non fate della ginnastica
di riscaldamento starete male!
¡Eh! ¿Y el calentamiento qué?
Então meninas? E o aquecimento?!
What are you splashing around like that for?
Ach, sei doch nicht so!
Perché mi stai schizzando?
¡Alegría, alegría!
De que te alegarais?
Oh, wow, it's cold!
Ist das kalt!
Ah, è fredda!
¡Qué fría!
Que fria!
When did you sneak this thing in?
Wann hast du den denn reingeschmuggelt?!
Si è portata dentro ‘sto coso
senza che ce ne accorgessimo...
¿De dónde has sacado eso?
Porque trouxeste isto?
In the first place, you can't practice
swimming with a float!
Du sollst doch Schwimmen lernen!
Insomma, questa dovrebbe essere
una lezione di nuoto, no?
¿Cómo vas a entrenar así?
Não serve de nada no treino!
Wait! You can't do that!
I'll sink without it!
Ja, aber, das geht nicht!
Ohne den geh ich unter!
No, aspetta, smettila!
Guarda che senza io annego!
¡N-no, no lo hagas!
¡Que me hundo!
Não! Pára!
Eu vou ao fundo se não usar!
No worries! After all, you've got two of
these fine things. No way are you gonna sink!
Keine Sorge! Mit diesen zwei
Prachtstücken kannst du gar nicht untergehen!
È tutto a posto! Hai queste due bellezze che
ti tengono a galla, vedrai che non affoghi!
Tranquila, tienes
un buen par de flotadores.
Não há problema!
Tens duas, não te afundas!
Stop it! Do you know where you're touching...
Nein! Was soll das denn?!
S-smettila, dove mi stai toccando?!
N-no, no me sobes...
Não toques aí!
I can't imagine what you're eating to
plump them up this much. Shame on you! Honestly!
Was muss man essen, damit sie so groß werden?
Unartiges Ding, du!
Ma che hai mangiato per averle così grosse?
Sei davvero imperdonabile, sai?
¿Qué tengo que comer
para que se me pongan tan hermosas?
O que comes para serem tão grandes?
Não pode ser!
Stop it!
Nein!
Noooo!
¡Jolín!
Pára!
Liz...
Liz ...
Lis...
Rizu...
Sorry.
Tut mir leid.
...chiedo scusa.
Perdón.
Desculpa.
Okay, why don't we start by having you
put your face in the water?
Fangen wir doch erst mal damit an,
das Gesicht unters Wasser zu halten.
Forza, per prima cosa cominciamo con
l'immergere la testa sott'acqua.
Empecemos por aprender
a sumergir la cabeza.
Então vamos começar
por meter a cara na água.
In order to survive SAO, revealed to be a death game,
most players acted together in parties they'd formed.
Um in SAO, das sich als Death Game entpuppt, zu überleben,
haben sich die meisten Spieler in Gilden zusammengeschlossen.
Per poter sopravvivere in SAO, divenuto un gioco mortale,
molti giocatori si sono uniti e organizzati in party.
Muchos jugadores formaron grupos
para sobrevivir al juego mortal de SAO.
Para se sobreviver no Jogo da morte SAO
é preciso que os jogadores formem uma equipa.
But you, Kirito, were mainly a solo player,
except for the very last phase, weren't you?
Aber du hast bis zum Endkampf meistens alleine gespielt, stimmt’s?
Tuttavia tu, Kirito, hai agito da solo con
l'esclusione delle fasi finali del gioco...
Pero tú, salvo la fase final,
siempre has jugado en solitario.
Mas tu fizeste tudo sozinho até
ao final não foi?
In a world where you would die for real once
your HP was depleted, why take such a risk?
Wieso bist du dieses Risiko in einer Welt, in der du stirbst,
wenn deine HP auf Null gesunken sind, eingegangen?
Perché hai fatto qualcosa di tanto rischioso in
un mondo in cui finendo gli Hit Point si moriva?
¿Por qué tanto riesgo sabiendo
que te jugabas la vida?
Porque é que fizeste isso
mesmo sendo tão arriscado?
Well, I never planned on becoming
a solo player from the get-go. But...
Ich hatte am Anfang auch nicht vor,
alleine zu spielen, aber ...
Io, fin dall'inizio, avevo intenzione
di giocare in solo. Però...
No tuve esa intención al principio,
pero...
Eu nunca quis jogar sozinho. Mas...
Why?
Wieso?!
Ma perché?!
¡¿Por qué?!
Porquê?
Why...
Wieso ...
Perché...
¿Por qué?
Porquê...
why did you let Diabel die?
Wieso hast du Diabel sterben lassen?!
Per quale motivo hai lasciato morire Diabel?!
¿Por qué dejaste morir a Diabel?
Porque é que deixaste o Diabel morrer?
Let him die?
Ihn sterben lassen?
Lasciato morire?
¿Qué le dejé morir?
Deixei?
Of course!
Ganz genau!
Esattamente!!
¡Claro que sí!
O que achas?!
You knew what technique
the boss would use!
Du wusstest doch, was der Boss alles drauf hat!
Tu avevi già visto le tecniche di
combattimento di quel mostro, vero?
¡Conocías las técnicas del jefe!
Tu sabias os truques do boss!
If you'd given us that information
up front, he wouldn't have died!
Wenn du uns das von Anfang an gesagt hättest,
hätte Diabel nicht sterben müssen!
Se fin dall'inizio avessi condiviso con noi
ciò che sapevi, Diabel non sarebbe morto!
Si nos las hubieses dicho antes,
Diabel aún seguiría vivo.
Se nos tivesses dito isso desde
o início ele não tinha morrido!
He must be an ex–beta tester!
Er war bestimmt ein Betatester!
Probabilmente lui... è un ex beta tester!
Seguro que antes era un beta tester.
Ele estava só a testar o jogo...
That's how he knew all about
the boss's attack patterns.
Deshalb kannte er das Angriffsmuster von dem Boss!
Ecco perché gli schemi d'attacco
del boss gli erano familiari!
Por eso se sabía
todos los ataques del jefe.
Por isso é que ele sabia
os ataques todos!
He knew, but he kept it from us!
Er hat es uns nur verschwiegen!
Li conosceva e non ce l'ha detto!
Se los sabía pero se calló.
E escondeu que sabia!
There’s gotta be others here too,
right? Those beta testers!
Hier sind noch mehr, oder?!
Ce ne sono altri, qui, vero?
Seguro que hay más como tú.
Quem mais?
Come out!
Gebt es doch zu, Betatester!
Avanti, cosa aspettate...!
Uscite allo scoperto!
Dad la cara, malditos beta testers.
Apareçam!
An ex?beta tester, did you say??
Hast du Betatester gesagt?
Ex beta tester, hai detto?!
¿Ex-beta tester?
Ex-Testador, dizes tu?
I wish you wouldn't compare
me to those newbies.
Bitte vergleicht mich nicht mit diesen lächerlichen Amateuren.
Ti spiacerebbe non mettermi sullo
stesso piano di quel branco di pivelli...?
No me compares con esos novatos.
Não quero treinar
com amadores como vocês.
W-What?
W... Wie bitte?!
C-che cosa?!
¿Q-qué has dicho?
Que dizes?
Most of the 1,000 people who won
SAO beta test slots were beginners
Die meisten der 1000 Betatester von
SAO waren total unerfahrene Anfänger,
Tra i mille beta tester scelti per questo gioco,
De los mil beta testers de SAO...
Praticamente todos
os 1000 testadores do SAO
who didn't even know
how to level up.
die nicht mal wussten, wie man richtig levelt.
c'erano quasi solo principianti, che non erano
nemmeno in grado di aumentare il proprio livello.
...casi nadie sabía cómo subir de nivel.
Eran unos principiantes.
Não saber subir de nível, uns amadores.
Even you guys are better than them.
Verglichen damit seid ihr viel besser.
Al momento attuale, voi siete
già molto meglio di loro...
Vosotros ahora sabéis más que ellos.
Vocês ainda vá lá que não vá...
But I'm not like those guys.
Aber mit ihnen hab ich nichts gemeinsam.
Io però sono molto diverso da quella gente...
Pero yo no soy como ellos.
...mas eu não sou dessa laia.
During the beta test, I made it to higher levels
than anyone else was able to reach.
Ich bin in der Beta-Phase weiter gekommen,
als jeder andere Spieler.
Durante il beta test ho conquistato livelli
che nessun altro era riuscito a raggiungere...
Durante el beta, subí a pisos
que nadie más pudo.
De entre os testadores,
fui em que conseguir passar de nível.
The reason I knew about
the boss's sword skills
Ich kannte die Katana-Skills des Bosses nur deshalb,
Se conoscevo l'abilità del boss,
Se las habilidades
con la katana del jefe...
Eu sabia dos poderes do boss...
was because I fought tons of monsters
with those skills on floors far above us.
weil ich in viel höheren
Ebenen gegen Monster mit Katana gekämpft habe.
è perché ho combattuto molti altri mostri che
la usavano, su piani ben più alti di questo.
...porque me harté de luchar
con monstruos en los pisos de arriba.
...porque cheguei até ao último nível.
I know lots of other things too.
Und ich weiß noch viel mehr als das.
E ci sono tante altre cose che so...
Y sé mucho más.
E ainda sei mais coisas.
Way more than any information broker.
Ich weiß sogar mehr als sämtliche Informanten zusammen.
Per questo non mi preoccupo di
cercare informatori che mi aiutino.
Mucho más de lo que sale
en cualquier guía.
Sei de muita coisa aliás.
W-What?
W... Was soll das?
Che... che cosa hai detto?
¿Q-qué has dicho?
Mas que é isso?
That's... That's way worse
than a beta tester!
Der ist ja viel schlimmer als ein Betatester!
Tu non sei un semplice beta tester,
sei anche peggio!
Tú no eres un beta tester.
Então e dizes que não és testador beta?
That’s cheating! You’re a cheater.
That’s what you are!
Du cheatest, du bist ein verdammter Cheater!
Tutto questo non è leale,
sei un maledetto cheater!
Eres un tramposo, un cheater.
Então és um Cheater!
Yeah, a cheater!
- Ja, ganz genau!
- Genau, ein Cheater!
Già, sei un cheater!
- Sí.
- Eso, un cheater.
- Sim!
- Cheater!
A beta tester and a cheater... A beater!
Ein cheatender Betatester! Das ergibt einen Beater!
Un beta cheater... ovvero un beater!
Eres un cheater de los beta tester.
¡Un beater!
Um Cheater Beta!
A beater... that’s a good name.
Ein Beater... Das klingt gut.
Beater, eh? È una bella definizione, mi piace.
Beater.
Me gusta como suena.
Bom nome esse.
That's right...
Genau.
Già,
Sí.
Sim.
I am a beater.
Ich bin ein Beater.
potete chiamarmi "beater"...
Yo soy un beater.
Eu sou beta.
From now on, don't confuse
me with the other testers.
Also vergleicht mich nicht mehr mit den anderen Testern.
così d'ora in poi eviterò di essere
paragonato agli ex beta tester.
Así que no me comparéis
con los ex-beta testers.
Não me confundam com testador.
Coat of Midnight
I see... So it was you who inspired the term “beater.”
Verstehe. Deinetwegen ist also der Begriff „Beater“ entstanden.
Ma guarda... Ad essertene uscito con
la parola “beater” sei stato tu, Kirito.
Tú creaste la palabra "beater", ¿eh?
Então foste tu
que arranjou essa palavra...
By assuming the role of the villain, you made sure that
Du hast den Groll gegenüber den Betatestern auf dich gelenkt,
damit es die anderen leichter haben.
Assumendoti il ruolo del cattivo, ti sei
attirato l'odio degli altri beta tester.
Te hiciste pasar por malo para evitar
que odiasen a los otros beta testers.
Fizeste uma clara separação entre ti
e os testadores.
the other beta testers wouldn't be treated with hostility.
That must have been a pretty painful role to take on.
Die Rolle des Bösewichts war sicher nicht angenehm.
Un compito parecchio spiacevole.
Fue un duro papel, ¿no?
Um trabalho chato...
It wasn't really all that painful, though...
So schlimm war es auch wieder nicht.
In realtà, non lo è stato particolarmente...
No, para nada.
Não foi nada de mais.
Sachi!
¡Sachi!
Kirito!
¡Kirito!
Sachi!
¡Sachi!
What was really painful was losing
someone you'd bonded with...
Wirklich schlimm war es,
Kameraden zu verlieren, die man liebgewonnen hatte ...
La cosa spiacevole è stata perdere
i compagni a cui ero legato...
Lo más duro es perder
a un camarada.
O mais difícil foi perder
a pessoa a quem estava ligado...
Well? Are you starting to get
used to being in the water?
Und? Hast du dich daran gewöhnt?
Beh, ti sei un po' abituata all'acqua?
¿Te has acostumbrado un poco?
Habituaste-te à água?
Yes, I can somehow manage to put my face
in the water now,
Ja, ich kann mein Gesicht jetzt schon unter Wasser halten,
aber die Augen bekomme ich noch nicht auf.
Sì, ma anche se riesco a tenere la testa sott'acqua,
non riesco ancora ad aprire gli occhi...
Si, ya puedo sumergir la cabeza
aunque no puedo abrir los ojos.
Já consigo meter a cabeça na água,
mas ainda não consigo abrir os olhos...
but I still can't open my eyes...
No need to rush it. Just try to
get used to it little by little.
Wir haben keine Eile.
Gewöhn dich langsam nach und nach daran.
Non serve avere fretta, basta
abituarsi poco alla volta.
Tú tranquila, poco a poco.
Não há pressa, devagar se vai ao longe!
Why don't we take a break now?
Wollen wir erst mal eine Pause machen?
Ora prendiamoci un po' di pausa.
¿Descansamos ya?
Vamos fazer uma pausa?
Roger!
OK.
Certo!
Now this is what you call summertime...
Wie schön der Sommer ist.
Aah... È proprio estate!
Ya llegó el verano, ¿eh?
É mesmo Verão...
It totally is, isn't it?
Ja, wirklich.
Davvero!
Sí, por fin.
É mesmo.
The area we're heading to on this quest...
isn't it summer there all year, too?
Im Gebiet unserer nächsten Quest gibt es ewigen Sommer, oder?
Anche nell'area dove facciamo
le quest adesso è sempre estate.
En la próxima aventura vamos
a un área tropical, ¿no?
Na área da missão também era verão?
It's way in the southern part of the Sylph territory,
so I hear it's pretty hot there.
Das Territorium der Sylphen liegt weit im Süden,
darum ist es da ziemlich warm.
Il regno di Syplh è nel profondo Sud,
quindi fa molto caldo.
Está al sur de Sylph
y parece ser muy calurosa.
É a sul de Sylph, é muito quente!
And they say it's loaded with traps we've never seen
before, so that's something to look forward to!
Es soll auch ein ganz neues Feature geben.
Ich freu mich schon drauf.
E dato che fino ad ora non sembrano
esserci trappole, è anche piacevole.
Me apetece mucho ir porque dicen
que hay muchos artefactos nuevos.
Ainda não experimentei,
mal posso esperar!
We have to make sure that Kirito doesn't get
too fired up and rush off on his own, right?
Wir müssen aufpassen, dass Kirito vor lauter
Enthusiasmus nicht Hals über Kopf losstürmt.
Kirito è sin troppo entusiasta,
quindi ci tocca corrergli dietro.
Habrá que vigilar a Kirito para que
se vuelva a lanzar a lo loco.
É preciso ter cuidado com o Kirito,
ele quando está agitado...
I've been meaning to ask you this, but...
Ich wollte euch das schon lange mal fragen:
In effetti è da un po' che me lo chiedo...
Hace tiempo que os lo quería preguntar.
Já estava para perguntar...
How did you all meet my brother?
Wie habt ihr meinen Bruder eigentlich kennengelernt?
Ma voi in che modo avete
conosciuto il fratellone?
¿Cómo conocisteis a mi hermano?
Como conheceram o meu irmão?
Well, I was under attack by a bunch
of monsters when Kirito rescued me.
Kirito-san hat mir geholfen, als ich von einem
Monster angegriffen wurde.
Io sono stata salvata di Kirito una volta
in cui venni attaccata da dei mostri.
Kirito me salvó cuando
me atacaban unos monstruos.
Ele ajudou-me uma vez que estava
a ser atacada por um monstro.
Pina!
¡Pina!
Pina... Pina!
Pina! Pina!
Pina, Pina!
¡Pina, Pina!
Pina! Pina!
Pina.
Pina!
Pina...
Pina.
Pina!
Pina... Pina!
Pina Pina
Pina, Pina!
¡Pina, Pina!
Pina. Pina.
Pina!
¡Pina!
Pina...
Pina!
Pina.
Why would you do all this for me?
Wieso tust du das alles für mich?
Scusa ma... come mai ti dai
tanto da fare per me?
¿Por qué has hecho todo esto por mí?
Porque fazes isso?
If you promise not to laugh, I'll tell you.
Wenn du versprichst, mich nicht auszulachen, sag ich’s dir.
Te lo dico solo se prometti di non
metterti a ridere. Siamo d'accordo?
Te lo diré,
si me prometes no reírte.
Eu digo se prometeres não te rir.
I won't laugh.
Versprochen.
Te lo prometto.
Prometido.
Não me rio.
It's because you look like my little sister...
Du erinnerst mich an meine kleine Schwester.
Okay, allora. Il fatto è che tu...
somigli tanto a mia sorella.
Porque te pareces
a mi hermana pequeña.
Pareces a minha irmã mais nova.
I'm sorry.
Entschuldige.
Scusami tanto!
Perdona.
Desculpa.
Who else but Kirito can say something
like that with a straight face?
Das sieht ihm ähnlich, so was ernsthaft zu sagen!
È proprio il tipo di cosa che direbbe
lui con l'espressione tutta seria!
Solo él diría algo así tan serio.
Dizer isso com
uma cara séria é mesmo dele.
Still... Suguha, you and Keiko
don't really look alike at all, do you?
Aber eigentlich sehen sich
Suguha und Keiko doch gar nicht ähnlich, oder?
Però in effetti Suguha e Keiko non
si assomigliano quasi per niente...
Pero, vosotras dos os parecéis
bien poco, ¿no?
Mas vocês nem são parecidas.
Wh-What are you comparing?
W... Was vergleichst du denn?!
S-su quale aspetto ci stai confrontando?!
¿Q-qué estás comparando?
O que comparas?
After that, Kirito went on
an adventure with me to save Pina.
Danach haben wir zusammen ein Abenteuer unternommen,
um Pina zu retten.
Dopodiché, per salvare Pina, Kirito
è venuto in missione insieme a me...
Luego, Kirito me acompañó
para salvar a Pina.
E mais, para ajudar a Pina ele fez
a missão comigo.
Go on. Take it.
Nimm sie dir schon.
Su, coraggio. Puoi prenderlo.
Cógela.
Segura nela.
Pneuma Flower・
Pneuma-Blume
"FIORE DI PNEUMA"
"FLOR DEL PNEUMA"
"FLOR DE PNEUMA"
This will bring Pina back to life, right?
Die Blume wird Pina wiederbeleben, ja?
Allora, con questo Pina tornerà in vita?
¿Con esto puedo resucitar a Pina?
A Pina pode reviver com isto certo?
Yeah.
Ja.
Già.
Sí.
Sim.
I'm so glad...
Gott sei Dank.
È meraviglioso.
Qué bien.
Ainda bem!
But there are lots of strong monsters around here.
Let's revive it after we get back to town.
Aber hier sind viele starke Monster unterwegs.
Wir sollten sie in der Stadt wiederbeleben.
Qui circolano mostri molto forti. Sarà meglio
resuscitare Pina dopo essere tornati in città.
Pero por aquí hay muchos monstruos.
Mejor la resucitamos en la ciudad.
Aqui há muitos monstros,
vamos revivê-la depois de regressarmos à cidade.
I'm sure that Pina would prefer it that way too.
Pina wäre Pina sicher auch lieber.
Sono sicuro che anche lei sarebbe d'accordo.
Seguro que Pina te lo agradecerá.
É melhor assim.
Nein!
No!
¡Socorro!
Ai!
Calm down, Silica! This one’s really weak!
Ganz ruhig, Silica! Das ist ein schwaches Monster!
Calmati, Silica. È un mostro da niente.
Silica, cálmate.
Es muy débil.
Acalma-te! Ele é bem fraco.
K-Kirito, save me!
Don't look, but save me!
Kirito-san! Hilf mir bitte, aber schau nicht hin!
Aiuto! Salvami, Kirito!
Ti prego, non guardare, ma salvami!
¡Kirito, sálvame!
¡Pero no me mires!
Kirito, ajuda-me! Não olhes!
- That's impossible.
- Enough is enough!
Das wird nicht gehen.
È fuori discussione...
No creo que pueda...
É difícil...
D-Darn you...
Enough is enough!
Jetzt reicht’s mir!
Ehi tu, lasciami andare!
¡Ahora verás!
Para aprenderes!
Did you see anything?
Hast du’s gesehen?
...che cosa hai visto?
¿Lo has visto?
Olhaste?
In my case, it's not like we had
a dramatic encounter like Silica's...
Bei mir war es nicht so dramatisch wie bei Silica.
Il mio incontro con lui non è stato
drammatico quanto quello di Silica...
Mi encuentro no fue tan dramático
como el tuyo, Silica.
O meu encontro
não foi dramático como o teu...
Welcome to Lisbeth's Smith Shop!
Willkommen in Lizbeths Schmiedewerkstatt!
Benvenuto all'Armeria di Lisbeth!
¡Bienvenido a la armería de Lisbeth!
Bem-vindo à Lisebete!
U-Uh... I'd like to order
a custom-made weapon.
Ähm, ich würde gerne ein maßgefertigtes Schwert kaufen.
Ah, salve... Vorrei un'arma su ordinazione.
¿Me podrías hacer
un encargo a medida?
Queria uma coisa personalizada...
Does he have enough money?
Kann er sich so was überhaupt leisten?
Questo qui avrà abbastanza soldi?
¿Tendrá dinero?
Será que consegue pagar...?
At the moment, metal prices are high.
Im Moment sind die Metallpreise ziemlich überteuert ...
Devo avvisarti, il prezzo dei metalli è
aumentato, potrebbe essere costoso.
Es que el precio del metal
se ha encarecido y...
O preço do metal aumentou...
Don't worry about the cost. I just want
the best sword you can make right now.
Geld ist überhaupt kein Problem. Ich würde nur gerne das beste
Schwert haben,da s du schmieden kannst.
I soldi non sono un problema. Vorrei la spada migliore
che le tue skills ti consentono di forgiare.
No te preocupes por el dinero.
Hazme mejor espada que sepas.
O preço não é problema.
Quero é uma boa espada.
That's somewhat vague.
Sehr gerne, aber ...
Mi servono altri dettagli.
La cosa no es tan fácil...
Mesmo assim...
You'll have to give me an idea
of your target quality level.
Vorher muss ich wissen, welche Stats es haben soll.
Anzi... l'ideale sarebbe conoscere i valori
esatti delle prestazioni che desideri.
Dime antes para qué la quieres.
Precisamos de ver
uma amostra semelhante...
Oh, I see.
Oh, natürlich.
Va bene, posso farlo.
Vale, ya te entiendo.
Ah, aqui está.
Then something of the same
quality as this or better?
Ich hätte gerne eines mit mindestens genauso guten
Stats wie bei diesem Schwert hier.
Se mi servisse un'arma con capacità
pari o superiori a questa?
Pues quiero una espada
más fuerte que ésta.
Se pudesse ser como esta aqui...
Hm ...
Vediamo...
A ver...
Sim.
An Elucidator...
Elucidator?
L'Elucidator?!
"Elucidator".
Elucidator.
It's a beast of a magic sword
obtainable from monster drops.
Das ist ein verfluchtes
Dämonenschwert von einem Monster-Drop.
È fra le spade magiche più potenti
che si possano sottrarre a un mostro!
Es una espada mágica "matamonstruos"
fuera de lo común.
Esta espada é tipo
o monstro das espadas.
Can you make one?
Kriegst du das hin?
Potresti farlo?
¿Podrás hacerme una?
É possível?
How about this one?
Was hältst du von dem hier?
Che te ne pare di questa?
¿Qué tal ésta?
Que tal esta?
It's the best I've ever forged. My masterpiece!
Das ist mein absolutes Meisterstück.
Ne vado molto fiera.
È il mio capolavoro assoluto!
Es mi obra maestra.
É a obra-prima que forgei.
It's a little light...
Ist ein bisschen leicht ...
Non so, mi sembra un po' leggera...
Quizás demasiado ligera.
É um bocado leve...
Well, I did use a speed-type metal to forge it.
In ihm ist ein Metall verarbeitet, das den Speed erhöht.
Solo perché ho usato un metallo
specifico per la velocità.
Claro, para que sea más rápida.
Foi feita para ser veloz.
Would you mind if I tested it?
Darf ich es kurz austesten?
E potrei sperimentarla un attimo?
¿Puedo probarla?
Será que posso experimentar?
Test it?
Was testen?
Come, sperimentarla?
¿Probarla dices?
Experimentar?
You know, its durability.
Die Haltbarkeit.
Per capire se è resistente.
Sí, para ver su aguante.
A resistência.
H-Hey! Your sword will
break in two if you do that!
W... Warte! Wenn du das machst,
wirst du dein Schwert zerbrechen!
Ehi! No, aspetta un attimo!
In quel modo, spezzerai la tua spada!
¡Quieto!
¡Romperás tu espada!
Olha que se fizeres isso
a tua espada parte-se!
If that happens, it'll just be... too bad!
Mach dir darum mal keine Sorgen.
Nel caso, ci penserò dopo.
¡Ahora lo sabremos!
Vamos ver!
He comes in and snaps a sword for sale in two,
so my first impression was absolutely awful.
Er hat einfach meine Ware zerbrochen.
Damit hat er einen schlechten ersten Eindruck hinterlassen.
Mi distrusse senza preavviso una spada in vendita,
quindi la mia prima impressione fu pessima.
Se presenta y me rompe mi espada.
Me cayó fatal.
Partir a espada que estava à venda,
para primeira impressão... mau!
S-Sorry about that...
D... Das tut mir leid.
C-chiedo scusa da parte sua...
L-lo siento...
Desculpa...
Kirito tends to do
the most outrageous things sometimes, huh?
Manchmal macht Kirito-san echt verrückte Sachen.
In effetti Kirito ogni tanto
faceva cose davvero assurde.
Kirito a veces se pasa, ¿eh?
Ele faz coisas disparadas às vezes...
Another time, we fell into a dragon's burrow together,
and then he tossed some dragon poop right at me,
Danach sind wir zusammen in ein
Drachennest gefallen und wurden mit Drachen-Kot beworfen!
Senza contare di quando cademmo insieme nella tana
di quel drago, e lui poi ci si scagliò contro...
Nos caímos en un nido de dragón,
me lanzó caca de dragón...
Cair em buracos de dragões e ser atirado
com cocó de dragões...
so I hardly have any decent memories of him...
Nicht gerade eine angenehme Erinnerung.
Non erano certo dei bei ricordi.
Vamos, un encanto.
Não me lembro de nada bom...
Sorry, Liz.
Tut mir leid, Liz.
S-scusalo tanto, Liz...
Lo siento, Lis.
Desculpa, Rizu.
Oh, but looking back now,
they're all good memories!
Ach, inzwischen denk ich gerne daran zurück.
Beh, ora sono diventati piacevoli.
Tranquila, ahora me hace gracia.
Mas agora são boas memórias!
It's warm.
Du bist so warm.
Sento il suo calore.
Qué calidez.
Quentinho...
Ja.
Sì.
Sí.
Sim.
Even though you and I are
both data in a virtual world...
Dabei sind wir auch nur Daten in dieser virtuellen Welt ...
In questo universo virtuale non siamo
altro che file di dati, eppure...
Si tú y yo solo somos datos
de este mundo virtual.
Mesmo no mundo virtual nós dois...
Liz...
Liz ...?
Lis...
Rizu...
Amazing!
Wahnsinn!
È bellissimo!
¡Es genial!
Fixe!
Kirito!
Kiritooo!
¡Kirito!
Kirito!
You know what?
Weißt du was?
Devo dirti una cosa!
¿Sabes?
Sabes eu...
What?
Was denn?
Sì, che cosa?
¿Qué?
O quê?
I... I like you, Kirito!
Ich bin in dich verliebt!
Ecco, io... credo proprio di amarti!
¡Me gustas mucho!
Eu, eu gosto de ti!
What? I can't hear you!
Was hast du gesagt? Ich hör dich nicht!
Non ho capito niente!
C'è troppo frastuono, qui!
¿Qué?
No te oigo.
O quê? Não ouço nada!
It's nothing!
Macht nichts!
Fa lo stessooo!
¡Da igual!
Não é nada!
Tell Asuna what you just told me.
Du solltest Asuna erzählen, was du mir gerade anvertraut hast.
Devi dire anche ad Asuna... quello
che hai detto a me poco fa, d'accordo?
Dile lo mismo a Asuna.
Diz aquilo à Asuna.
Liz...
Liz ...
Lis.
Rizu.
I'm fine!
Mir geht’s gut.
Io starò bene!
Estaré bien.
Está tudo bem.
This warmth will still linger for a while.
Ich kann deine Wärme noch spüren.
Mi godrò questo dolce calore
ancora per qualche minuto.
Todavía queda un poco
de aquella calidez.
Ainda sinto o nosso calor...
So... please...
Darum hab ich eine Bitte.
Ma tu fammi un favore.
Por eso te lo pido.
Por isso, por favor...
End this world, Kirito.
Bitte setz dieser Welt ein Ende.
Ti prego, Kirito... metti fine a
questo assurdo gioco.
Acaba con este mundo.
Acaba com este mundo...
Until then, I’m sure that I can hang on!
Bis dahin gebe auch ich mein Bestes.
Fino ad allora... io saprò farmi forza.
Yo me esforzaré hasta entonces.
...que eu espero por ti...
I don't know...
Er braucht aber lange ...
Chissà se...
Pues eso...
Que coisa...
Wonder if he's making out with that
gorgeous doctor right about now. Damn him!
Flirtet er jetzt etwa wirklich mit unserer sexy Lehrerin rum?
Dieser Kerl ...
In questo momento sta facendo le birichinate
con quella bella dottoressa, quello là.
Seguro ahora estará tonteando
con la psicóloga "modelo"...
Será que estão no namorico...?
Aquele gajo...
Look, Kirito ? right there.
Schau, Kirito-kun, hier!
Su, Kirito, qui.
Ves, Kirito.
Aquí.
Hei, Kirito. Aqui.
- Where?
- Right here.
Wo?
- Da!
- Uhm? Dove?
- Qui, qui.
- ¿Dónde?
- Aquí, aquí.
- Onde?
- Aqui, aqui.
Where?
Wo denn?
Dove?
¿Pero dónde?
Onde!?
These coordinates here.
Diese Koordinate.
A queste coordinate.
Mira en estas coordenadas.
Estas coordenadas.
Are all the high-level players gathered
here because it's a boss raid?
War das hier ein Bosskampf, für den sich lauter
Spieler auf hohem Level zusammengetan haben?
Vi si sono riuniti giocatori di alto livello,
c’è stato forse uno scontro contro un boss?
Hay muchos jugadores de nivel alto.
¿Es un combate contra un jefe?
É aqui que os de nível mais alto se juntam,
é aqui a luta com o Boss?
What can I say...?
Was denn?
Beh, che c’è?
Desde luego...
Não.
It's just that I was surprised to see
that when it came to boss fights,
Selbst der stärkste Solo-Spieler,
Kirito-kun, hat sich für die Bosskämpfe
Pensavo che anche tu, Kirito, il migliore dei
giocatori in solitaria, ti unissi comunque
Me sorprende que un jugador solitario
tan fuerte como tú...
Mesmo que sejas dos jogadores solo
mais fortes, nas lutas com bosses...
even you, the most powerful solo player
of all, would still take part in raid parties.
jeder Ebene einem Raid angeschlossen, oder?
a un raid party per sconfiggere
i boss di ogni livello.
...participe en una incursión.
...tens que ter uma equipa do zero.
Of course I would.
Basically, a floor boss can't be overcome by a solo player.
Ist doch klar.
Ovviamente.
Pues claro.
Mas é claro.
Die Bosse waren grundsätzlich nicht alleine zu bewältigen.
Riuscire a sconfiggere i floor boss in solo
è fondamentalmente impossibile.
No se puede luchar solo
contra los jefes de cada nivel.
Não dá para lutar a solo com
um boss desses.
Actually, there are more floor bosses than you'd
think who'd be a threat even if you were in a party.
Selbst im Raid waren die meisten Bosse noch harte Brocken.
E poi, i boss pericolosi anche formando un
raid party non sono pochi.
Y aunque hagamos una incursión
siguen siendo muy peligrosos.
E esses bosses não são poucos.
The sword skills of the first floor boss, Illfang the Kobold Lord,
Der Schwert-Skill des ersten Bosses, Illfang,
La tecnica di spada del boss del primo livello,
Illfang il signore dei coboldi,
Illfang el Lord Kobold,
jefe del primer piso...
O nível de Skill do 1º boss,
Ilfang o Lorde dos Goblins,...
were powerful enough to partially destroy our raid...
hat den halben Raid vernichtet.
è stata in grado di annientare metà del raid...
...era tan poderoso que pudo matar
a medio grupo...
...dava para destruir uma equipa.
Diabel!
Watch out!
Vorsicht!
Attento!
¡Cuidado!
É perigoso!
I'll get you first!
Triff!
Colpisci!
¡Toma!
Toma!
Crap!
Scheiße!
Maledizione!
¡Mierda!
Bolas!
When we took on the floor 74 boss, Gleam Eyes…
Den Boss von Ebene 74, Gleam Eyes,
Sconfissi in qualche modo il boss
del settantaquattresimo livello,
Con el jefe del piso 74, Gleam Eyes...
O boss do nível 74, o Gleam Eyes.
Although I defeated it somehow
by using my dual-wielding skill,
habe ich gerade so mit meinem Zwei-Schwerter-Skill besiegt.
Gleam Eyes, usando la mia
tecnica segreta a due spade
...tuve que emplear mi técnica secreta
delas dos espadas.
Usando ataques especiais há-de se safar.
I came this close to getting myself killed.
Um ein Haar wäre ich draufgegangen.
ma rischiai seriamente di morire.
Pero aún así, casi me mata.
Escapei de morrer.
Starburst Stream!
Star Burst Stream!
Starburst... Stream!
¡Starburst Stream!
Starburst Stream!
Wh-What is that skill?
Was für ein Skill ist das?
Ma che diavolo è quella skill?!
¿De dónde ha sacado eso?
Mas que é aquilo?
Faster...
Schneller!
Veloce...
Rápido.
Even faster!
Noch schneller!
Più veloce...
Más rápido.
Mais rápido!
But in Aincrad, there was something
more terrifying than any floor boss.
Aber in Aincrad gab es noch Furchterregenderes, als die Bosse.
Però, ad Aincrad c’erano creature ancora
più pericolose dei floor boss.
Pero, en Aincrad hay algo mucho peor
que los jefes de cada nivel.
Haviam seres mais fortes que
os bosses em Aincrad.
Oh? What was that?
Ach, und das wäre?
Oh, e quali?
¿Ah sí?
¿El qué?
O quê?
The players themselves.
Die Spieler.
I giocatori.
Son los jugadores.
O jogador.
The players?
Die Spieler?
I giocatori?
¿Los jugadores?
O jogador?
Yes. The bosses' parameters were formidable, sure.
But ultimately, they were just programs.
Ja. Die Parameter der Monster waren zwar heftig,
aber letztlich waren sie nur Programme.
Anche se i parametri dei boss erano temibili, dopotutto
non potevano superare la propria programmazione.
Los parámetros de los jefes asustan,
pero solo son un programa.
O boss pode ser uma ameaça,
mas não passa de um programa.
You could deal with them once
you figured out their attack patterns,
Man muss nur ihre Angriffsmuster kennen.
Riuscendo a comprendere lo
schema dei loro attacchi,
Puedes hacerles frente,
si sabes sus patrones de ataque.
Dá para nos defendermos se soubermos
o padrão de ataque.
and since they never emerged from the boss rooms,
you could escape if it came to that...
Sie kommen nie aus den Boss-Räumen,
also kann man notfalls fliehen.
dato che i boss non potevano uscire dalle loro stanze,
in caso di pericolo si poteva sempre fuggire.
Y como no salen de su mazmorra,
puedes huir si estás en peligro.
Ele não sai da casa de Boss portanto
podemos fugir quando quisermos.
But red players were humans, just like yourself.
Aber die Red Player waren auch Menschen.
Però i giocatori rossi
erano anche loro esseri umani.
Pero los jugadores son humanos.
Mas os vermelhos também são humanos.
Spawning one new PK method after another,
they killed countless other players...
Sie haben sich ständig neue Wege für PKs ausgedacht und eine
Menge Spieler auf dem Gewissen.
Cercando di escogitare modalità di PK
sempre nuove, hanno ucciso molti giocatori...
Pronto empezaron a matar a otros
jugadores para robarles los ítems.
Inventam nos métodos PK
e conseguem jogadores.
Paralysis poison?
Lähmungsgift?!
Veleno paralizzante!
¿Veneno paralizante?
Paralisía.
What's this? So you're
afraid of dying after all?
Was denn? Hast du etwa Angst vor dem Tod?
Beh... che succede ora? Ti sei reso conto
che in fondo hai paura di morire?!
¿Tienes miedo de morir?
Sempre tens medo de morrer.
That's right...
Genau. Ich darf noch nicht sterben!
Esatto. Non posso ancora... morire!
No me matarás.
Sim, mas ainda cá estou.
I can't die yet!
Is that so?
Ach wirklich? Das gefällt mir!
Ma davvero? Ora sì che mi diverto!
Pues claro que sí.
Não me digas. Vamos tratar disso!
That's the way I like it!
Die! Die!
Stirb! Stirb! Stirb!
Muori! Muori! Muori!
¡Muere, muere!
Morre, morre, morre!
Die!
It wasn't just the battles with red players.
Nicht nur die Kämpfe gegen die Red Player,
E non combattei solo contro i giocatori rossi;
No solo he tenido que luchar
contra otros jugadores,...
Não só com os vermelhos,...
auch das Duell, bei dem ich mich Beweisen sollte,
war ein hoffnungsloser Kampf.
anche nei duelli di pura arte di spada
gareggiai non so quante volte.
...también me he visto obligado
a batirme en duelo muchas veces.
...também tive dificuldades com
as técnicas de espada.
I struggled time and time again
even in pure swordsmanship duels.
We're called the top guild, but our numbers
are never more than barely sufficient.
Man nennt uns zwar eine Top-Gilde,
aber auch wir stoßen an unsere Grenzen.
Siamo considerati la gilda più forte, ma il
nostro potenziale d’attacco è sempre al limite.
Aunque dicen que eres un as,
tu nivel de lucha es regular.
Por muito forte que se seja,
por vezes a força só vem ao fim.
He attacks with his shield?
Sein Schild?!
Con lo scudo?!
¡¿El escudo?!
Um escudo?
Splendid reaction time.
Du hast hervorragende Reflexe.
Il tuo tempo di reazione è straordinario!
Excelentes reflejos.
Bela velocidade de reacção...
I can strike!
Ich schaff es!
Posso farcela!
¡Ahora!
É agora!
And that brilliant player among players
„Die Ritter des Blutschwurs" war die Top-Gilde
Quel giocatore incredibile era Heathcliff,
il capo della gilda più forte,
Y en la cima de esa élite de jugadores...
O ponto forte desses
jogadores é a Guild.
was the leader of the Knights of
the Blood Oath Guild ? Heathcliff, right?
aus den geschicktesten
Spielern und Heathcliff ihr Kommandant, stimmt’s?
i Cavalieri del Giuramento
di Sangue, non è così?
...está Heathcliff, jefe del gremio
de los Caballeros del Pacto de Sangre.
O líder desse clã era o Heathcliff,
certo?
Yes. And ironically enough, it was my duel with Heathcliff
Ja. Und ironischerweise war dieses Duell ein Hinweis
Già. E forse sarò cinico,
ma il duello contro Heathcliff
Así es.
Y en el duelo contra Heathcliff...
Sim. E curiosamente a luta
com ele serviu-me...
that tipped me off about his true identity.
auf seine wahre Identität.
mi permise di raccogliere indizi
sulla sua vera natura.
...encontré una pista sobre
su verdadera identidad.
...para o compreender.
I made all kinds of things, so eat up, okay?
Ich habe reichlich zubereitet. Greift nur zu.
Ho preparato un sacco di cose,
quindi mangiate a volontà!
Comed lo que queráis.
He preparado mucho.
Há que chegue, comam à vontade.
Oh, I brought lunch, too, so please have some if you like...
Oh, ich habe auch ein Bentou dabei. Bedient euch ruhig.
Ah, anche io ho portato il pranzo
al sacco. Servitevi pure...
Yo también he traído cosas.
Comed si apetece.
Também trouxe a minha comida,
estão à vontade para tirar.
Let's dig in!
Guten Appetit!
Buon appetito!
¡Buen provecho!
Bom apetite!
Kazuto. Es wird noch eine Weile dauern. Esst ruhig schon mal.
"CI VORRÀ ANCORA TEMPO,
PRANZATE PURE SENZA DI ME."
"EMPEZAD A COMER.
AÚN TARDARÉ UN RATO."
"VOU DEMORAR, VÃO COMENDO."
It will be a while so please have lunch first
Who is it?
Von wem ist die?
Chi è?
¿De quién es?
De quem é?
Kirito. He says to start without him.
Kirito-kun schreibt, wir sollen ruhig schon essen.
Kirito. Dice di mangiare senza di lui.
De Kirito, que empecemos a comer.
É o Kirito a dizer para comermos.
Then I'll have Kirito's share for him!
Dann ess ich Kirito-kuns Portion gleich mit!
Beh, allora mi mangerò anche la sua porzione!
Pues yo me comeré su parte.
Então eu também como a parte dele.
Oh!
Ah!
No.
Ah.
You shouldn't do something like to him.
Das kannst du doch nicht machen!
Wir müssen ihm was übrig lassen.
Dai, poverino, non fargli questo!
Dobbiamo avanzare la sua parte.
Pobrecito, tenemos que dejarle algo.
Pára com isso.
Temos que deixar para ele.
We have to leave some for him.
Right, right.
Ist ja gut.
Ehi ehi!
Vale.
Hei, hei.
Wow! Asuna's lunch is so adorable.
Asuna-sans Bentou ist ja hübsch.
Uah! Il tuo pranzo al sacco
è adorabile, Asuna!
Halaaa, Asuna tu comida es preciosa.
Uau, o tua merenda é mesmo fofa.
I wonder if Kazuto prefers girls who are feminine
and can make lunches like this...
Mein Bruder steht wohl auf Mädchen,
die solche Bentous zubereiten können?
Come pensavo, per il fratellone ci vuole una
ragazza in grado di preparare un pranzo così...
¿A mi hermano le gustarán las chicas
tan femeninas como ella?
O melhor para o mano é uma mulher
que saiba preparar a merenda assim.
What's the matter, Suguha?
Was ist los, Suguha-chan?
Che succede, Suguha?
¿Qué te pasa Suguha?
Que foi, Suguha?
Oh, nothing...
Ach, gar nichts.
Ah, no, nulla...
Ah, es que...
Ah, nada, nada.
I was just wondering how you and my brother met, see...
Ich habe mich nur gerade gefragt,
wie du und mein Bruder euch kennengelernt habt.
Mi stavo chiedendo in che tipo di situazione
vi foste incontrati tu e il fratellone, Asuna.
Tengo curiosidad por saber cómo
conociste a mi hermano.
Estava a pensar como é
que vocês se terão conhecido...
Äh ...
Ehm...
Pues...
Eh.
- I want to hear all about that!
- I'd like to hear it, too!
- Los, erzähl!
- Das will ich auch wissen!
- Voglio sentire quella storia!
- Sì, anche io!
-¡Sí, quiero saberlo!
-¡Yo también!
- Quero saber!
- Eu também!
But...
Aber ...
Però...
Es que...
Mas...
Come on! We just told you how we met him!
Komm schon, wir haben es vorhin auch erzählt!
Eddai, anche noi prima
abbiamo raccontato le nostre!
Anda, que nosotras ya lo hemos dicho.
Tudo bem, já falámos disto...
That's right, you're the only one
who hasn't talked about it yet!
Stimmt, nur du hast dich davor gedrückt!
È vero, Asuna, sei l'unica
che non ha ancora parlato.
Eso.
Solo faltas tú, Asuna.
A única que não falou foi a Asuna!
Well, I guess I have no choice.
Dann hab ich wohl keine Wahl ...
Beh... Non posso farci niente.
En fin... Que remedio.
Bem, nada a fazer...
- Yay!
- Juhu!
- Evvai!
- ¡Viva!
- ¡Genial!
- Yay! Fixe!
- Hei.
It was at a boss raid meeting in a town called
Tolbana on the first floor that I first met Kirito.
Also, zum ersten Mal habe ich Kirito
La prima volta che incontrai Kirito
La primera vez que me encontré con él...
A primeira vez que conheci
o Kirito foi....
in Tolbana, auf Ebene 1,
bei der Kampfbesprechung getroffen.
fu in una città chiamata Torbana, in cui si teneva
un incontro per conquistare il primo piano.
...fue en Torbana, la aldea del primer
piso donde nos explicaron las reglas.
Na cidade da reunião estratégica do 1º nível,
Torbana.
At the time, all I could think about was clearing the game.
Damals konnte ich an nichts anderes denken,
als das Spiel zu schaffen.
In quel momento tutto quello a cui
pensavo era come finire il gioco.
En aquella época solo pensaba
en completar el juego.
Naquela altura só pensava
em acabar o jogo.
Do you really think it's good?
Findest du das echt lecker?
Pensi sul serio che sia buono?
¿En serio que te gusta?
A sério que gostas?
Of course.
Und wie.
Ma certo.
Claro.
Ever since I came to this town,
I've been eating at least one daily.
Seit ich in der Stadt bin,
esse ich jeden Tag mindestens eins.
Da quando sono in questa città,
ogni giorno ne mangio almeno uno.
Desde que vine aquí,
me como una al día.
Desde que vim que como uma vez por dia.
I do change it up a little though.
Ich variiere es nur ein bisschen.
Anche se in realtà lo miglioro un po'.
Bueno, tengo un truco.
Bem, cá tenho o meu esquema.
Change it up?
Variieren?
Migliori?
¿Un truco?
Esquema?
Try putting some on the bread.
Mach mal etwas hiervon auf dein Brot.
Prova a metterci questa sopra.
Úntalo en el pan.
Experimenta no pão.
Cream?
Butter?
È crema?
¿Crema?
Creme?
But Kirito showed me that you
could enjoy life even in Aincrad...
Aber Kirito-kun hat mir die schönen Seiten des Lebens
in Aincrad gezeigt.
Però Kirito mi ha insegnato che anche io
potevo vivere felicemente ad Aincrad...
Kirito me enseñó que podía disfrutar
de la vida en Aincrad.
Ele ensinou-me que
em Aincrad também há alegria de viver.
Oh. It's only you.
Ach so. Du bist’s nur.
Ah, sei tu.
¿Tú por aquí?
Que queres?
Everyone else in the Assault Team is
going all out to clear the dungeon, so...
Die anderen an der Front mühen sich in den Dungeons ab.
Gli altri giocatori si stanno battendo
con tutte le loro forze nei dungeon,
Todos los del grupo se esfuerzan
por salir del laberinto...
Estão todos perdidos no labirinto...
What are you doing
taking a nap out here?
Warum hältst du hier seelenruhig ein Nickerchen?
tu invece te ne stai qui tranquillo
a schiacciare un pisolino.
...y tú aquí tirado durmiendo la siesta.
...e tu aqui a relaxado a descansar.
Even solo players need to
take this more seriously—
Selbst als Einzelgänger solltest du etwas ernster ...
Ho capito che sei un solitario, ma stai esagerando!
Aunque juegues solo,
deberías ser más serio.
Mesmo que estejas a solo podias ajudar!
Not only is this Aincrad’s
nicest season,
Heute ist in Aincrad das beste Wetter und die schönste Jahreszeit.
Oggi ad Aincrad è impostata la stagione più mite
dell'anno. È la condizione migliore che possa capitare.
Hoy está programado que sea
el mejor día de esta estación.
Opá hoje é o dia com melhor tempo
em Aincrad.
but today’s weather is
at its optimum setting.
Hä?
Eh?
¿Qué?
Quê?
Diving into a dungeon on a
day like this is a waste.
In irgendeinem Dungeon herumzulungern wäre Verschwendung.
È un peccato infilarsi nei labirinti
in una giornata così.
No quiero desperdiciar este día
por el laberinto.
Labirinto num dia destes
é um desperdício.
Do you even understand
what’s going on?
Verstehst du es nicht?
Ma non capisci?
¿Eres consciente de lo que haces?
Mas tu estás bem?
Every day we waste here is one
more we've lost in the real world.
Jeder verschwendete
Tag hier ist ein verlorener Tag in der realen Welt!
Per ogni giorno perso qui a non combinare niente, anche
il nostro tempo nel mondo reale diventa uno spreco!
Cada día que pasamos aquí,
lo perdemos en nuestra vida real.
Também perdemos tempo de vida
no mundo real!
But right now, the place where
we're alive is here in Aincrad.
Aber jetzt gerade leben wir nun mal in Aincrad.
Ma la verità è che ora noi viviamo ad Aincrad.
Pero ahora vivimos aquí en Aincrad.
Mas onde estamos a viver agora é
em Aincrad.
See?
Siehst du? Der Wind und das Sonnenlicht fühlen sich echt toll an.
Visto? I raggi del sole e
il vento sono così piacevoli...
¿Ves?
El sol y la brisa son tan agradables.
O vento e a luz do sol são
tão agradáveis.
The wind and sunlight feel so good.
Do they?
Ach ja? Ist das Wetter nicht immer gleich?
A dire il vero, credevo che il tempo
fosse più o meno sempre uguale.
A mí todos los días me parecen igual.
Que dizes? O tempo é sempre o mesmo...
Isn’t the weather always the same?
If you were to lie down
like me, you'd understand.
Wenn du dich auch kurz hinlegen würdest,
würdest du es verstehen.
Prova a sdraiarti anche tu e capirai cosa intendo.
Túmbate un poco y lo notarás.
Se te deitasses percebias.
Wah!
Ah!
¡Hala!
Uau...
Hey, take a look at that.
Hey, seht euch die mal an!
Ehi, guardate laggiù!
Mirad, mirad.
Olha isto!
Taking a nap at this time of day?
Am helllichten Tag zu schlafen ...
Non è mica ora di dormire!
¿La siesta a estas horas?
A descansar agora?
Some people don't have
a care in the world.
Manche haben echt die Ruhe weg.
Chissà chi sono.
Los hay despreocupados, ¿eh?
Mas que festa...
Who are they? Jeez...
Wer sind die beiden? Meine Güte ...
Roba da matti!
Desde luego...
Esta gente, enfim...
I didn't think she'd really fall asleep.
Sie ist tatsächlich eingeschlafen ...
Non credevo si addormentasse sul serio.
Me he quedado frito...
Adormeceu...
W... What...
Morning.
Guten Morgen. Hast du gut geschlafen?
Buongiorno a te. Fatto una bella dormita?
Buenos días.
¿Has dormido bien?
Hei, dormiste bem?
Sleep well?
One meal...
Ein Essen ...
Ti offro la cena.
Una comida.
Comida, 1 vez.
A meal!
Ich werde dich zum Essen einladen. Dann sind wir quitt. Okay?
Sì, la cena! Quello che preferisci, te lo pago io.
Così saremo pari, d'accordo?
Te invito a comer o a lo que quieras.
Y en paz, ¿vale?
Ofereço-te uma refeição, que tal?
I'll treat you one time
to anything you want.
Then we'll be even! Deal?
From what you just said, it sounds like
you were the one who fell for Kirito first!
Jetzt wo ich das so höre, scheint mir,
du hast dich als allererste in ihn verknallt!
Ciò che mi pare di capire da questa storia è che
sei stata tu la prima ad innamorarti, Asuna...
Así que te colgaste tu primero
de Kirito, ¿eh?
A ver assim, parece que a primeira
a gostar dele foi a Asuna.
N-No, it wasn't like that...
D... Das stimmt nicht!
N-no, non direi...
N-no pasó eso...
N-não é nada disso...
Hey, hey, don't hide it!
Tu doch nicht so!
Su, non nasconderlo!
Venga, no lo escondas.
Não mintas, é feio.
Als du bei mir dein Schwert hast schleifen lassen,
hast du doch gesagt „Es ist noch einseitig“!
Ma sei ogni volta che venivi a farti affilare la
spada mi dicevi "È un sentimento a senso unico"!
¿No dijiste que aún no te gustaba
cuando se presentó en tu armería?
E tu que dizias que não era nada, mesmo
depois de ele ter ido polir a espada.
You came in to hone your sword one day
and said, “Well, it's still one-way!” Remember?
Y-Yeah...
J... Ja ...
S-sì.
Mmm...
Bem...
So how did you go about wooing him
and telling him how you felt?
Und wie hast du dann das Geständnis in Angriff genommen?
E da lì in poi come l'hai attaccato
per arrivare alla dichiarazione?
¿Qué hiciste para que se te declarase?
Como é que fizeste a confissão?
Um... Well, it was like this...
Ähm, also das ...
Ecco, vediamo...
Pues...
Quanto a isso...
So... where should
I do the cooking?
Also, wo soll ich denn kochen?
Allora, dove posso cucinarlo?
¿Y dónde cocinamos?
Onde queres cozinhar?
Well...
Ähm ...
Dunque...
Veamos...
Bem...
You probably don't have any decent
cookware at your place anyway, right?
So wie ich dich kenne, hast du eh kein vernünftiges Geschirr.
Dubito che nel tuo alloggio ci sia
il necessario, eh, Kirito?
En tu casa no tienes
buenos utensilios, ¿verdad?
Não tens utensílios de cozinha pois não?
Just this once,
Dieses eine Mal lade ich dich zu mir ein.
Weil die Zutaten so gut sind.
Se è così, per questa volta potrei aiutarti mettendo
a disposizione la cucina del mio alloggio.
Por esta vez podríamos
utilizar mi cocina.
Vamos esquecer cozinhar e assim nem
é preciso ir a minha casa.
considering the ingredient,
I wouldn’t mind using my place.
Am I?
Ja.
Bene.
Pues eso.
Sim.
In that case, party up with me.
It's been forever.
Dann tu dich doch mal wieder mit mir zusammen.
Allora fai squadra con me, dopo tanto tempo.
Formarás otra vez pareja conmigo.
Então vamo-nos juntar de novo.
Also, black is my lucky color this week.
Schwarz ist diese Woche meine Glücksfarbe.
Il nero è il mio colore fortunato, questa settimana.
Además, esta semana mi color
de la suerte es el negro.
A cor da sorte é o preto e tudo.
What's up with that?
Was redest du da?! Was ist mit deiner Gilde, Asuna?!
Ma che vuol dire? E poi come pensi di fare,
con i tuoi doveri nei confronti della gilda?
¿Estás loca?
¿Y qué pasa con el gremio?
Não digas isso? E a Guild?
That’s easy for you to say, Asuna...
but what about your guild?
We don't have any leveling quotas.
Ach, wir haben keine Levelquoten.
Mica devo salire sempre di livello.
Yo no tengo normas
para subir de nivel.
Não tenho regras para isso.
Th-Then what about
your bodyguard?
Und deine Eskorte?
Sì, però c'è il problema della scorta.
¿Y aquel escolta?
E o guarda?
I'll ditch him.
Den werd ich schon los.
Me ne libererò.
Me desharé de él.
Está lá.
Asuna invites you to join her party.
"ASUNA HAT DICH IN EINE GRUPPE EINGELADEN."
"SEI STATO INVITATO DA ASUNA A UNIRTI A UN PARTY."
"ASUNA TE INVITA
A UNIRTE A SU GRUPO"
"CONVITE PARA A FESTA DA ASUNA."
The front lines are dangerous.
An der Front ist es gefährlich.
Ti ricordo che il fronte è pericoloso.
Es peligroso ir en primera línea.
A linha da frente é perigosa.
F-Fine.
I... Ist ja gut.
O-okay.
V-vale.
Percebido.
That was more aggressive than I thought.
Du bist ja ganz schön stürmisch rangegangen.
Un attacco più deciso di quanto pensassi...
Menuda ofensiva.
Ela ataca mais forte...
Do you think maybe you have to be
that aggressive for it to work out?
Scheinbar muss man wirklich so energisch sein, was?
E infatti essere stata così diretta
non sarà stato un po' troppo?
Para que funcione,
hay que ir al grano, ¿eh?
Será que ser assertiva é a chave?
W-Well, what could I do? After all...I was in love with him.
W... Was hätte ich denn tun sollen?
Ich mein ... Ich war doch verliebt ...
N-non ho potuto farne a meno...
D-dopotutto mi piaceva...
N-no tuve elección.
Es que... me gustaba mucho...
Então tinha que ser.
Gostava dele...
- Um...
- Okay, okay! Thanks, that was delicious.
- Ähm ...
- Ja, ja, schon klar.
Ecco... Sì, grazie per il pranzo.
- Esto...
- Vale, vale. Tranquila.
- Hum....
- Ok, ok. A comida está boa.
So how far did you two go?
Und wie weit seid ihr beide gegangen?
Beh, fin dove vi siete spinti, voi due?
¿Y hasta dónde habéis llegado?
E vocês o que fizeram?
It might have been in-game, but you were married.
Es war zwar nur ein Spiel, aber ihr habt doch sicher geheiratet?
In fondo, dato che mentre eravate nel gioco vi siete
perfino sposati, sarebbe solo naturale, no?
Si en el juego os habéis casado,
algo habréis hecho, ¿no?
Vocês até se casaram,
mesmo sendo um jogo né?
So naturally...right?
I'm sorry.
Verzeih mir ...
Perdonami...
Perdóname.
Desculpa.
This was...
Das war ... Das war meine Schuld ...
Tutto questo... È soltanto colpa mia!
Ha sido... culpa mía.
A culpa é minha.
This was my fault, right?
Asuna...
Asuna ...
Asuna.
I'm sorry.
Verzeih mir!
Mi dispiace.
Perdóname.
Desculpa.
I sh-should
Ich sollte
Kirito, forse...
Yo...
Eu já...
stay away from you
mich von dir
È meglio che stia...
Ya no puedo...
...não sirvo...
fr-from now on.
fernhalten.
Lontana da te.
...estar contigo.
...para ti.
My life belongs to you, Asuna.
Mein Leben gehört ganz allein dir, Asuna.
La mia vita appartiene a te, Asuna.
Mi vida es tuya, Asuna.
A minha vida é tua... Asuna.
So I'll use it for you.
Let's stay together until the end.
Also werde ich es für dich nutzen.
Ed è per te che la userò.
Por eso quiero darla por ti.
Eu luto por ti,
Lass uns bis zum Ende zusammenbleiben.
Restiamo insieme fino alla fine, va bene?
Estemos juntos hasta la muerte.
Ficaremos juntos até a morte.
And I... I'll protect
you too, no matter what.
Ich ... Ich werde dich auch beschützen.
Anche io ti proteggerà ad ogni costo.
Y-yo también te protegeré.
Eu, eu também te protejo.
I'll protect you forever.
Ich werde dich für immer beschützen.
Da adesso in poi e per l'eternità.
Te protegeré eternamente.
Vou proteger-te para sempre.
So...
Also ...
Perciò...
Por eso...
Por isso...
I'll see to it that you can go back
to the other world, no matter what.
Ich werde alles dafür tun, damit du in die reale Welt
Qualunque cosa dovesse succedere,
giuro che ti farò tornare
Te prometo devolverte
a aquel mundo.
Aconteça o que acontecer
tens que voltar...
zurückkehren kannst.
nel nostro mondo!
Cueste lo que me cueste.
...àquele mundo...
Asuna...
Asuna,
Asuna.
Today...
heute Nacht will ich bei dir sein.
questa notte voglio passarla assieme a te.
Quiero pasar esta noche contigo.
Hoje, esta noite quero ficar contigo...
Tonight, I want to stay with you.
Okay.
D-Don't look over here.
S... Schau mich nicht so an ...
Non guardare da questa parte.
N-no me mires.
Não olhes.
H-Hurry and get undressed too.
K... Kirito-kun, los, zieh dich auch aus!
C-cosa aspetti a toglierti i vestiti, Kirito?
V-venga, desnúdate.
Despe-te, rápido!
It's embarrassing,
b-being the only one...
Alleine ist mir das peinlich.
È imbarazzante se lo faccio solo io.
Me da vergüenza si lo hago yo sola.
Tenho vergonha sozinha.
Sorry, I woke you, didn't I?
Entschuldige, habe ich dich geweckt?
Scusa... Ti ho svegliata, vero?
Perdona, te he despertado.
Desculpa, acordei-te.
I was just dreaming a little.
About our old world.
Ich hatte gerade einen Traum.
Stavo facendo un sogno.
Estaba soñando.
Tive um sonho.
Von unserer früheren Welt.
Un sogno sul mondo reale.
Soñaba en el mundo real.
No mundo real.
It's strange...
Es war seltsam.
È strano.
Ha sido muy raro.
É estranho.
In the dream, I was worried that
things in Aincrad and things with you
Ich fragte mich, ob alles hier in Aincrad
Nel sogno pensavo a cosa avrei fatto se Aincrad,
En el sueño creía que Aincrad...
Se Aincrad não existisse...
und unsere Begegnung nur ein Traum waren.
Das hat mir Angst gemacht.
e l'aver incontrato te, Kirito, fossero stati
solo un'illusione. Ero così spaventata!
...y el haberte conocido, era un sueño.
Me dio mucho miedo.
...e ter-te encontrado
não passasse de um sonho...tive medo.
were only a dream.
I was really scared.
I'm glad this wasn't a dream.
Zum Glück war es kein Traum.
Ma per fortuna... è tutto vero.
Menos mal que no ha sido así.
Não é um sonho, ainda bem.
You're so strange...
Don't you want to go back?
Du bist mir eine ... Willst du nicht zurück?
Sei proprio strana, sai?
Non vuoi tornare a casa?
Eres rara.
¿Es que no quieres volver?
Então não queres voltar?
I do.
Natürlich will ich. Ich will, aber ...
Certo che lo voglio.
Claro que sí, pero...
Sim, quero, mas...
I do, but I don't want
my time here to disappear.
Ich will nicht, dass unsere Zeit hier nie passiert ist.
Però senza che i momenti
trascorsi qui scompaiano.
No quiero perder el tiempo
que he pasado aquí.
...não quero perder
o tempo passado aqui.
These two years have been important
to me. I can think of them that way now.
Diese zwei Jahre bedeuten mir sehr viel ...
So denke ich inzwischen.
Ora so che per me questi due anni
sono stati molto importanti.
Ahora me doy cuenta.
Han sido dos años muy valiosos.
Foram 2 anos muito importantes para mim.
Hey, Kirito.
Hey, Kirito-kun,
Senti, Kirito...
Oye, Kirito.
Kirito...
Do you think it would be okay
if we left the front lines for a bit?
glaubst du, es wäre okay,
wenn wir die Front für eine Weile verlassen?
Che ne pensi di allontanarci
per un po' dalla prima linea?
¿Estaría mal
que nos alejásemos del frente?
E se nos afastarmos da linha da frente?
Somehow, I'm scared.
Ich hab Angst.
È che ho paura.
Tengo miedo.
Tenho medo.
If we return to the battlefield, it feels
like something else bad will happen.
Ich hab das Gefühl, dass etwas Schreckliches passiert,
wenn wir jetzt aufs Schlachtfeld zurückkehren.
Ho la sensazione che potrebbe
succederci qualcosa di brutto.
Intuyo que pasará algo malo,
si salimos enseguida a pelear.
Se formos logo para
a luta podem acontecer coisas más.
Maybe I'm just a little tired.
Vielleicht bin ich auch einfach nur ausgelaugt.
Forse sono solo stanca di combattere.
Me siento muy cansada.
Devo estar cansada...
Yeah...
Kann sein.
Hai ragione.
Sí.
Sim.
I'm tired too.
Mir geht’s genauso.
Anche io sono un po' stanco.
Yo también lo estoy.
Eu também estou.
In the southwest part of floor 22,
Im südwestlichen Teil von Ebene 22
Al ventiduesimo piano, a sud-ovest,
En el área suroeste del piso 22...
Na área sudoeste do 22º nível...
there's a small village
surrounded by forests and lakes.
gibt es ein Dorf mit einem Wald und einigen Seen.
c'è un piccolo villaggio circondato
dai boschi, vicino a un lago.
...hay una aldea rodeada
por un bosque y un lago.
...há uma aldeia rodeada por
uma floresta e lago.
Let's move there together.
Lass uns dorthin gehen.
Trasferiamoci lì assieme.
Nos podríamos mudar allí.
Vamos os dois morar lá.
And...
Und ...
E poi...
Y...
E depois.
And?
Und was?
E poi?
¿Y?
Depois o quê?
Let...
Lass ...
Sp...
Ca...
Vamos...
Let's get married.
Lass uns heiraten!
Sposiamoci.
Casémonos.
Vamos casar.
Yes!
Ja!
Sì.
Vale.
Sim.
Hey, earth to Asuna!
Hey, was hast du, Asuna?
Ehi, che ti prende, Asuna?
Eh, ¿qué te pasa, Asuna?
Ui, então Asuna?
Huh? Um, i-it's nothing! We didn't do anything, okay?
Äh ... Ähm ... E... Es ist nichts! Wir haben nichts gemacht!
Eh, no, n-nulla!
Non abbiamo fatto proprio nulla!
¡N-nada, nada!
¡No hicimos nada!
Não, não é nada, nada!
Lucky you for getting married.
Muss schön gewesen sein.
Che bello però, un matrimonio...
Casarse, qué bonito.
Uau, casamento...
And you even have an adorable kid like Yui. I'm so envious!
Und dann hattet ihr auch noch so ein süßes Kind wie Yui.
Ich werd echt eifersüchtig!
E avete avuto anche una bambina carina
come Yui, sono troppo gelosa...
Y encima tenéis a una niña como Yui.
Me dais una envidia.
E ter uma filha tão fofa como
a Yui... que inveja.
Yes, well, she's our daughter ? our pride and joy!
Sie ist eben meine wunderbare Tochter.
Lei era la figlia
di cui eravamo orgogliosi.
Es la alegría de la casa.
É o nosso orgulho!
Well, well, for a teenager you're
quite the doting parent, aren't you!
Selber noch Teenager, aber benimmt sich schon wie eine Glucke.
Ma dai, tempo dieci anni e diventerai
una mammina coi fiocchi!
Mírala, tan joven
y ya hecha una madraza.
Mesmo tão novos são muito bons pais...
I'm going to take that as a compliment.
Das werde ich als Kompliment werten.
È un complimento che accetto molto volentieri.
Me lo tomaré como un cumplido.
Fico agradecida.
All right, then, let's give it our all in
today's quest, so we can make Yui happy!
Dann strengen wir uns heute bei der Quest an,
um Yui-chan eine Freude zu bereiten.
Bene, allora impegniamoci nella missione
di oggi, anche per rendere felice Yui!
¡Demos lo mejor en la aventura de hoy
para que Yui esté orgullosa de nosotras!
Vamos então fazer um esforço
na missão de hoje e alegrar a Yui!
Right...
Ja.
Sì!
Sí.
Sim.
Auna?
A-una? Ki-to?
A... U... Na... Ki... To...
A-u-na.
Ki-to.
A... u... na.
Ki... to.
Kito?
Hey, Yui, what were
you doing in the forest?
Hey, Yui-chan, warum warst du da draußen im Wald?
Ricordi come mai ti trovavi
in quel bosco da sola?
Yui, ¿qué hacías en el bosque?
Yui, porque foste à floresta?
Are your mom and dad somewhere?
Sind deine Mutter und dein Vater hier irgendwo?
La tua mamma e il tuo papà
sono qui con te?
¿Dónde están tus padres?
Que é feito dos teus pais?
I don't know...
Ich weiß nicht ...
Non lo so.
No sé.
Não sei.
I don't know anything.
Ich weiß überhaupt nichts.
Non ricordo niente.
No sé nada.
Não sei de nada.
That's awful.
Oh nein ...
Ma come...
No puede ser...
Mas que...
Hello, Yui.
Hör mal, Yui-chan ...
Allora hai detto
Oye, Yui.
Olha lá, Yui.
Can I call you Yui?
Ich darf dich doch so nennen?
che ti chiami Yui, vero?
¿Te puedo llamar Yui?
Posso chamar-te Yui?
Okay. Then I want
you to call me Kirito.
Sehr schön. Dann nenn du mich doch Kirito.
Bene, Yui, è un vero piacere conoscerti.
Il mio nome è Kirito.
Vale, pues tú llámame Kirito.
Muito bem. Chama-me de Kirito então.
Kito?
Ki-to?
Ki... To...
Ki-to.
Ki... to...
It's Kirito. Ki-ri-to.
Kirito. Ki-ri-to.
È Kirito. Ki, Ri, To.
Me llamo Kirito.
"Ki-ri-to".
É Kirito! Ki...ri...to.
Kito.
Ki, To...
Ki-to.
Ki... to.
Maybe it's a little hard. You can
call me whatever's easiest for you.
Vielleicht ist das ein bisschen viel.
Forse per te è troppo difficile, eh?
Es un poco difícil, ¿eh?
Deve ser difícil.
Nenn mich so, wie es für dich einfacher ist.
Facciamo così, chiamami pure come preferisci.
Pues llámame como quieras.
Como for mais fácil para ti.
Daddy.
Papa.
Papà.
Papá.
Me?
Ich?
I-io?!
¿Y-yo?
Eu?
Auna is Mommy.
Auna ist Mama ...
Auna è "mamma".
Auna es Mamá.
A Auna... mamã.
That's right. I'm your mommy, Yui!
Genau. Ich bin deine Mama, Yui-chan.
Ma certo, puoi chiamarmi "mamma".
Sí, Yui.
Soy Mamá.
Isso mesmo! Sou tua mamã!
Mommy!
Mama!
Mamma.
Mamá.
Mamã.
Daddy! Mommy!
Papa! Mama!
Papà, mamma.
Papá, Mamá.
Papá, mamã.
You must be hungry! Let's eat.
Du hast sicher Hunger! Lass uns essen!
Sarai affamata! Facciamo colazione?
Tienes hambre, ¿verdad?
Vamos a comer.
Deves ter fome.
Vamos comer.
Yeah!
Ja!
Sì!
Vale.
Sim.
Yui?
Yui-chan?
Yui.
Yui...
Yui ...
Yui.
Daddy... Mommy.
Papa, Mama ...
Papà, mamma.
Papá, Mamá.
Papá, mamã.
I remember everything now.
Ich kann mich wieder erinnern.
Adesso io... ricordo tutto quanto.
Ya lo recuerdo todo.
Já me lembro de tudo.
Mental Health Counseling
Program, prototype 1.
Mentales Gesundheits-Beratungsprogramm, Prototyp 1.
Programma di consulenza per la sanità mentale,
prototipo numero uno.
Soy el Prototipo O1 del Programa de
Asesoramiento de Salud Mental
O programa de aconselhamento mental,
teste 1.
Code name: Yui.
Code Name: Yui.
Nome in codice "Yui".
Nombre clave: Yui
Nome-código: Yui.
That's me.
Das bin ich.
Ecco cosa sono.
Esa soy yo.
Sou eu.
You aren't just a program that
the system controls anymore.
Du bist nicht mehr nur ein Programm, das vom System kontrolliert wird.
Yui, ormai non sei più soltanto un
programma generato dal sistema.
Ya no eres solo un programa
controlado por el sistema.
Já não és um programa qualquer
do sistema, Yui.
So you should be able to say
what it is that you want.
Deshalb solltest du deinen Wunsch aussprechen können.
Io credo che tu sia in grado
di capire cosa desideri.
Deberías poder expresar tus deseos.
Consegues dizer o que queres.
What do you want?
Was wünschst du dir?
Qual è il tuo desiderio, Yui?
¿Qué deseas?
O que queres fazer?
I...
Ich möchte ...
Ecco...
Yo...
Eu...
I...
Ich möchte
Io...
Yo...
Eu...
I want to stay with you forever...
für immer bei euch bleiben.
Voglio stare per sempre insieme a voi!
Quiero estar siempre con vosotros.
Quer estar sempre convosco.
Daddy, Mommy!
Papa, Mama!
Il mio papà! La mia mamma!
¡Papá, Mamá!
Papá, mamã!
Together...We'll be together forever, Yui.
Wir werden immer und ewig zusammenbleiben, Yui-chan.
Noi tre staremo insieme per sempre, Yui.
Sí, Yui.
Siempre estaremos juntos.
Vamos estar sempre juntos.
That’s right. You’re our child, Yui.
Genau. Du bist unser Kind.
Giusto. Perché tu sei
la nostra bambina, Yui.
Sí, siempre serás nuestra hija.
Sim, és a nossa filha.
Kirito!
Kirito-kun!
Kirito.
Kirito!
Are you okay?
Geht es dir gut?
Va tutto bene?
¿Estás bien?
Estás bem?
What's this?
Was ist das?
Questo è...
Esto es...
Isto é...
Before Yui's admin
credentials were denied,
Bevor Yuis Admin-Berechtigungen verweigert wurden,
Prima che i privilegi di amministratore
di Yui svanissero,
Antes de que expirase
la autorización del administrador,...
A Yui foi tornada num ser real antes
dos direitos...
I split off her main program and
turned it into a game object.
konnte ich sie vom Hauptprogramm trennen und zu einem Ingame-Objekt machen.
sono riuscito a estrapolare il suo
programma principale per commutarlo in oggetto.
...he podido separar el programa de Yui
y convertirlo en un objeto.
...de administrador terem sido
colpapsados.
So this is...
Dann ist das ...
Allora... Questo è...
Entonces, esto es...
Então isto é...
Yui's heart.
Es ist Yuis Herz.
Il cuore di Yui.
El alma de Yui.
O coração da Yui.
So Yui met you and Kirito inside SAO, then?
Ihr seid Yui-chan zuerst in SAO begegnet, nicht wahr?
Quindi avete incontrato Yui dentro SAO, Asuna...
Vaya, así que Yui os conoció a los dos
dentro del SAO.
A Yui conheceu-vos no SAO não foi?
Yes.
Ja.
Sì.
Sí.
Sim.
Ever since then, she's been our child.
Seitdem ist sie meine und Kirito-kuns Tochter.
Lei sarà per sempre la bambina mia e di Kirito.
Y desde entonces es nuestra hija.
E desde então que é nossa filha.
Okay, why don't we resume practice now?
Wollen wir dann mal mit den Schwimmübungen weitermachen?
Bene, adesso ricominciamo la lezione!
Bueno, ¿volvemos al entrenamiento?
Vá, vamos voltar ao treino!
All righty, Suguha! Let's get you swimming
like a fish, and knock Kirito off his feet!
Los, Suguha, überrasch Kirito damit,
wie schnell du Schwimmen gelernt hast!
Forza, Suguha, se imparerai a nuotare per bene
lascerai Kirito a bocca aperta!
Venga, Suguha.
¡Que Kirito vea hecha una sirena!
Sim, vamos meter-te a nadar para
impressionares o Kirito!
Okay!
Gut!
Sì!
¡Vale!
Sim!
Ah, what a splendid thing it is to be young!
Hach, die Jugend ...
Che bella cosa essere giovani, già.
Ah, juventud, divino tesoro.
Ai que bom ser-se jovem!
Those kids were able to make a safe return to the real world
Auch sie haben es dir zu verdanken,
dass sie wohlbehalten ins Reallife zurückkehren konnten.
Anche il fatto che quelle ragazze siano tornate sane e
salve nel mondo reale è stato solo grazie a te, Kirito.
Esas chicas han vuelto sanas y salvas
al mundo real gracias a ti.
A menina ter conseguido vir para este mundo
for graças a te ter encontrado, não foi?
because of your heroics, wasn't it, Kirito?
There were no heroics from me.
Ich hab überhaupt nichts dazu beigetragen.
Non direi che è stato merito mio.
Yo no he hecho nada.
Não fiz nada.
But isn't it a fact that you unmasked Heathcliff's true identity,
Aber du hast Heathcliff durchschaut
Però sei stato tu a comprendere
il vero volto di Heathcliff,
No puedes negar que descubriste
la identidad de Heathcliff,...
Mas teres penetrado o Heathcliff...
and claimed victory in that final battle against Akihiko Kayaba?
und im letzten Kampf gegen Akihiko Kayaba gewonnen, oder nicht?
e a vincere l’ultimo scontro contro
Akihiko Kayaba, non è così?
...y que venciste a Kayaba
en el último combate.
...e teres lutado com o Kayaba
é verdade?
If you can call that a victory...
Ob man das einen Sieg nennen kann ...
Se quella si può chiamare una vittoria...
No creo que fuese una victoria...
Se lhe chamas vitória...
I'm sorry, Asuna...
Es tut mir leid, Asuna, aber du musst am Leben bleiben.
Perdonami, Asuna, e continua a vivere.
Perdóname, Asuna.
Te dejo sola.
Desculpa por seres a única a viver,
Asuna...
I want you at least to live.
Farewell, Kirito.
Leb wohl, Kirito-kun.
Addio per sempre, Kirito!
Llegó tu hora, Kirito.
Adeuzinho, Kirito.
You’re kidding, right? Asuna...
Bitte nicht! Asuna!
Non è vero... Asuna...
¡Asuna, no!
Não pode... Asuna...
This can't... This can't be...
Das ... Das ...
Questo non... può essere...
No puede ser verdad...
Não, não pode ser...
I'm sorry.
Es tut mir leid.
Mi dispiace...
Lo siento.
Desculpa.
Goodbye.
Leb wohl.
Addio.
Adiós.
Adeus.
It's over now...
Jetzt ist es aus ...
E così... è la fine!
Se acabó...
Acaba aqui...
I believe in you, Kirito.
Ich glaube an dich, Kirito-kun.
Ho fiducia in te... Kirito!
Creo en ti, Kirito.
Acredito em ti, Kirito.
Not yet...
Noch nicht ...
Non ancora...
Aún no.
Ainda não.
Not yet!
Noch nicht!
Non ancora!
Aún no.
Ainda não.
Is this good enough?
Hab ich’s geschafft?
Ci sarò... riuscito?
¿Suficiente así?
Agora sim.
As of 2:55 PM, November 7,
Es ist 14:55 Uhr am 7. November.
7 Novembre, ore 14 e 55.
A las 14:55 h del 7 de noviembre,...
7 de Novembro, 14:55
the game has been cleared.
Das Spiel wurde beendet.
Il gioco è stato completato.
...se ha completado el juego.
Jogo acabado.
The game has been cleared.
Das Spiel wurde beendet.
Il gioco è stato completato.
Se ha completado el juego.
Jogo acabado.
Kayaba lost that battle against you,
Kayaba wurde im Kampf mit dir besiegt und sein
Gehirn mit einem experimentellen NerveGear gegrillt.
Quando il professor Kayaba è stato sconfitto da te in
duello, il suo cervello è stato distrutto dal Nerve Gear.
Al derrotar a Kayaba, murió por la
descarga de su Nerve Gear, ¿no?
Então o Kayaba perdeu contigo e destruiu
o próprio cérebro com o Nerve Gear.
and burned his own brain with
the mock-up version of the NerveGear.
That's been borne out by the autopsy on his body.
Das stimmt so mit dem
Obduktionsergebnis überein.
La cosa è stata confermata dall’esame
autoptico svolto su di lui.
Eso concuerda con su autopsia.
Concide com o que já tinha ouvido.
But the fact that you survived even though
you were killed at the same time is,
Doch obwohl du zeitgleich mit ihm gestorben bist,
konntest du zurückkehren.
Tuttavia, il fatto che tu sia riuscito a tornare
nonostante vi foste in teoria uccisi a vicenda,
Pero que hayas vuelto al mundo real
cuando deberías estar muerto,...
Mas ainda assim é estranho terem
morrido os dois mas tu...
is, I have to say, mind-blowing.
Was that due to a system-related reason,
Das ist schon eigenartig.
è qualcosa che in effetti
ha dell’incredibile.
...me resulta sorprendente.
...conseguires regressar vivo.
War das systembedingt
Che sia accaduto per una
ragione legata al sistema,
¿Fue cosa del sistema?
Ou foi do sistema...
or was it the will of Kayaba?
oder Kayabas Wille?
oppure si è trattato della volontà
dello stesso professor Kayaba?
¿O de la voluntad de Kayaba?
...ou por vontade do Kayaba.
Quite a view, isn't it?
Was für eine Aussicht.
Che spettacolo, vero?
Bonito paisaje.
Uma bela paisagem.
Akihiko Kayaba...
Akihiko Kayaba ...
Akihiko Kayaba.
The SAO mainframe, located in
the fifth-level basement at Argus HQ,
Gerade werden sämtliche gesicherte Daten vom
SAO-Hauptserver
In questo momento sto formattando
tutti i dispositivi di memoria
Ahora en el sótano de Argus,...
Neste momento estão os dados...
im 5. Untergeschoss des
Hauptsitzes von Argus unwiderruflich gelöscht.
contenuti nel mainframe di SAO, che si trova
nei sotterranei della sede centrale della Argus.
...se están borrando todos los datos
almacenados de SAO.
...da estrutura principal do SAO a ser
eliminados no 5º andar do subsolo da nossa sede.
is deleting all data on
its storage devices.
In 10 minutes or so, everything
in this world will vanish.
In etwa zehn Minuten wird alles in dieser Welt verschwunden sein.
Altri dieci minuti, e ogni cosa in
questo mondo verrà distrutta.
En 10 minutos,
no quedará nada de este mundo.
Daqui a uns 10 minutos
este mundo será destruído.
What's happened to
the people down there?
Was ist mit den ganzen Spielern?
Cos’è successo alle persone che erano laggiù?
¿Y que pasará con la gente?
E as pessoas que lá estavam?
You needn't worry about them.
Mach dir keine Sorgen.
Non preoccuparti per loro.
No os preocupéis.
Nada de preocupações.
Just a moment ago, the remaining
6,147 players were logged out.
Vor kurzem wurden alle überlebenden
Il processo di logout dei
6147 giocatori sopravvissuti
Hace un momento,
ha finalizado el log out...
Todos os 6147 jogadores que...
6147 Spieler vom System ausgeloggt.
è terminato pochi istanti fa.
...de los 6147 jugadores supervivientes.
...restavam conseguiram fazer logout.
And the ones who died?
Und was ist mit den 4000 Spielern,
die in dieser Welt gestorben sind?
E quelli che sono morti?
I 4000 giocatori che hanno perso la vita?
¿Y los que han muerto?
¿Qué pasa con esos 4000?
E os que morreram?
E os 4000 que morreram, que é feito deles?
What about the 4,000 people who died?
Their minds will never return.
Ihr Bewusstsein wird nie wieder zurückkehren.
Non riprenderanno conoscenza.
No recuperarán su consciencia.
Tanto neste mundo como...
The dead vanish from our midst...
It’s the same in any world.
Der Tod ist in jeder Welt endgültig.
I morti scompaiono, in questo mondo
come in quello reale.
Los muertos desaparecen,
aquí y en cualquier lugar.
...morrram. Não vão voltar
a ter consciência.
Why...
Warum? Warum haben Sie das getan?
Perché? Perché hai fatto questo?
¿Por qué has hecho todo esto?
Porque fizeste isto?
Why did you do this?
Why, you ask?
Warum?
Perché, dici?
¿Por qué?
Porquê?
It's been so long I've forgotten myself.
Das habe ich schon vor langer Zeit vergessen.
Persino io ho dimenticato la ragione,
Hace mucho tiempo que lo he olvidado.
Esqueci-me durante um tempo...
I wonder why...
Weshalb wohl?
da molto tempo.
¿Por qué lo habré hecho?
Porque será?
When I began developing the full-dive
environment system... No, long before that,
Als ich mit der Entwicklung des Fulldive-Systems anfing ...
Nein, schon lange vorher,
Fin da quando ho iniziato a sviluppare l’ambiente
full dive... anzi, da molto prima di allora,
Cuando desarrollé el sistema Full Dive.
No, mucho antes.
Desde que comecei, não, desde antes de
construir este submundo virtual que...
creating that castle, a world that surpassed
all our laws and all our restrictions,
träumte ich von nichts anderem,
als der Erschaffung einer Welt wie dieser hier,
ciò che desideravo era solo riuscire a creare
quel castello, un universo a sé,
Solo vivía para crear aquel castillo...
...sempre quis construir
um mundo assim,...
was my only desire
and what I lived for.
die sämtliche Regeln und Gesetze der realen Welt übersteigt.
che trascendesse tutti i limiti
e le leggi del mondo reale.
Un mundo capaz
de superar las leyes del mundo real.
...como o mundo real.
And now I've been able to see something
that surpassed my own world's laws...
Doch nun sah ich,
wie jemand die Gesetze meiner eigenen Welt übersteigen konnte.
E alla fine ho potuto vedere qualcosa che travalica
i limiti e le leggi del mio stesso mondo!
He conseguido ver cosas que
han superado las leyes de mi mundo.
E assim foi-me possível ver para além das
fundações do meu mundo.
How old was I, when I was obsessed with the
fantasy of a steel castle that floated in the sky?
Wie alt war ich wohl, als die Idee eines stählernen Schlosses,
das über den Wolken schwebt,
Non so quanti anni avessi quando ho iniziato a
rincorrere l’immagine di un castello d’acciaio
¿Cuántos años tendría cuando empecé
a obsesionarme con la visión...
Quando é que eu comecei
a ficar obcecado...
von mir Besitz ergriff?
che fluttuava nel cielo.
...de un castillo de acero
levitando en el cielo?
...com isto, mesmo...?
I wanted to leave the ground
Ich wollte vom Boden abheben und zu diesem Schloss fliegen.
Volevo innalzarmi in volo sulla Terra
e raggiungere quel luogo!
Quería llegar a él de un salto.
Quero um dia ir até aquele castelo...
to fly to that castle.
For a long, long time,
that was my only desire...
Für sehr lange Zeit war das mein einziger, innigster Wunsch.
Per tanto, tanto tempo, quello è stato
il mio unico desiderio.
Ese fue mi único deseo
durante mucho tiempo.
Foi o meu desejo durante muito tempo.
You know, Kirito,
Weißt du, Kirito-kun, ich glaube noch immer,
E ancora adesso, Kirito,
io sono fermamente convinto...
¿Sabes, Kirito?
Aún tengo fe.
Kirito. Eu ainda acredito
que aquele castelo...
I believe even now
that in some other world,
that castle truly exists.
dass mein schwebendes Schloss in einer anderen Welt existiert.
Che là fuori da qualche parte, forse in qualche
altro mondo, quel castello esista davvero.
Creo que en algún otro mundo
existe de verdad ese castillo.
...existe algures noutro mundo.
Yes... I hope you're right.
Ja, das hoffe ich.
Già, spero sia così.
Ojalá sea así.
Mas que bom.
I forgot to tell you something.
Fast hätte ich es vergessen:
Dimenticavo...
Se me olvidaba.
Esqueci-me.
Congratulations on clearing
the game, Kirito, Asuna.
Ich gratuliere euch zum Sieg, Kirito-kun, Asuna-kun.
Asuna, Kirito... Congratulazioni
per aver completato il gioco.
Kirito, Asuna.
Enhorabuena por completar el juego.
Parabéns por terem passado o jogo,
Kirito e Asuna.
Now then, I must be going.
Nun... Ich sollte allmählich gehen.
Bene, per me è giunta l’ora di andare.
Bueno, llegó la hora de irme.
Bem, eu vou indo.
By the way,
Übrigens,
Tuttavia,
Por cierto...
Uma coisa...
before Dr. Kayaba left, did he mention anything to you
hat dir Kayaba noch irgendetwas dazu gesagt,
warum er dieses Death Game angefangen hat?
prima della sua dipartita, il professor Kayaba ha rivelato
il motivo per il quale diede inizio a quel gioco mortale?
¿No dijo antes de partir por qué
empezó ese juego mortal?
Antes do Kayaba partir, ele disse alguma
coisa sobre a razão para ter criado este jogo?
about why he started this death game?
Uh... Not that I recall.
Tja, daran erinnere ich mich nicht.
Mah... Non ricordo davvero.
No lo recuerdo.
Não me recordo.
We finished eating already
Asuna. Wir sind schon fertig mit dem Essen.
“NOI ABBIAMO FINITO DI MANGIARE. ASUNA”
"YA HEMOS COMIDO, ASUNA"
"JÁ COMEMOS. ASUNA."
Who's that from?
Wer schreibt dir?
Da parte di chi?
¿De quién es?
De quem é?
Oh, it's your princess, eh?
That was quite an ordeal for you both.
Ach, deine Prinzessin?
Ah, dalla tua principessina.
De tu princesa, ¿verdad?
Ah, da tua princesa...
Das muss schlimm für euch gewesen sein.
Anche per voi dev’essere stata dura.
Ha sido duro para vosotros, ¿eh?
Deve ter sido difícil...
Just when you thought you'd escaped SAO...
Gerade, als du dachtest,
ihr wärt SAO entkommen ...
Pensavate di essere riusciti a
fuggire da SAO, quella volta...
Os escapáis de SAO, para luego...
Ter saido do SAO e agora...
Yes, it really was an ordeal.
Ja, das war furchtbar.
Già, è stata davvero dura.
Sí, muy duro.
Sim, foi muito complicado.
Weil ein gewisser jemand nicht bemerkt hat,
dass sich ein Schwerverbrecher in ALO herumtrieb.
E la colpa è di chi non si accorse che dentro
ALO si stava compiendo un crimine efferato.
Porque alguien no se dio cuenta del
gran crimen que pasaba en ALO.
Por culpa de um certo alguém que não se
apercebeu do que se passava em ALO.
No thanks to somebody who didn't realize that
a monumental crime was being committed right inside ALO.
Well, I have no excuse to offer as far as that's concerned.
Ja, das kann ich nicht leugnen.
Beh, anche a riguardo di ciò
non ho spiegazioni da offrirti.
Bueno, puedo explicarlo.
Não há como explicar isso.
By the time we discovered that
300 of those comatose SAO players
Dass die 300 nicht erwachten Spieler aus SAO von
Nobuyuki Sugou als Versuchsobjekte missbraucht wurden,
Abbiamo saputo dell’esperimento di Nobuyuki Sugo
sui trecento giocatori di SAO non risvegliatisi,
Supe que Sugou estaba experimentando
con 300 jugadores del SAO...
Foi graças só depois de tu solucionares este
caso, que os 300 jogadores do SAO...
were being used as Nobuyuki Sugou's personal guinea pigs,
the incident had been resolved by a student ? namely, you.
habe ich erst erfahren, nachdem du 10.
Klässler den Fall gelöst hattest.
soltanto dopo che uno studente del primo anno
di liceo, cioè tu, aveva risolto la cosa.
...después de que tú resolvieses el caso.
...souberam da experiência
do Nobuyuki Sugou.
Why couldn't you prevent him from carrying out his scheme?
Wieso konnten Sie seine Intrige nicht verhindern?
Perché non siete riusciti a prevenire
l’attuazione del suo piano?
¿Por qué no tomó precauciones
para detener su plan?
Porque não tomaram medidas preventivas?
Sugou was a member of
the same research lab as Akihiko Kayaba,
Da Sugou im selben Institut wie Akihiko Kayaba gearbeitet hat,
haben wir ihn natürlich überprüft.
Sugo faceva parte dello stesso laboratorio di ricerca
di Akihiko Kayaba, quindi lo abbiamo tenuto d'occhio...
Vigilábamos a Sugou porque estaba
en el mismo laboratorio que Kayaba.
Nós fizemos uma verificação porque o
Sugou estava na mesma sala do Kayaba.
so it's not like we weren't keeping tabs on him.
But then because we suddenly had 6,000 players
returning to the real world,
Aber da auf einen Schlag 6000 Spieler ins Reallife
zurückgekehrt waren, hatten wir mit ihren
Tuttavia, con l'improvviso ritorno al
mondo reale di ben 6000 giocatori,
Pero, al volver de repente
los 6000 jugadores al mundo real,...
Mas não posso negar que quando os
6000 jogadores voltaram...
we were swamped checking on their health,
easing them back into society.
Gesundheitschecks und ihrer
Resozialisierung alle Hände voll zu tun.
ci siamo dati da fare fino allo stremo per
monitorare la loro riabilitazione nella società,
...nos centramos en sus cuidarlos y
reinsertarlos a la sociedad.
...que ficamos demasiado ocupados com
testes de saúde e etc...
So I can't deny that for a time, we were
short-handed in our surveillance of Sugou.
Zweifelsohne haben wir deswegen
Sugous Beobachtung vernachlässigt.
e non posso negare che abbiamo temporaneamente
allentato la sorveglianza su Sugo.
No puedo negar que temporalmente
la vigilancia de Sugou haya flaqueado.
...que negligenciámos
a vigilância do Sugou.
Not to mention,
Außerdem hätten wir nie damit gerechnet,
dass er ein Labor einrichtet,
Mai avrei pensato che Sugo potesse stabilire un laboratorio
per praticare esperimenti illegali all'interno di un gioco.
Jamás hubiese pensado que utilizaría
el mundo virtual para experimentos ilegales.
E nunca pensei que ele pudesse fazer
experiências ilegais num laboratório noutro mundo.
it never occurred to us that Sugou would install a lab
for illegal experiments inside the world of the game.
um illegale Experimente in der Spielewelt durchzuführen.
In the real world, he never once tipped his hand to us.
Hier in der realen Welt konnten wir ihm absolut nichts nachweisen.
Nel mondo reale, di sicuro gli saremmo stati alle costole.
En el mundo real no dejó ningún indicio.
Não conseguimos nada dele no mundo real.
Tell me all about it, will you, Kirito?
Kirito-kun, verrätst du mir bitte,
Perché non me lo spieghi tu, Kirito?
Dime, Kirito.
Ajuda-me por favor, Kirito.
How did you get wise to Sugou's plot?
wie du von seiner Intrige auf die Schliche gekommen bist?
Di come ti sei reso conto del piano di Sugo.
¿Cómo descubriste su plan?
Como te apercebeste dos planos dele?
The thing is, I didn't have a clue ? not at first.
Das bin ich am Anfang gar nicht.
All’inizio non me ne ero accorto
nemmeno io, in realtà...
Al principio no me di cuenta.
Ao início não me tinha apercebido.
This is our laboratory chief, Sugou.
Das ist der Kopf unserer Forschungsabteilung, Sugou-kun.
Lui è Sugo, è a capo del mio istituto di ricerca.
Éste es Sugou,
el investigador jefe del laboratorio.
Este é o Sugou, supervisorl em nosso
laboratório.
I'm Nobuyuki Sugou.
Nice to meet you.
Mein Name ist Nobuyuki Sugou. Freut mich.
Mi chiamo Nobuyuki Sugo, molto lieto.
Me llamo Nobuyuki Sugou.
Encantado.
Sou o Nobuyuki Sugou. Prazer.
I’m Kazuto Kirigaya.
Ich bin Kazuto Kirigaya.
Io sono Kazuto Kirigaya.
Yo soy Kazuto Kirigaya.
Sou o Kazuto Kirigaya.
Kirigaya, I'll see you again.
Kirigaya-kun, wir sehen uns.
Arrivederci, Kirigaya.
Hasta la vista, Kirigaya.
Até um dia.
Is it true that within that game,
you were living with Asuna?
Ich habe gehört, dass du innerhalb des Spiels mit
Asuna zusammengelebt hast, ja?
Ho sentito che dentro al gioco vivevi insieme ad Asuna.
¿Es verdad que vivías con Asuna
dentro del juego?
Tu vivias com a Asuna no jogo?
Yes...
Richtig ...
Sì.
Sí.
Sim.
Then I suppose that complicates
our relationship somewhat, doesn’t it?
Das verkompliziert unser Verhältnis zueinander ein wenig.
In tal caso purtroppo ho il fondato timore che i
rapporti fra noi due si faranno un po’ complicati.
Eso hará que nuestra relación
sea un tanto complicada.
Então nós os dois vamos ter
uma relação complexa.
What we were just discussing,
you see... was Asuna's marriage to me.
Unsere Unterhaltung eben
Vedi, il discorso di prima...
¿Sabes de qué hemos hablado?
A conversa de antes, sabes...
drehte sich um meine bevorstehende Hochzeit mit Asuna.
Riguardava il fatto che io
e Asuna presto si sposeremo.
Asuna y yo nos vamos a casar.
...era sobre eu casar com a Asuna.
Stop it.
Finger weg!
Ora basta!
Basta.
Pára.
Are you trying to take advantage
of the fact that she's in a coma?
Wollen Sie wirklich ausnutzen, dass Asuna im Koma liegt?
Tu... Vuoi davvero approfittare
dello stato comatoso di Asuna?!
¿Te vas aprovechar de que Asuna
está inconsciente?
Queres aproveitar-te do facto de ela estar
em coma?
Take advantage?
No, it’s a legitimate right.
Ausnutzen? Nein, es ist mein gutes Recht.
Approfittarmi?! Ma che dici?
Questo è un mio legittimo diritto!
¿Aprovecharme yo?
Estoy en mi derecho.
Aproveitar-me? Achas?
É o meu direito justo.
Listen, Kirigaya.
Hör zu, Kirigaya-kun.
Dì un po’, Kirigaya...
Oye, Kirigaya.
Ó Kirigaya,...
Do you know what happened
to Argus, the developer of SAO?
Weißt du, was nach der Veröffentlichung von
SAO mit ARGUS passiert ist?
Tu sai cos’è successo alla Argus,
dopo aver sviluppato SAO?
¿Sabes qué pasó con Argus,
la desarrolladora de SAO?
...sabes o que aconteceu a Argus
que desenvolveu o SAO?
I heard it was dissolved.
Ich habe gehört, sie sind bankrott.
Ho sentito che è stata smantellata.
Dicen que cayó en la bancarrota.
Ouvi que se separaram.
Yes.
Genau.
Già.
Exacto.
Sim.
The development costs and massive
damages they were forced to pay
Die Entschädigungen, die sie zusätzlich zu den
Entwicklungskosten zahlen mussten,
I costi di sviluppo e i debiti contratti
per risarcire le vittime dell’incidente
Como los gastos por las indemnizaciones más
los de desarrollo fueron enormes...
Além dos custos do desenvolvimento,
tiveram compensações e dívidas.
bankrupted them.
richteten sie zugrunde.
hanno mandato la società in rovina.
...la empresa quebró.
E a empresa acabou.
And the maintenance of
the SAO servers was entrusted
Die Wartung der SAO-Server wurde dem
Elektronikhersteller anvertraut,
Il mantenimento dei server
di SAO è stato affidato
El mantenimiento de los servidores
de SAO pasó a manos de...
Quem preservou o servidor do SAO foi...
to electronics maker RCT,
whose CEO is Shozo Yuki.
bei dem Shouzou Yuuki als Vorstandsvorsitzender tätig ist:
alla ditta di apparecchiature elettroniche
di cui Shozo Yuuki è l’amministratore delegato,
Shozo Yuuki, presidente de la empresa
fabricante de productos electrónicos...
...o presidente das empresas de eletrónica,
Shozo Yuuki.
RTC!
la RCT.
...RECTO.
RCT.
And I work for its full-dive
technology research division.
Und ich arbeite für die Forschungsabteilung seiner
Fulldive-Technologie.
Io lavoro al dipartimento di ricerca
sulle tecnologie full dive.
Yo trabajo en la división
de investigación del Full Dive.
Trabalho no departamento de tecnologia
"Full Dive".
In other words, you could say
I'm the one who's keeping Asuna alive.
Man könnte
In altre parole,
Resumiendo.
Por isso...
sogar so weit gehen zu sagen, dass ich derjenige bin,
der Asuna am Leben erhält.
ora come ora sono la persona che
continua a mantenere in vita Asuna.
Soy yo quien mantiene en vida a Asuna.
...pode-se dizer que eu controlo
a vida da Asuna.
So I can ask for a little something
by way of compensation, can't I?
Findest du nicht auch,
dass mir Asuna dafür ein paar kleine Gefälligkeiten schuldet?
Pertanto non vedo proprio che male ci sia nel
voler ottenere qualcosa in cambio, ti pare?
¿Está mal que pida
una pequeña compensación por ello?
Então não é bom ter-te pedido
uma coisa tão pequena?
I don't know what sort of promises
you made to her in the game.
Ich habe keine Ahnung,
welche Versprechungen du ihr im Spiel gemacht hast,
Non ho idea di che promesse tu le
abbia fatto all’interno del gioco,
No sé qué os habéis prometido
dentro del juego, pero...
Mas não sei o que é que prometeste durante
o jogo...
But I don’t want you
to ever come back here.
aber ich will dich hier nicht wiedersehen.
ma d’ora in poi voglio
che tu smetta di venire qui,
No quiero que vuelvas más aquí.
Não quero que voltes aqui.
I’d also have you refrain from
any contact with the Yuki family.
Und versuch bloß nicht, die Familie Yuuki zu kontaktieren.
e che eviti ogni rapporto con la famiglia Yuuki.
Tampoco quiero
que te relaciones con su familia.
E afasta-te dos Yuuki.
The ceremony will be held in this
hospital room in a week, on January 26th.
Die Zeremonie wird heute in einer Woche,
am 26. Januar, in diesem Zimmer stattfinden.
La cerimonia si terrà tra una settimana,
qui in questa stanza, il ventisei gennaio.
La boda se celebrará el 26 de enero.
Aquí, dentro de una semana.
A cerimónica será neste quarto daqui a
uma semana, a 26 de Janeiro.
Too bad it's not an auspicious day,
Schon schade, dass es ein Unglückstag sein wird.
Si dice che sia un giorno infausto
per gli amici della sposa,
Aunque los astros dicen
que no es un día muy propicio.
É uma pena não ser um dia de sorte.
but I want you to have a little piece
of my happiness, so I'll invite you.
Aber gerade deswegen bist du auch eingeladen.
per cui magari inviterò anche te!
Por supuesto, estás invitado.
Estamos ligados, podes vir.
Lament your final goodbye, Mr. Hero.
Jetzt heißt es endgültig Abschied von ihr nehmen,
du furchtloser Held.
Adesso puoi anche dirle addio per sempre,
caro il mio giovane eroe.
Disfruta de tu última despedida,
valiente "paladín".
Para fazeres a última despedida,
heroizinho.
At the time, didn't you find him at all suspicious?
Da hast du ihn noch nicht verdächtig gefunden?
E in quel momento non ti
parve un individuo sospetto?
¿No sospechaste de él entonces?
Não o achaste suspeito?
All I could think about was Asuna.
Ich habe an nichts, außer Asuna denken können.
È che riuscivo a pensare soltanto ad Asuna.
Lo único que me preocupaba era Asuna.
Só conseguia pensar na Asuna.
Mein einziger Anhaltspunkt war ein Bild von einem Charakter,
der Asuna sehr ähnlich sah.
L’unico indizio che avevo, era l’immagine
di un avatar molto somigliante a lei.
La única pista que tenía era una imagen
de un avatar que se parecía a ella.
Eu só possuia a imagem de
um avatar parecido à Asuna.
The only clue I had was a screenshot
of an avatar that looked just like her.
Are you saying that you ventured
into ALO based on that intel alone?
Nur deswegen bist du in ALO eingetaucht?
E solo con quell’informazione
decidesti di accedere ad ALO?
¿Te aventuraste en ALO
sabiendo solo eso?
E foi assim que entraste na ALO?
If there was the least shred of hope,
I would've done anything.
Ich hätte alles getan,
wenn es auch nur den Hauch einer Chance gäbe.
Per quanto le probabilità fossero basse,
dovevo fare qualcosa.
No quería desaprovechar
ninguna oportunidad de salvarla.
Fazia os possíveis sempre
que tinha oportunidade.
Please help me one more time.
Bitte gib mir noch einmal die Kraft!
Ti prego, dammi un’altra volta la tua forza.
No me falles.
Ajuda-me mais uma vez.
Link start!
Link Start!
Iniciar conexión.
Começar a ligação!
ALfheim, Neutral Territory, Ancient Forest
January 20, 2025
"ALFHEIM, ANTIKER WALD,
NEUTRALES TERRITORIUM, 20. JANUAR 2025"
"ALFHEIM, CASTELLO NEUTRALE,
VECCHIA FORESTA, 20 GENNAIO 2025"
"ALFHEIM, CASTILLO NEUTRAL - BOSQUE VIEJO
20 DE ENERO DE 2025"
"ALFHEIM, CASTELO, BOSQUE
20 DE JANEIRO DE 2025"
I'm back...
Ich bin wieder zurück ...
E così alla fine sono tornato.
Aquí estoy otra vez.
Cá estou eu de novo.
After everything that happened.
Nach allem, was ich durchgemacht habe ...
Se ripenso al casino dell’ultima volta...
Después de todo lo que he pasado.
Depois de tanto ter sofrido...
It's me, Yui!
Do you remember me?
Ich bin’s, Yui! Erinnerst du dich?
Sono io, Yui, mi riconosci?
Yui, soy yo.
¿Me recuerdas?
Sou eu, Yui, lembras-te?
I got to see you again, Daddy...
Papa, endlich sehen wir uns wieder! Papa!
Ci incontriamo di nuovo, papà!
Papá, otra vez juntos.
Encontramo-nos outra vez, papá.
Yui...
Yui ...
Yui!
Yui.
Daddy!
Papa! Papa!
Papà, papà!
¡Papá, Papá!
Papá, papá!
Daddy!
Daddy...
Papa ...
Il mio papà!
Papá.
Miracles really do happen.
Es gibt wirklich noch Wunder ...
E così i miracoli accadono veramente.
Los milagros existen.
Os milagres existem.
Actually, it seems that Asuna...
Your mommy is here.
Weißt du, ich vermute, dass Asuna, deine Mama, hier ist.
Forse qui c’è anche Asuna.
Ti ricordi di lei? È la tua mamma.
Dicen que Asuna,
que Mamá está por aquí.
Sabes,
pelos vistos a tua mãe está por aqui.
Mommy? What do you mean?
Mama sagst du? Wie meinst du das?
La mamma? Che cosa intendi dire?
¿Mamá?
¿Qué ha pasado?
A mamã? Que aconteceu?
Even after SAO was cleared,
Asuna never woke up in reality.
Obwohl wir SAO gewonnen haben,
ist Asuna in der realen Welt bisher nicht aufgewacht.
Nonostante SAO sia stato completato,
Asuna è ancora priva di conoscenza.
Después que Asuna completase el SAO
no ha vuelto al mundo real.
Ela ainda não voltou à realidade
mesmo tendo passado o jogo.
I heard that someone who looked
like Asuna was seen in ALfheim.
Ich habe erfahren, dass hier in ALfheim jemand gesehen wurde,
der aussieht wie sie.
Poi sono stato informato che in Alfheim Online
c’è qualcuno che le somiglia molto.
Me han dicho que han visto en Alfheim
a alguien parecido a ella.
Disseram-me que uma pessoa muito parecida
com ela foi vista aqui...
So that's what happened...
Ich verstehe ...
Non ne avevo idea...
Vaya...
A sério...
What are you doing? Run!
Was machst du da?! Verschwinde von hier!
Che fai lì impalato? Svelto, scappa!
¿Qué haces?
¡Escapa, rápido!
Então? Foge!
Three heavy fighters
attacking a single girl?
Drei bis an die Zähne bewaffnete
Männer gegen ein einziges Mädchen? Das ist echt erbärmlich.
Ma guarda, tre guerrieri grandi e grossi contro una
ragazza sola. Non ci fate una gran figura, sapete.
¿Tres guerreros contra una chica?
Me parece un abuso.
3 tipos como vocês a atacar uma rapariga...
não deve ser elegante...
That's kind of lame.
- What did you say?
- You've got some nerve, newbie.
Wie war das?!
Che cos’hai detto?!
¿Qué has dicho, piojo?
Que queres?
Halt dich hier raus, du Noob!
Un pivellino che s’immischia nei fatti altrui!
¡Maldito novato!
Não queremos novatos!
If I remember correctly, that player named
Leafa was your younger sister, right?
Diese Spielerin namens
Lyfa war doch deine kleine Schwester, oder?
In effetti, quella giocatrice di nome Leafa
era tua sorella minore, giusto?
Es verdad, la jugadora Leafa era
tu hermana, ¿no?
A Leafa, era a tua irmã não era?
Yes. Even I never dreamed that I'd run into Sugu
? no, I mean my sister ? in ALO.
Stimmt. Ich hätte nie erwartet, dass ich in ALO
Sugu, ich meine, meine kleine Schwester, treffen würde.
Già. Non avrei mai pensato che in ALO avrei
incontrato Sugu... cioè, mia sorella minore.
Sí, nunca pensé encontrarme a Sugu...
digo, a mi hermana en el ALO.
Sim. Nunca pensei que fosse encontrar a
minha irmã em ALO...
Wow! You've gotten to the point
where you can swim 25 meters!
Klasse! Du kannst jetzt schon 25 Meter schwimmen!
Incredibile! Sei riuscita a nuotare
per venticinque metri!
¡Genial!
Ya nadas 25 metros.
Muito bem! Já consegues nadar
os 25 metros!
Hey, you've got the
breathing technique down, too.
Und das Atmen kriegst du auch hin.
E riesci anche a controllare la
respirazione come si deve!
Y también has aprendido a respirar.
E a respiração está boa!
You're a good athlete, Suguha, so no wonder!
Du bist eben einfach eine gute Sportlerin, Suguha-chan!
Certo che sei davvero portata per
le attività fisiche, Suguha!
El deporte se te da bien, ¿eh?
Suguha, tens uns bons reflexos!
Thank you very much!
Vielen Dank!
Grazie mille!
Gracias.
Muito obrigada.
Huh? What's this?
Are you feeling lonely without your big brother?
Was denn, bist du etwa einsam,
wenn dein Brüderchen nicht da ist?
Ecco... Non è che ti senti sola perché
non c'è il tuo fratellone?
Te veo triste.
¿Es por que no está tu hermano?
Ui, tens saudades do maninho?
I-It's not like that at all!
I was just wondering why he's so late...
S... So ein Unsinn!
Ich hab mich nur gefragt, wo er bleibt ...
A-assolutamente no!
Stavo solo pensando che è in ritardo...
¡D-de eso nada!
Solo pensaba que se está retrasando.
Claro que não!
Só acho que já começa a ficar tarde...
You and Kirito really are close.
Ihr steht euch wirklich nahe, was?
Certo che tu e Kirito avete davvero
un bel rapporto, Suguha!
Os lleváis muy bien los dos, ¿verdad?
Vocês dão-se muito bem!
I'm an only child, so that makes me envious.
Als Einzelkind beneide ich euch darum.
Visto che sono figlia unica, sono davvero gelosa!
Me dais una envidia.
Yo soy hija única.
Sou filha única, invejo-vos.
Y-You think so?
M... Meinst du?
D-davvero?
¿E-en serio?
Será...
But...
Aber
Però,
Pero...
Mas,...
Before my brother got trapped inside SAO,
we weren't really that close.
bevor mein Bruder in SAO gefangen war,
haben wir uns nicht so nahegestanden.
prima che il fratellone rimanesse bloccato dentro
SAO, non eravamo in chissà quali rapporti...
No nos llevábamos tan bien antes
de que se encerrase en el SAO.
Antes de ele entrar no SAO
não nos dávamos muito bem.
I wanted to see what those VRMMO
she was so obsessed with were all about,
Ich wollte wissen, warum er von diesen VRMMO so begeistert ist,
Per poter imparare qualcosa sui giochi di ruolo
virtuali in cui il fratellone si immergeva,
Quería saber qué era el VRMMO
que tanto le absorbía.
Ele só pensava naquilo, e uma vez
eu queria saber sobre o VRMMO e...
and that's when I started playing ALO...
darum habe ich mit ALO angefangen.
anche io iniziai a giocare ad ALO...
Por eso empecé a jugar yo también...
...além disso era nova no ALO.
And now I'm no slouch as a gamer myself!
Inzwischen bin ich auch durch und durch eine Gamerin.
Però adesso anche io sono una brava giocatrice!
Ahora soy una gamer excelente.
Agora sou boa jogadora!
It was you who guided Kirito to the World Tree,
wasn't it, Suguha?
Du hast Kirito-kun ja zum Weltenbaum begleitet, nicht wahr?
Ad avere guidato Kirito fino
all'Yggdrasill sei stata tu, Suguha.
Tú le guiaste hasta
el Árbol del Mundo, ¿verdad?
Foste tu que mostraste
ao Kirito a árvore mágica, certo?
Yes. But when I first met him,
I had no idea he was my brother.
Ja. Aber als wir uns dort zum ersten Mal begegnet sind,
wusste ich nicht, dass er mein Bruder ist.
Sì. Però quando ci siamo incontrati per la
prima volta, non sapevo che fosse il fratellone.
Sí, pero la primera vez que le vi,
no supe que era él.
Sim. Mas quando nos vimos pela primeira
vez não sabia que era meu irmão.
I just thought he was this rude guy.
Ich dachte: „Der ist vielleicht frech!"
In realtà pensavo fosse una
persona alquanto maleducata.
Me caía bastante antipático.
E achei-o mal educado.
But from time to time,
I could see that he was brooding over something.
Aber ab und an schien ihn irgendwas zu bedrücken.
Però ogni tanto dava l'idea di qualcuno
che rimuginava troppo sulle cose.
A veces parecía muy preocupado.
Mas estava a exagerar.
I didn't know why ,
but somehow I couldn't just leave him alone.
Wieso wusste ich nicht,
aber ich musste ihm einfach helfen.
Non ne conoscevo la ragione,
però non potevo semplicemente ignorarlo.
No sabía el motivo,
pero no podía alejarme de él.
Não sabia a razão e deixei estar.
Daddy?
Papa?
Papà...
Papá.
I'm sorry. But I need to reach
the top of the World Tree.
Es tut mir leid,
aber ich muss unbedingt auf die Spitze des Weltenbaums.
Scusate, però io... devo raggiungere la
vetta di quell'albero a tutti i costi!
Lo siento, pero tengo que llegar
al Árbol del Mundo sin falta.
Desculpa, mas tenho que
ir subir à arvore mágica.
Why is it so important?
Warum ist dir das so wichtig?
Perché ci tieni tanto?
¿Por qué?
Mas porquê...?
I'm looking for someone.
Ich suche jemanden.
Sto cercando una persona.
Estoy buscando a una persona.
Procuro alguém.
What do you mean?
Wie meinst du das?
Che vuoi dire?
¿A qué te refieres?
O quê?
It's not easy to explain.
Das ist eine lange Geschichte.
È una cosa un po' difficile da spiegare...
No es fácil de explicar.
Não sei explicar.
Thank you, Leafa. All that
information helped me a lot.
Danke, Lyfa. Du hast mir sehr weitergeholfen.
Ti ringrazio, Leafa... Quello che mi hai detto
mi è stato di grande aiuto.
Gracias, Lyfa.
Me has ayudado con tus explicaciones.
Obrigado, Rifa. Ajudaste-me muito.
Wait.
Warte!
Aspetta!
Espera.
Are you going
to the World Tree?
Du wirst zum Weltenbaum gehen?
Vuoi davvero dirigerti verso l'Yggdrasill?
¿Piensas ir al Árbol del Mundo?
Queres mesmo ir à árvore?
Yes, I need to see
for myself.
Ja. Ich muss es mit eigenen Augen sehen.
Esatto. Devo vedere coi miei occhi.
Sí, quiero comprobarlo en persona.
Sim, tenho que ver com os meus olhos.
But that's crazy.
Das ist Wahnsinn!
Ma non è prudente!
Es una locura...
Isso é ridículo.
It's really far, and there
are a lot of strong monsters.
Er ist sehr weit weg und auf dem Weg lauern starke Monster.
È molto lontano, e poi ci sono
un sacco di mostri pericolosi!
Está muy lejos y lleno
de monstruos peligrosos
É longe e está cheio
de monstros poderosos.
Sure, you're strong, but...
Ich weiß, dass du stark bist, aber ...
Lo so che sei forte, però...
Aunque seas fuerte,...
Tu também és forte, mas...
All right, I’ll take you there!
Lass mich dich hinbringen!
E va bene, allora ti ci accompagno io!
...yo te acompañaré.
Eu levo-te lá.
But since it only took us three days
to reach the World Tree,
Wir waren in nur drei Tagen beim Weltenbaum.
Das war ein ganz schöner Marsch ...
E così arrivammo fino all'Yggdrasil in
tre giorni, fu davvero una marcia forzata!
Llegasteis en solo 3 días.
Apretasteis el paso, ¿eh?
Mesmo tendo sido só 3 dias,
foi uma marcha daquelas...
it really was like a forced march!
Thanks so much, Suguha.
Danke, Suguha-chan.
Grazie di cuore, Suguha.
Gracias, Sugu.
Obrigada, Suguha.
Oh, no, don't thank me.
I had such a good time myself.
Ach, nichts zu danken.
Ich hatte ja auch meinen Spaß dabei.
Massì, figurati! Anche io ne ero molto felice.
No me las des.
Fue divertido.
Obrigada eu, foi divertido!
That's right, we went through a lot,
but I enjoyed my adventure with Kirito.
Ja, es war nicht einfach,
aber diese Reise mit Kirito hat Spaß gemacht.
Insomma, fu parecchio dura, ma andare
all'avventura con Kirito fu davvero divertente.
Aunque fue muy duro, la aventura con
Kirito fue muy divertida.
Foi um aventura complicada que tivemos,
mas divertida.
Tired?
Schon müde?
Sei stanco, non è vero?
¿Cansado?
Cansado?
Nope, not yet.
Noch nicht.
No, posso continuare!
No, aún no.
Não, ainda não.
You hung in there.
Oh, du bist aber hart im Nehmen.
Ce la metti proprio tutta, eh?
Eres un tipo duro, ¿eh?
Uau, tu esforças-te.
I’d like to say that, but our trip
through the sky is over for now.
Aber wir müssen jetzt trotzdem eine
Weile am Boden weitergehen.
In ogni caso ti informo che per un po' dovremo
smettere di spostarci via cielo.
En fin, de momento se acabaron
los viajes aéreos.
Mas vamos descansar um pouco!
Why?
Äh? Warum?
Cosa? E perché?
¿Por qué?
Porquê?
You see that mountain, right?
Siehst du den Berg da drüben?
Vedi quelle montagne?
¿Ves esa montaña?
Vês aquela montanha?
It’s above the altitude limit, so you
have to go through caves to pass it.
Der liegt über der maximalen Flughöhe,
deshalb müssen wir durch die Höhlen, um ihn zu passieren.
Sono più alte del limite di volo, perciò dovremo
passare attraverso le grotte per superarle.
No podemos cruzarla volando.
Debemos atravesar una cueva.
Como fica muito alta, além de atravessarmos
montanhas temos que atravessar cavernas.
I've heard it's the toughest leg
between Sylph territory and Arun.
Angeblich ist das der gefährlichste Teil der Reise,
vom Sylphen-Territorium nach Arun.
Pare che sia la parte più pericolosa del tragitto
che dalle terre Sylph porta ad Alne...
Es el paso más peligroso
entre Sylph y Arun.
Consta que é o trajeto mais difícil
de Sylph a Arun.
I’ve never been past here.
So weit bin ich selbst noch nicht gewesen.
Nemmeno io mi sono mai spinta fin là prima d'ora.
Es la primera vez que vengo por aquí.
É a minha primeira vez.
I see... Caves, huh?
Is it long?
Alles klar. Höhlen also? Sind die lang?
Dunque è così...
E queste grotte, sono molto lunghe?
¿Una cueva?
¿Y es larga?
Muito bem... cavernas. São longas?
Fairly. I hear there's a neutral
mining town midway where we can rest...
Ziemlich.
Abbastanza.
Bastante.
Unterwegs soll man sich in einer neutralen
Minenstadt ausruhen können.
Anche se a metà dovrebbe esserci
una città di minatori dove riposare.
A mitad de camino hay
una ciudad minera donde descansar.
Há uma cidade no caminho,
podemos descansar lá.
Kirito, do you still have time today?
Kirito-kun, wie lange kannst du heute machen?
Senti, Kirito... Hai ancora
tempo per stare qui, oggi?
¿Cómo vas de tiempo hoy?
Como estás de horas?
It’s 7:00 PM in the real world,
huh? I'm okay for a while.
Im RL ist es jetzt 19 Uhr, oder?
Dann kann ich noch ’ne Weile.
Fuori sono le sette di sera, no?
Io per un po' non ho problemi.
Serán las siete de la tarde.
Aún puedo quedarme un buen rato.
Se for VR, 7 da noite.
Por agora estou bem.
Okay... Then we can keep going
for a while. We can rotate out here.
Gut, dann lass uns weitermachen.
Bene! Allora possiamo andare avanti!
Vale, pues esforcémonos un poco más.
Então, bora lá mais um bocado.
Wir können erstmal rotate out machen.
Magari effettuando un logout a rotazione!
¿Hacemos una rotación?
Vamos fazer uma troca...
R-Rotate?
R... Rotate ...?
A rotazione...?
¿R-rotación?
T-troca?
Logging out and resting
while others keep watch.
Ja, so nennt man es, wenn man abwechselnd Pause macht.
Esatto, ci prenderemo una pausa
disconnettendoci a turno.
Sí, hacemos log out por turnos
para descansar.
Ah, fazer Log Out à vez.
You can’t log out instantly here.
In einer neutralen Zone kann man sich nicht komplett ausloggen.
In zona neutrale non è possibile
effettuale il logout dell'avatar,
Como estamos en un área neutral
no podemos bajar la guardia.
É uma zona neutra, não podemos ir logo.
So you log out in turn while who's
left guards your empty avatar.
Darum passt immer einer auf,
während der andere offline ist.
ma se usciamo dal gioco a rotazione, quello
che rimane qui potrà proteggere l'altro.
Así uno descansa mientras el otro
vigila su avatar vacío.
Vamos fazendo trocas
e quem ficar protege o avatar do outro.
I see... Got it.
You can go first.
Alles klar. Geh du zuerst, Lyfa.
Ho capito. In questo caso,
va' pure prima tu, Leafa!
OK, pues vete tú primero.
Muito bem. Começa tu.
"Du kannst dich hier nicht vollständig ausloggen.
Möchtest du trotzdem fortfahren?"
"NON È POSSIBILE EFFETTUARE IL
LOGOUT DA UN TERRENO. VA BENE?"
"¿ESTÁS SEGURO DE QUE QUIERES
SALIR DEJANDO ACTIVO EL AVATAR?"
"NÃO PODE SAIR. PRETENDE CONTINUAR?"
I’m excited.
Ich bin so aufgeregt ...
Io... sono elettrizzata!
Estoy muy emocionada.
Estou ansiosa.
Kirito...
Kirito-kun ...
Kirito.
It's not that I'm in love or anything.
Es ist ja nicht so, dass ich mich in ihn verliebt hätte
Non è che sia innamorata di lui.
No estoy enamorada de ti.
Não é que goste dele.
Or that I'm glad to adventure with someone.
und es etwas Besonderes sei,
mit ihm eine Quest zu machen.
È solo un compagno di avventura!
Ni tampoco estoy así porque
vayamos de aventuras juntos.
Não é que queira estar com ele,...
I’m just looking forward
to journeying to a new world.
Ich bin nur aufgeregt,
weil ich einen neuen Teil dieser Welt erkunden kann.
La verità è che non vedo l'ora di
volare in un mondo tutto nuovo!
Es que me emociona
descubrir nuevos mundos.
...só divertido ir ao novo mundo.
So what was your impression of Kirito
after going on that adventure with him?
Und welchen Eindruck hattest du dann von ihm,
als ihr zusammen die Reise gemacht habt?
Beh, che impressione ti fece andare
all'avventura insieme a Kirito?
¿Qué impresión te causó
al ir de aventuras juntos?
Qual foi a impressão dele depois
da vossa aventura?
You didn't know he was your brother, right?
Du wusstest ja nicht, dass er dein Bruder war.
All'inizio non sapevi che
fosse il tuo fratellone, no?
¿A que no sabías que era tu hermano?
Não sabias que é teu irmão.
My first impression was just,
“He's so fast,” I guess.
Mein erster Eindruck war: „Der hat’s aber eilig."
La mia prima impressione fu che fosse "veloce".
La primera impresión fue
que era muy "rápido".
Achei-o "rápido".
But more than that, his intensity during each and
every battle was nothing like anyone else's...
Aber er war bei jedem Kampf voller Ernst bei der Sache.
So jemandem war ich noch nie begegnet.
Tuttavia, mentre affrontavamo una battaglia dopo l'altra,
la sua onestà lo rese diverso da chiunque altro...
Después que se tomaba cada pelea
más en serio que nadie.
Mas depois apercebi-me
que ele leva isto muito a sério.
Enough, Kirito!
Das ist genug, Kirito-kun!
Ora smettila, Kirito!
Kirito, vale ya.
Já chega, Kirito.
If we lose, it’ll just mean a few extra
hours of flying! Let’s just give up!
Es dauert doch nicht lange, wieder herzukommen,
wenn wir sterben! Wir sollten aufgeben!
Anche se ci uccidono, basterà qualche ora
di volo per tornare qui! È meglio arrenderci!
Si perdemos, volaremos unas horas más.
Abandona ya.
Depois podes continuar. Pára por agora!
No way.
Niemals.
No, mai!
No quiero.
Não.
Hä?
Eh?
¿Eh?
Hã?
As long as I'm alive, I won't
let any party members die.
Solange ich am Leben bin,
wird keines meiner Gruppenmitglieder sterben.
Finché avrò vita, non lascerò che
un membro del mio party venga ucciso!
No dejaré que maten a nadie del grupo
mientras yo viva.
Enquanto estiver vivo ninguém morre.
I'll never let that happen!
Das werde ich nicht zulassen!
Non permetterò mai che accada!
Nunca lo permitiré.
Isso é que não pode ser.
Damn, what's he doing?
Scheiße! Was hat der für’n Problem?!
Ma cosa...! Che diavolo vuole fare?!
Mierda.
Está loco.
Mas que raio?
The moment I realized that the source of
his seriousness was his desire to protect someone,
Als ich mitbekommen habe, dass er so ernst bei der Sache ist,
weil er jemanden beschützen will,
E nel momento in cui capii che la fonte di quell'onestà
era la volontà di proteggere qualcuno,
Al saber que su valor nacía
de su deseo de proteger a alguien,...
Quando me apercebi
que ele queria proteger alguém,...
I thought to myself,
“This is someone I can believe in.”
dachte ich: „Ihm kann ich vertrauen."
pensai "Posso fidarmi di una persona così."
...pensé que podría confiar en él.
..."se for ele acredito", pensei eu.
In the end, it's a game,
so anything goes.
Das hier ist nur ein Spiel, also ist alles erlaubt.
In fondo è solo un videogioco, perciò tutto è lecito.
Esto es un juego después de todo.
Isto não passa de um jogo, ou seja,
vale-tudo.
If you want to kill, you kill.
If you want to steal, you steal.
Wenn man töten will, tötet man.
Wenn man stehlen will, stiehlt man.
Se vuoi uccidere, uccidi! Se vuoi rubare, ruba!
Si quieres matar, matas.
Si quieres robar, robas.
Posso matar, posso roubar.
I've met more people than I care to
who think that way. In a way, it's true.
Ich habe mehr solcher Leute getroffen, als mir lieb war
Ho incontrato troppa gente
che ragionava in questo modo...
Estoy harto de encontrarme
a tipos que piensan así.
Encontrei gente que pensa assim.
I used to think that way too.
und in gewisser Weise stimmt das ja …
Ich habe auch mal so gedacht.
Per certi versi è vero,
e io stesso un tempo la pensavo così.
En parte, es verdad.
Yo antes también pensaba igual.
Por um lado é verdade.
Também já pensei assim.
But it's not true. There are things you have
to protect because it is a virtual world.
Aber das ist nicht richtig. Es gibt Dinge,
die wir beschützen müssen, gerade weil diese Welt nicht real ist.
Ma mi sbagliavo. Ci sono cose che dobbiamo proteggere,
proprio perché siamo in un mondo virtuale.
Pero justo por ser un mundo virtual,
hay cosas que debemos proteger.
Mas não é bem assim. Precisamente porque
é um mundo virtual devo proteger os meus.
I learned that from
someone important to me.
Das hat mich jemand gelehrt,
der mir unheimlich wichtig ist.
Me l'ha insegnato una persona a cui tengo molto.
Eso me lo enseñó alguien
muy importante para mí.
Disse-me alguém importante.
If you give in
to your urges here,
Gibt man sich in dieser Welt seinen Begierden hin,
verändert das einen auch unweigerlich im Reallife.
Se ci lasciamo accecare dai desideri in questo mondo,
anche il nostro "io" reale ne pagherà il prezzo.
Si la ambición nos domina aquí,
eso repercute en el mundo real.
Se nos deixarmos levar pelos desejos,
isso reflete-se no mundo real.
the price is that it changes
your personality in real life.
The player and
the character are one.
Spieler und Character sind ein und dasselbe.
Giocatore e personaggio sono una cosa sola!
El jugador y el personaje
son una misma cosa.
O jogador e o personagem são um.
I like you, Leafa.
I want to be your friend.
Ich mag dich, Lyfa, und möchte gern mit dir befreundet sein.
Tu... Mi piaci, Leafa! Vorrei che fossimo amici!
Lyfa, me caes bien.
Y quiero que seamos amigos.
Eu gosto de ti.
Quero ser teu amigo.
No matter what the reason,
attacking someone for my own benefit
Aus welchem Grund auch immer,
ich würde niemals zu meinen eigenen Vorteil jemanden umbringen,
Quale che possa essere il motivo, non ucciderei mai
una persona come te per il mio profitto personale!
Yo jamás mataría a nadie
para beneficiarme.
Seja por que razão for, eu nunca trairia
alguém para o meu...
is something I'd never do.
der mir wichtig ist.
Non potrei mai farlo!
Nunca.
...próprio interesse.
That's why, no matter who his opponent was,
my brother...
Darum hat mein Bruder, Kirito-kun, vor keinem Kampf gekniffen
Per questo, qualsiasi nemico affrontasse,
il fratellone... Kirito non fuggiva mai.
Por eso Kirito nunca abandona
contra ningún oponente.
Seja com quem for o Kirito nunca
irá fugir à batalha.
Kirito never tried to run away.
I believed that there was
no way he could ever lose.
und an seinen Sieg geglaubt.
Credeva nel fatto che
non sarebbe mai stato sconfitto.
Confiaba en que jamás perdería.
Acreditei que nunca perderia.
Kirito!
Kirito-kun!
¡Kirito!
Kirito!
Die!
Stirb!
Muori!
¡Muere!
Toma lá.
You know, being close as siblings is all well and good,
Es ist schön, wenn ihr euch gut versteht,
aber da wird doch wohl keine verbotene Liebe im Spiel sein?
Un bel rapporto fra fratelli è un'ottima cosa, ma la tua
sorellona è preoccupata che si tratti di amore proibito.
Es bueno que os llevéis bien, pero...
Me preocupa tu amor prohibido.
É bom que os irmão sejam amigos,...
but this older chick's
a little worried about forbidden love...
...mas seria estranho caso houvesse outro
tipo de amor no meio...
Wh-What are you talking about?
Never mind that, let's get back to practice! Practice!
Was redest du da?! Lasst uns lieber weiter üben!
M-ma che stai dicendo?! Piuttosto
continuiamo con la lezione, su!
¿P-pero qué dices?
¡Venga a entrenar, a entrenar!
Que estás para aí a dizer?
Vamos treinar!
All right, then shall we give it another go?
Dann mal auf zum Endspurt.
Allora diamoci di nuovo da fare!
Bueno, un último esfuerzo.
Vá, vamos lá então!
If only I'd known before I fell in love with him...
Wenn ich es nur vorher gewusst hätte ...
Se l'avessi saputo prima di innamorarmi...
Si lo hubiese sabido
antes de enamorarme...
Quem me dera ter sabido antes...
Is that you, Big Brother?
Bist du das, Onii-chan?
Sei tu... fratellone?
¿E-eres mi hermano?
És meu irmão?
Hä?
Cosa?
¿Eh?
Hã?
Sugu?
Sugu ...?
Sugu...
Sugu?
Suguha?
¿Suguha?
This is awful.
Mein Gott ...
Non è giusto!
Eso es muy cruel.
Não pode!
This isn't fair...
Ich halt das nicht aus ... Das darf doch nicht ...
Questo... È troppo!
Demasiado...
Ai minha nossa...!
- It isn't...
- S-Sugu?
S... Sugu?
S-Sugu...
S-sugu...
Su-sugu...
Are you sure you want to log out?
"Möchtest du dich wirklich ausloggen?"
"VUOI DAVVERO EFFETTUARE IL LOGOUT?"
"¿ESTÁS SEGURO DE QUE
QUIERES SALIR?"
"QUER MESMO SAIR?"
Sugu!
¡Sugu!
I... I...
Ich ... Ich ...
Io... Io...
Yo...
Eu, eu...
I...
Ich
Io ho...
Yo...
Eu.
I betrayed my own heart!
habe meine eigenen Gefühle ignoriert!
Ho rinnegato i miei sentimenti!
...he traicionado mis sentimientos.
Fui traída pelo meu coração!
I betrayed my love for you...
Ich liebe dich, aber ich habe mich selbst belogen.
Ho tradito l'amore che provo... per te!
He traicionado mi amor... por ti.
Porque me apaixonei por ti!
I was about to forget it all, to give it up.
To fall in love with Kirito...
Ich wollte aufgeben und einfach alles vergessen.
Ich wollte mich in Kirito-kun verlieben.
Avevo intenzione di dimenticare tutto,
rinunciare a te e innamorarmi di Kirito!
Quise olvidarlo todo
y enamorarme de Kirito.
Esqueci e desisti de tudo
e queria me apaixonar por ti.
No, I already had!
Nein, ich habe es sogar schon!
E ormai ci ero riuscita!
Sí, ya me había enamorado.
Mas já aconteceu!
But... But...
Aber trotzdem ...
Invece... Invece ora...
Y sin embargo...
Mas ainda assim...
L-Love? But we're...
L... Lieben? Aber wir sind doch ...
A-amore? Ma... Sugu, noi due siamo...
¿E-enamorarte?
Si somos...
Apaixonar? Mas nós somos...
I know.
Ich weiß es.
Io lo so.
Ya lo sé.
Eu sei.
Hä?
Eh?
¿Eh?
Hã?
I already know!
Ich weiß längst alles!
Ormai so tutto!
Yo también lo sé.
Já sei disso.
You and I aren't really siblings!
Du und ich, wir sind keine richtigen Geschwister!
So che in realtà io e te non siamo
affatto fratello e sorella!
¡Tú y yo no somos hermanos de verdad!
Mas não somos mesmo irmãos!
I've known for the last two years.
Ich weiß das schon seit zwei Jahren.
Sono due anni che conosco la verità su noi due.
Hace ya dos años que lo sé.
Já sei disso há uns dois anos.
Wasn't the reason you quit kendo
and started avoiding me
Du wusstest schon länger davon und hast deswegen mit dem
Kendo aufgehört
Dimmi, se hai smesso di praticare
il kendo e hai iniziato a evitarmi,
Por eso dejaste el kendo
y empezaste a evitarme.
O facto de teres desistido do Kendo
e me evitares é porque...
because you knew the whole time?
und bist mir aus dem Weg gegangen, oder?
è perché tu lo sapevi già da molto tempo, vero?
Lo sabías desde hacia tiempo, ¿verdad?
...já sabes disso há muito tempo.
You were distancing yourself
because I'm not your real sister, right?
Du hast mich gemieden,
weil ich nicht deine echte Schwester bin, oder?!
Mi hai tenuta a distanza perché non sono
davvero tua sorella, non è così?!
Me evitabas porque
no soy tu hermana, ¿eh?
Evitavas-me porque
não sou mesmo tua irmã?
If so...
Wieso ... Wieso bist du auf einmal so lieb zu mir?!
Allora... Perché tutto a un tratto hai
deciso di essere gentile con me?!
E-entonces, ¿por qué eres tan cariñoso
ahora conmigo?
Então porque é que agora és simpático?
Why are you
being nice to me now?
I was so happy you
came back from SAO.
Ich war so glücklich, als du aus SAO zurückkamst.
Io... Ero così felice quando sei ritornato da SAO!
Me alegré mucho
cuando volviste de SAO.
Fiquei muito contente quando voltaste
da SAO.
I was so happy you were being
nice to me, like when we were little.
Ich war so froh,
dass wir endlich wieder so gut miteinander auskamen wie früher.
Ero contenta che fossi di nuovo carino con me,
come quando eravamo piccoli!
Era muy feliz porque nos llevábamos bien
igual que cuando éramos pequeños.
Ser amigos como quando éramos crianças,
fiquei mesmo contente.
You were finally giving me a chance...
That’s what I thought.
Ich dachte, du gibst mir endlich eine Chance!
Pensavo che finalmente stessi
iniziando a considerarmi!
Pensé que por fin
te habías fijado en mí.
Pensava que estavas
a tomar conta de mim.
But... If I'd known this would happen,
I wish you'd stayed cold to me.
Wenn ich gewusst hätte, was passiert,
wäre es mir lieber gewesen, du wärst weiter auf Distanz geblieben.
Però... Se doveva finire così, avrei preferito
che tu continuassi a evitarmi!
De haber sabido que pasaría esto,...
Mas mais valia que tivesses sido frio,
para isto.
If you had, I wouldn't have realized
my feelings for you...
Dann hätte ich mich vielleicht niemals in dich verliebt
Almeno io non mi sarei
mai accorta di quanto mi piacessi!
...no me hubiese dado cuenta
que me gustabas,...
Em vez de me ter apercebido
que gostava de ti,...
Or been sad to learn
about Asuna...
und es hätte nicht so wehgetan,
von Asuna-san zu erfahren ...
Non avrei sofferto tanto per essere
venuta a conoscenza di Asuna!
...ni me hubiese apenado
al saber lo de Asuna,...
...e saber da Asuna, talvez...
Or fallen in love with
Kirito instead of you!
Dann hätte ich mich als Ersatz für dich auch nicht in
Kirito-kun verliebt!
E di certo non mi sarei mai innamorata di Kirito
nel tentativo di dimenticare te!
...ni hubiera intentado enamorme
de Kirito para olvidarme de ti.
...não me tivesse apaixonado pelo Kirito!
I'm sorry.
Tut mir leid.
Mi dispiace.
Lo siento.
Desculpa.
Just... leave me alone...
Lass mich bitte allein.
Ora... Lasciami sola.
Déjame sola.
Deixa estar.
Why?
Warum?
Ma che...
¿Por qué...?
Porquê...
Why?
Wieso?
Perché?
¿Por qué...?
Mas porquê...
I wanted to apologize to you...
Ich wollte mich bei dir entschuldigen,
Io... Volevo scusarmi con te, Sugu...
Quería pedirte perdón.
Queria pedir-te desculpa...
But I didn't know what to say.
aber ich wusste nicht, was ich sagen soll.
Ma non riuscivo a trovare le parole,
Pero como no me salían las palabras,...
...mas não me saía nada.
So I thought I'd at least give you a free shot.
Also wollte ich dir einen freien Schlag geben.
così ho pensato di farmi colpire
dalla tua spada, almeno una volta.
...pensé que al menos
podría dejarme golpear.
Eu que ia levar com a espada...
You did too?
Das wolltest du?
Anche tu?
¿Tú?
Tu?
I'm sorry.
Es tut mir leid.
Perdonami.
Perdóname.
Desculpa.
I am too.
Mir auch.
Anch'io ti chiedo perdono.
No, perdóname tú a mí.
Desculpa, eu!
I still haven't returned from that world,
not in the true sense.
Ich bin noch nicht wirklich aus dieser Welt zurückgekehrt.
Sai... Io non sono mai ritornato
veramente da quel mondo.
En realidad, aún no he regresado
de aquel mundo.
Eu ainda não voltei ao outro mundo.
It hasn't ended. Not yet.
Es ist noch nicht vorbei.
Non è ancora finita.
Todavía no he acabado con él.
Ainda não acabou.
Until she wakes up,
I'm not really back in reality.
Solange Asuna nicht aufgewacht ist,
kann ich nicht in die Realität zurück.
Finché lei non riprenderà conoscenza,
la mia vita reale non potrà avere inizio.
Mi vida real no empezará
hasta que ella vuelva en sí.
Se ela não acordar não volto à realidade.
That's why...
Darum
Per questo...
Por eso...
Por isso...
I don't know how I should think of you yet.
weiß ich jetzt auch nicht,
was ich gerade von dir denken soll.
Mi è ancora difficile capire come dovrei
comportarmi nei tuoi confronti, Sugu.
Todavía no puedo
aclarar qué siento por ti.
...ainda não sei o que fazer sobre ti.
I'll be waiting...
I'll be waiting for you to come home to us for real.
Ich werde warten. Ich warte auf dich,
bis du wirklich wieder nach Hause zurückgekehrt bist.
Ti aspetterò, fratellone. Continuerò ad aspettare il
momento in cui ritornerai definitivamente a casa nostra.
Esperaré a que vuelvas
de nuevo a casa.
Eu espero.
Espero pelo momento que regressas a casa.
So I'm going to help you!
Aber bitte lass mich dir helfen!
E ti aiuterò a fare in modo che ciò accada presto!
Yo también quiero ayudarte.
Eu também te ajudo!
Hey, Suguha! There's no point unless you come!
Komm schon, Suguha! Ohne dich läuft nichts!
Dai, Suguha! Guarda che se non entri non incominciamo!
¡Suguha, ven!
¡Te estamos esperando!
Hei, Suguha! Anda que tens que começar!
Okay!
Ja!
Sì!
¡V-voy!
Sim!
And after reaching the World Tree
thanks to your sister's guidance,
Deine Schwester hat dich also zum
Weltenbaum geführt und als ihr endlich da wart,
Beh, grazie all'aiuto della tua sorellina
sei arrivato fino all'Yggdrasil,
Tu hermana te guio
hasta el Árbol del Mundo,...
Graças à tua irmã que te
guiou até à árvore tu...
you cleared the Grand Quest, supposedly designed by
Sugou to be so difficult that it could never be solved,
hast du die Meisterquest abgeschlossen,
die Sugou systembedingt als unlösbar konfiguriert hat,
e hai completato la quest principale, creata con un
grado di difficoltà ritenuto impossibile secondo Sugo,
...y completaste la misión imposible
que había diseñado Sugou.
...passaste a missão que era difícilima
graças a um erro de sistema...
and rescued Asuna, am I right?
und Asuna-kun gerettet, stimmt’s?
solo per poter salvare Asuna?
Así fue como rescataste a Asuna, ¿no?
...e ajudaste a Asuna?
No, it's not like I cleared it alone.
Nein, alleine habe ich das nicht geschafft.
No, io da solo non sarei riuscito a completarla.
No, no la completé yo solo.
Não, não o fiz sozinho.
Just a little more...
Nur noch ein bisschen ...
Solo un altro po'!
Un poco más.
Mais um pouco.
Just a little more...
Nur noch ein Stück ...
Solo... un altro po'...
Un ... poco más...
Mais um bocadinho...
Kirito!
Kirito-kun!
¡Kirito!
Kirito!
Eck Karla Zwart Tugari Velfa Hym!
Ek, Kalla, Svalt, Tugari, Verba, Hymn!
Ek Kanra Sbalt Tugari Belfahim
Ekku kanra subaruto to yugāri berufahimu
That's dark magic...
Das ist Schwarze Magie ...?
Ha pronunciato... una formula di magia oscura?
¿Magia oscura?
Isso é uma magia da escuridão?
Grott Regin Kavr Nisavoll!
Brot, Regin, Karpa, Meesafol!
¡Brotolegiri Kaba Misabol!
Burottoregiri kaba a myizaboru!
Dragoons, ready breath attack!
Drachenritter, fertig machen zum Flammenangriff!
Dragoni! Preparatevi al soffio di fuoco!
¡Escuadrón de Dragones,
preparad el ataque Aliento!
Exército Dragão,
preparem-se para o ataque!
Sylphs, prepare additional offensives!
Sylphen, bereitet zusätzliche Angriffe vor!
Esercito Sylph, preparatevi all'attacco extra!
¡Escuadrón Sylph,
preparad el ataque extra!
Exército Sylph, preparem-se para
o ataque extra!
Fire Breath... Go!
Feueratem! Jetzt!
Soffio di fuoco... lanciate!
¡Disparad Aliento de Fuego!
Bafo de fogo, ataquem!
Fenrir Storm... Fire!
Fenrir-Sturm! Feuer!
Tempesta di Fenrir, fuoco a volontà!
¡Ahora! ¡Tormenta Fenrir!
Tempestade Fenrir, soltar!
It was Leafa and Recon, Sakuya, Alicia,
Die Quest abgeschlossen haben Lyfa, Recon, Sakuya, Alicia,
Ad avere completato quella quest sono stati
Leafa, e Recon, Sakuya, Alicia,
Gracias a Lyfa, Rekon,
Sakuya, Alicia,...
A minha vitória deveu-se à Rifa, Recon,
Sakuya, Arisha,...
and the Sylph and Cait Sith warriors.
sowie die Krieger der Sylphen und Caith Sith.
e gli eserciti di Sylph e Cait Sith.
...y a los guerreros Sylph y Cait Shit.
...aos Sylph e aos Kettoshi.
It was thanks to their help
that I was able to reach Asuna.
Ich habe Asuna nur deshalb erreicht,
weil sie alle mir geholfen haben.
Tutti loro mi hanno soccorso,
perché potessi arrivare in tempo da Asuna.
puede superar aquella aventura y
llegar hasta Asuna.
Graças a eles cheguei à Asuna.
I see.
Verstehe.
Capisco.
Ajá.
Percebido.
But just then, Sugou ? a.k.a. Oberon,
the Fairy King ? appeared.
Aber dann stellte sich dir Sugou in Form des
Elfenkönigs Oberon in den Weg.
Però è lì che apparve Sugo
come Oberon, il re delle fate.
Pero entonces apareció Sugou como
Oberon el rey de las hadas.
Mas isso das fadas foi graças ao Sugou.
Normally, I wouldn't think it possible for you, a player,
to defeat Sugou, the game master, but...
Normalerweise wäre es für einen Spieler wie dich
unmöglich gewesen, einen Gamemaster zu besiegen.
Da un punto di vista normale, pensare che un giocatore come
te abbia battuto Sugo, il game master, sarebbe impossibile.
Lo lógico sería pensar que un jugador
jamás podría vencer al Game Master...
Mesmo que tenhas te tornado num grande jogador,
não creio que consigas derrotar o Sugou.
Now!
Ja!
Sì!
¡Más!
Sim!
Great! I love it!
NPC women just can't make that face...
Toll! Ich liebe es!
Keine NPC-Frau könnte so einen Gesichtsausdruck imitieren!
È proprio vero, una ragazza NPC non riuscirebbe
mai a riprodurre quell'espressione!
Me encanta.
Un PNJ nunca tendría esta cara.
Mas que bem. As raparigas de NPC sempre
não conseguem fazer essa cara não é.
What a lovely smell.
Hach, welch schöner Duft.
Aah, che buon profumo!
Qué bien huele.
Que cheirinho.
Replicating your scent from the real world was hard.
Es war nicht leicht, den Duft der echten Asuna zu reproduzieren.
Sapessi quanto ho faticato per riuscire a
ricreare qui il profumo che hai nella realtà!
Me ha costado mucho simular
tu perfume, Asuna.
Foi complicado voltar a reconstituir o
teu cheiro do mundo real.
I hope you appreciate how much work it took
to get an analyzer into your hospital room...
Ich hoffe, du weißt die Mühen, die ich auf mich genommen habe,
um die Analysatoren ins Krankenhaus zu schmuggeln, zu schätzen.
Ho messo anche un analizzatore
nella tua stanza di ospedale.
Tuve que meter el analizador
en tu habitación, ¿sabes?
Avalia meu esforço para levar
o analisador no quarto de doentes.
Stop it.
Hör auf ...!
Smettila...
Para.
Pára!
Sugou...
Sugou!
Sugo...
Sugou...
My my...
Meine Güte ...
Ma tu guarda.
Vaya, vaya.
Calma lá.
Onlookers can just grovel on the ground! Writhing!
Kriech brav vor mir im Dreck, du Wurm!
Gli spettatori dovrebbero limitarsi a guardare
in silenzio e strisciare per terra!
¡Calla y mira!
Calminha com isso que aqui não mandas!
Kirito!
Kirito-kun!
¡Kirito!
Kirito!
System command!
System Command! Schmerzregler
Comando di sistema! Assorbitore di dolore.
Comando del sistema,
"Tolerancia al dolor"
Comando de sistema, Pain Absorver!
Change pain absorber
from level 10 to level 8.
von Stufe zehn auf acht heruntersetzen.
Da livello 10 a livello 8.
Cambio de nivel 10 al 8.
Passar de nível 10 para 8.
Hurts, no? I'll gradually let the pain increase,
so look forward to that.
Tut weh, oder? Ich werde deine Schmerzen schrittweise erhöhen. Freu dich schon mal!
Fa male, vero? Beh, farò in modo che a poco a poco
il tuo dolore aumenti, tieniti pronto.
¿Duele verdad?
Pues te dolerá más aún.
Dói não dói? Vai ficando cada vez
mais difícil, espera só.
Of course, below level 3,
it will start to affect your physical body.
Unter Level drei wird es aber auch auf deinen realen Körper
Auswirkungen haben.
Sai, sembra che regolandolo al di sotto del livello 3
sia in grado di procurare danni anche al corpo reale.
Cuando baje al nivel 3,
causará heridas en tu cuerpo real.
Na verdade, se for abaixo de
nível 3 tem efeito no corpo real.
Now then...
Nun denn ...
Allora...
Veamos.
Então.
S-Sweet... So sweet!
Ah, so süß! So süß!
Aah! Hai un sapore così dolce!
Ah, ¡qué dulzor!
Doce... Docinha!
Sugou, you bastard!
Sugou, du Bastard!
Sugo, maledetto!
Sugou...¡Maldito!
Sugou... pára!
Bastard!
Du Bastard!
Maledetto!
¡Maldito seas!
Vou-te matar!
You bastard, I'll kill you!
I'll kill you no matter what!
Ich bring dich um!
Dannato vigliacco, ti ucciderò...
Te... mataré...
Ouviste! Vou-te matar!
Ich murks dich ab!
Giuro che ti ucciderò!
¡Te juro que te mataré!
Vou-te matar!
Are you going to run away?
Läufst du davon?
Vuoi fuggire?
¿Pretendes huir?
Fujo?
That’s not it... I'm going to accept reality.
Nein ... Ich akzeptiere nur die Realität.
Niente affatto. Sto solo ammettendo la realtà.
No, estoy aceptando la verdad.
Não. Fico para ver.
Are you going to surrender?
To the power of a system you once denied.
Dann gibst du nach?
Gegenüber der Macht des Systems, das du einst ablehntest?
Vuoi sottometterti al potere di un sistema
a cui ti sei già opposto una volta?
¿Te rendirás a un sistema al que
ya has ganado antes?
Rendo-me ao sistema.
I don't have a choice.
I'm a player, and he's a GM.
Was soll ich denn machen?
Ich bin ein Spieler und er ein Gamemaster!
Che altro potrei fare?! Io sono solo un giocatore,
mentre lui è il game master.
No puedo hacer nada.
Él es el Game Master, y yo solo un jugador.
Nada a fazer. Sou apenas jogador,
ele é o mestre.
Those words make a mockery of our battle.
Deine Worte verhöhnen unseren einstigen Kampf.
Le tue parole sono un insulto al nostro scontro.
No deshonres aquel combate.
Não digas isso.
Our battle that proved
human will superior to the system,
Erst dieser Kampf zeigte mir die wahre
Macht des menschlichen Willens
Uno scontro grazie al quale ho compreso che la volontà
umana è in grado di sovrastare il sistema,
Tú me enseñaste que la voluntad
era más poderosa que el Sistema.
Fizeste-me ver que há poderes superiores
a mim,...
and awakened me to the possibilities of the future.
und die Möglichkeiten, die die Zukunft bereit hält.
e che mi ha aperto gli occhi
verso possibilità future.
Con nuestra pelea me abriste los ojos
a nuevas posibilidades.
...que há outras possibilidades futuras.
You're...
Du bist ...?
Ma tu sei...
¿Tú eres...?
Tu és...?
Stand up, Kirito!
Erhebe dich, Kirito-kun!
In piedi, Kirito.
Levántate, Kirito.
Levanta-te, Kirito.
It's true that a game master's
authority is ultra-powerful.
Stimmt, ein Gamemaster hat viele Berechtigungen.
In effetti, il potere di un game master è incredibile.
El poder del Game Master es tremendo.
Sem dúvida que
o poder do mestre é forte.
As long as he's in that world,
he's capable of unleashing god-like powers.
In der Welt des Spiels haben sie fast so viel Macht wie ein Gott.
In un mondo come quello, si tratterebbe di un potere
equiparabile a quello degli stessi dei.
Dentro de su mundo tiene
la fuerza de un dios.
É possível atingir um nível de força
como os deuses.
But... those powers were granted
to him by the system.
Aber diese Macht wurde ihm nur vom System verliehen.
Però... Tale potere è qualcosa che
gli è stato garantito dal sistema.
Pero... esa fuerza se la da el sistema.
Mas é uma força atríbuida ao sistema.
It's not like he discovered them
or honed them himself.
Er hat sie sich nicht selbst erarbeitet.
Non è qualcosa che ho scoperto e compreso da solo.
No la ha conseguido
por sus propios medios.
Não fui eu que a criei.
True power can always be found inside you.
Die wahre Kraft steckt immer in einem selbst.
Il vero potere è sempre quello
che ognuno di noi ha dentro di sé.
El poder verdadero siempre
está en nuestro interior.
A força está sempre dentro de mim.
In a virtual world... and in the real world.
Egal, ob in der virtuellen oder der realen Welt.
Che si tratti di un mondo virtuale o di quello reale...
Tanto en el mundo virtual...
como en el mundo real.
No mundo virtual e real.
There's nothing like ice cream
after a day at the pool!
Jetzt holen wir uns ein Eis!
Dopo la piscina facciamoci una granita!
¿Qué tal un helado?
Depois da piscina um gelado?
What an ice idea!
Auf Eis bin ich schon ganz heiß!
È sempre gradita!
¡Sí, heladooo!
Ai que bom!
In the end, Sugou self-destructed.
All because he overestimated the powers he was given.
Sugou hat sich sein eigenes Grab geschaufelt,
weil er sich selbst überschätzt hat.
Sugo si è rovinato con le sue stesse mani, per avere
confidato troppo nel potere che gli è stato affidato.
Sugou se autodestruyó.
Confió demasiado en ese falso poder.
O Sugoi auto-destruiu-se.
Teve demasiada confiança...
I see, self-destruct, eh?
Verstehe. Sein eigenes Grab ...
Già, con le sue stesse mani...
Con que se autodestruyó...
Pois. Auto-destruição.
"Suguha : Wir gehen bald rüber."
"[MAIL SUGUHA]:
STIAMO VENENDO A PRENDERTI, D'ACCORDO?"
"SUGUHA:
YA VAMOS PARA ALLÁ"
"SUGUHA
VOU TER AÍ CONTIGO."
"Rika : Flirtest du etwa mit unserer sexy Lehrerin?!"
"[MAIL RIKA]:NON AVRAI MICA FATTO BIRICHINATE
CON QUELLA BELLA DOTTORESSA?!"
"RIKA:
¿NO ESTARÁS HACIENDO MANITAS?"
"RIKA
NÃO ESTÁS A FAZER NADA COM A CONSELHEIRA?!"
What happened next,
you already know, Mr. Kikuoka.
Alles Weitere wissen Sie bereits, Kikuoka-san.
Il resto della storia lo
conosce anche lei, signor Kikuoka.
El resto de la historia ya lo sabe.
O Kikuoka também sabe
o que se passou depois.
That should be enough, right? I'm supposed to
meet the others in ALO after this.
Das reicht doch langsam?
Ich bin mit den anderen in ALO verabredet, also gehe ich jetzt.
Basta così? Ora ho promesso agli altri di incontrarmi
con loro in ALO, quindi se vuoi scusarmi...
Eso es todo, ¿no? Me voy.
Me esperan para jugar al ALO.
Já chega não? Fiquei de ir ter com as
de ALO. Fico-me por aqui.
If you'll excuse me...
Oh, right ? just one last thing before you go.
Ach ja, eines noch:
Giusto, ancora un'ultima cosa.
Una última pregunta.
Mais uma coisa.
I wonder if you've ever heard
the term, “The Seed?”
Hast du schon mal von „The Seed" gehört?
Hai già per caso sentito da
qualche parte il nome "The Seed"?
¿Has oído hablar de "La Semilla"?
Já ouviste o nome "The Shido"?
Yes, of course.
Ja, natürlich.
Sì, certo.
Claro que sí.
Sim, claro.
Till we meet again, Kirito.
Wir sehen uns, Kirito-kun.
Ci incontreremo ancora, Kirito.
Hasta pronto, Kirito.
Até breve, Kirito.
July 25, 2025 Tule Island in ALO
"25. JULI 2025 - INSEL THULE IN ALO"
"25 DE JULIO DE 2025
ALO, ISLA DE THULE"
"25 DE JULHO DE 2025, INTERIOR DE ALO,
ILHA DE TOURÉ"
Hey, Kirito... I was never so glad about ALO time
and real time not being in sync as I am today!
Kirito, ich habe mich noch nie so sehr wie heute darüber gefreut,
dass die Zeit in ALO anders tickt als im Reallife.
Sai, Kirito... Sono davvero felice che il tempo
in ALO sia in sincrono con quello del mondo reale!
Me alegro que el tiempo en ALO
sea diferente al del mundo real.
Kirito, com dias como este às vezes
não me apetece voltar à realidade.
Yeah, since it's already nighttime in the real world.
Ja, im RL ist es schon Nacht.
A dire il vero nella realtà è già sera...
Sí, allí afuera ya es de noche.
Na realidade já é de noite...
I'm telling you, it's gotta be like this
at the beach! Blue skies!
Zum Sommer gehören einfach ein blauer Himmel ...
E infatti dovevamo venire al mare!
Il cielo azzurro!
¡Esta es la playa perfecta!
¡Mira qué cielo!
O mar deve ser assim, céu azul!
White sand...
Ein weißer Strand ...
La sabbia bianca...
Arena blanca...
Praia branca...
The oncoming waves!
Die rauschenden Wellen ...
Le onde che si infrangono.
¡El vaivén de las olas!
Ondas a bater!!
Dazzling sunlight...
Die strahlende Sonne ...
Il sole che splende...
Un sol deslumbrante...
E o sol radiante...
And...
Und ...
E poi...
Y...
E...
Hey there! Thanks for waiting!
Jo, da bin ich!
Ehi, scusate l'attesa!
¡Perdón por el retraso!
Yo! Desculpem a demora!
Hey, what's the matter, you two?
Hey, was habt ihr beiden denn?
Ehi, ma che vi prende, a voi due?
Oye, ¿qué os pasa?
Que estão a fazer vocês os dois?
- What are you doing!
- Come on, it's so cold!
Wah! Das ist kalt! Was machst du denn ...?
- Ehi, ti ho detto che è fredda!
- Che stai facendo?
- ¡Ay qué fría!
- ¡¿Qué haces?!
-Está muito fria!
-Pára...!
STR mode power, full speed ahead!
Und jetzt volle Kanne!
Bwahahah! Assaggia il vero potere di una STR!
¡A topeee!
Poder total STR!
I'll go you one better! Pina, Water Breath!
Pass bloß auf! Pina, Water Breath!
Non mi farò sconfiggere! Pina, soffio d'acqua!
¡Ahora verás!
¡Pina, Aliento Marino!
Eu não perco, Pina!
Fire!
Feuer!
Azione!
¡Dispara!
Toma lá!
That's my Pina!
Klasse, Pina!
Grande, Pina!
¡Muy bien, Pina!
Muito bem Pina!
Yes, she did it!
Wir haben’s geschafft!
Ce l'abbiamo fatta!
¡Buen trabajo!
Muito bem!
Leafa, do you think all that training
you did today will pay off?
Lyfa-chan, hat das Üben heute Mittag geholfen?
Allora, Leafa, l'allenamento speciale
di oggi ha dato i suoi frutti?
Lyfa, ¿te ha servido el entrenamiento?
Rifa, consegues ter efeito
do treinamento?
Y-Yes, I'm all set! I'm not afraid anymore!
J... Ja! Unheimlich. Ich hab keine Angst mehr.
C-certo, ovviamente! Ora non ho per niente paura!
¡S-sí, ha sido perfecto!
¡Ya no tengo miedo!
Sim! Já não tenho medo!
...As long as my feet can touch the bottom.
Solange ich stehen kann.
Quantomeno finché ci tocco.
Bueno, mientras haga pie.
Se for água rasa...
Really? That's good to hear.
Oh, but where we're headed later on...
Das freut mich. Oh, aber da, wo wir nachher hin wollen ...
Ah, meno male.
Però... Nel posto in cui andremo ora...
Me alegro, pero al sitio
que vamos a ir ahora...
Muito bem. Mas para onde vamos?
Yes, I know. I wonder how deep this dungeon
at the bottom of the sea is...
Stimmt, die Quest findet am Meeresgrund statt.
Wie tief müssen wir?
Già, è vero, il dungeon in fondo al mare...
Mi chiedo quanto sia profondo...
¿A qué profundidad está
esa mazmorra submarina?
Como será o nível de produndidade
nas misões de baixo de água...
Let's see... I think it was around
100 meters or so from the surface...
Ähm, ich glaube, so hundert Meter etwa.
Ecco, se non sbaglio...
È cento metri sotto alla superficie...
Pues... A unos cien metros.
A uns 100 metros da superfície...
O-One hundred?
H... Hundert?!
C-cento...
¿C-cien?
C-cem...!
N-No, no, I'll find a way!
I... Ist gut! Ich gebe mein Bestes!
N-no, posso farcela!
¡V-vale!
¡Yo no me rindo!
Não, vou-me esforçar!
After all, it's for Yui's sake, right?
Wir machen das immerhin für Yui-chan.
Lo farò per Yui!
Lo hacemos por Yui, ¿no?
É pela Yui não é...?
Thank you, Leafa!
Danke, Lyfa-chan.
Grazie, Leafa.
Gracias, Lyfa.
Obrigada, Rifa.
And then, see... Would you believe Kirito?
Und als er dann den gigantischen Fisch gesehen hat,
hat Kirito-kun ganz laut gekreischt.
E poi Kirito, nel momento in cui ha visto il
signore del lago, ha lanciato un urlo incredibile!
Y Kirito gritó cuando vio
al Nushi del lago.
O Kirito gritou tão alto quando viu
o lorde do lago!
TThe second he sees the guardian of the lake,
he lets out a blood-curdling scream!
The second he sees the guardian of the lake,
"24. JULI 2025 - YGGDRASIL CITY"
Und als er dann den gigantischen Fisch gesehen hat,
hat Kirito-kun ganz laut gekreischt.
"24 DE JULIO DE 2025
CIUDAD DE YGGDRASIL"
Y Kirito gritó cuando vio
al Nushi del lago.
"24 DE JULHO DE 2025,
CIDADE DE YGGDRASILL"
O Kirito gritou tão alto quando viu
o lorde do lago!
-July 24, 2025 Yggdrasil City-
Like “YIIIIIIIIIKES!”
"24. JULI 2025 - YGGDRASIL CITY"
Hijaaaah!
Uaaaaaah!
"24 DE JULIO DE 2025
CIUDAD DE YGGDRASIL"
"¡¡¡Buajaaah!!!"
"24 DE JULHO DE 2025,
CIDADE DE YGGDRASILL"
Tipo... Ahhhhhhhhhhh!
H-Hey, it wasn't that out of control.
Not much more than a “Whoaaaaa!” I'm sure!
D... Das stimmt doch gar nicht! Ich war vielleicht überrascht,
aber ich hab doch nicht gekreischt!
N-non ho urlato così forte!
È stata più una cosa tipo "Iiiiiiih!"
No grité tan fuerte.
No pasó de un: "¡Aaah!"
Não foi assim!
Foi mais ihhhh!
You're so lucky! I wish I could've seen
the guardian spirit, too!
Wie schön. Den hätte ich auch gerne gesehen.
Che bello... Anche io volevo
vedere il signore del lago!
Qué guay.
Yo también quiero ver un Nushi.
Também o queria ter visto...
Once the New Aincrad opens up to the 22nd floor,
Wenn wir Ebene 22 in Neu-Aincrad erreicht haben,
Quando il ventiduesimo piano della
nuova Aincrad sarà di nuovo aperto,
Cuando reabran el piso 22
del nuevo Aincrad,...
Se passarmos até
ao nível 22 em Ainkrad...
let's buy that log house again and
hold another fishing contest at the lake.
kaufen wir uns wieder eine
Blockhütte und veranstalten ein Angelturnier.
compreremo di nuovo quella capanna e faremo
un torneo di pesca al signore del lago.
...compraremos aquella cabaña
y pescaremos en el lago.
...compramos aquela casa
e vamos à pesca.
Oh, but that guardian is crazy huge.
You might end up in tears, Yui!
Aber weißt du, dieser Fisch ist so gigantisch,
der wird dir sicher eine Heidenangst einjagen.
Però, ecco, il signore del lago è un tipo gigantesco!
Magari ti farà piangere, Yui!
Pero el Nushi es muy grande, Yui.
Seguro que te hace llorar.
Mas o lorde é enorme...
Ainda vais chorar...
I will not! You say that it's big,
but when you factor in the area of the lake,
Bestimmt nicht! Er ist vielleicht groß,
aber in Anbetracht der Größe des Sees,
No che non piangerò! Sarà anche grande,
ma considerando l'area del lago
¡No voy a llorar!
Si comparamos el tamaño del lago,
Não choro! A ver pelas dimensões
do lago só pode equivaler...
it can't possibly be as big as
a whale in the real world!
kann er nicht größer als ein Wal in der realen Welt sein!
non sarà mai grande quanto le balene nel mondo reale!
¡seguro que no es tan grande como
una ballena del mundo real!
...a uma baleia do mundo real!
You've seen a whale before, Yui?
Yui-chan, hast du etwa schon mal einen Wal gesehen?!
Yui, hai visto le balene?
¿Has visto alguna vez una ballena?
Yui, já viste uma baleia?
No, I just estimated its size
from its measurements and video data.
Nein, aber anhand von Daten und
Bildern kann ich auf ihre Größe schließen.
No, è solo una stima di grandezza
basata sui dati numerici e visivi...
No, solo he supuesto su tamaño
con los datos que tengo.
Não, só usei dados numéricos
e imagens que vi para fazer a previsão...
Since I can't see what exists
in the real world like you can..
Dinge aus der realen Welt kann ich ja nicht so sehen wie ihr,
Papa und Mama.
Ciò che esiste nel mondo reale io non posso
vederlo come fate voi, mamma e papà.
Yo no puedo ver cosas del mundo real
como vosotros dos.
Isto porque eu não consigo ver coisas
no mundo real como os meus pais...
I see. Is that so?
Verstehe. Ja, das stimmt.
Già, è vero...
Vaya,... Tienes razón.
Pois é, pois é.
If there were any whales in ALfheim,
you could've seen them, too.
Aber wenn es in ALfheim einen Wal gäbe,
könntest du ihn auch sehen.
Se ad Alfheim ci fossero delle balene,
anche tu potresti vederle, Yui.
Si hubiese ballenas en Alfheim,
ya las habrías visto, ¿verdad?
Se houvessem baleias em
Aruvuheimu também podias ver.
They're gigantic, you know.
Sie sind wirklich riesig! Sie springen aus dem
Wasser und tauchen mit einem riesigen Platscher ...
Sono gigantesche, sai? E poi in mezzo al mare bam!
Saltano fuori dall'acqua, e poi splash!
Son gigantes y cuando salen del agua
hacen ¡PLAF!
Fazem saltos tipo "pum!"
They come leaping out of the ocean with a THUMP!
and then go down with a SPLASH!
Wh-What is it?
W... Was denn?
C-che c'è?
¡¿Qué pasa?!
O quê?
I heard something like that once.
Davon hab ich schon mal gehört! Ich glaube im Süden des
Sylphen-Territoriums
C'è una cosa che ho sentito.
In effetti, nel mare a sud di Sylph...
Me suena que al sur de Sylph...
Já ouvi isso...
sim, na parte sul de Sylph.
I think someone found a quest in the south of
the Sylph territory where a whale appears...
gibt es eine Quest, in der ein Wal auftaucht oder so.
Si può trovare una quest in cui c'è anche una balena.
...encontraron una misión
donde salía una ballena.
Uma Quest em que apareciam baleias.
Really? I'd like to see what it's like to ride a whale!
Wirklich? Ich würde zu gerne auf einem Wal reiten!
Davvero?! Voglio provare a cavalcare una balena!
¿De verdad?
¡Me gustaría montarme en una!
A sério? Quero andar numa baleia!
Now riding one might be out of the question...
Das mit dem Reiten wird wohl nichts ...
Cavalcarla mi pare impossibile...
Eso será un poco difícil...
Vai ser difícil...
Hey, Kirito, this better be legit.
That a whale appears in this quest?
Hey, Kirito, diese Quest, in der ein Wal auftauchen soll,
gibt’s doch wirklich, oder?
Ehi, Kirito, ma dicevi sul serio?
Riguardo a quella quest con la balena.
¿En serio que saldrá una ballena
en esta misión, Kirito?
Kirito, é?
Nesta Quest aparecerem baleias?
Yui's really looking forward to it.
Yui-chan freut sich schon wahnsinnig darauf.
Guarda che Yui la sta aspettando con ansia!
Mira que Yui está muy ilusionada.
A yui queria tanto!
Now if it turns out that it's not a whale,
but a jellyfish, or a sea butterfly,
Nicht, dass das jemand mit ’nem Walhai oder
Walross verwechselt hat. Das wär nich’ lustig.
Se invece di essere una balena fosse una medusa
o una lumaca di mare, non sarebbe la stessa cosa.
A ver si nos sale una medusa, un clione,
u otro bicho y metemos la pata.
Medusas e tal até é capaz de haver,
agora baleias...
it's gonna be lamer than hell!
If it's a giant sea butterfly,
I wouldn't mind seeing it, though.
Ein riesiger Walhai wär aber auch cool.
In effetti non mi dispiacerebbe
vedere una lumaca di mare gigante...
Un clione gigante no estaría mal...
Bem, até isso eu gostava de ver...
Agil, did you come up with any info?
Hast du irgendwelche Infos, Agil?
Egil, hai qualche informazione?
Egil, ¿algún dato nuevo?
Egil, tens novidades?
Well, the thing is, since this quest is
way out on the edge of the world map,
Nein. Diese Quest ist am äußersten Zipfel der Worldmap,
darum gibt’s nur wenige,
No, per niente. Dato che è una quest che
si trova ai margini della mappa del mondo,
Como esta misión está
al final del mapa,...
Não. Como é neste mundo
é complicado receber...
not a lot of people even know about it.
die sie kennen.
quelli che ne sanno sono davvero pochi...
...casi nadie sabe nada...
...informações...
But the part about a gigantic aquatic monster
appearing at the end of the quest seems to be true.
Sicher scheint nur, dass am Ende der
Quest ein gigantisches Meeresungetüm auftauchen soll.
Però pare che sia vero che alla fine della quest
un gigantesco mostro acquatico salti fuori, comunque.
Pero es seguro que al acabar la misión,
sale un monstruo marino gigante.
Mas consta que no fim da Quest há
um moｎstro gigantesco...
Hey, that means we can pretty
much get our hopes up, right?
Oh, da können wir uns ja auf was gefasst machen!
Eh? E questo non ti riempie di aspettative?
¡Eso suena muy bien!
Eish, mas que bom!
All right, let's go for it today!
Gut, dann lasst uns mal ranklotzen!
Forza, diamoci da fare, oggi!
¡Bien, manos a la obra!
Vamos dar tudo!
People! It's time for us to get going!
Leute, es wird Zeit! Wir sollten aufbrechen!
Forza, ragazze, è il momento di andare!
¡Chicas, hora de salir!
Vamos! Está quase na hora...!
Okay! We're coming!
Ja, wir kommen!
Sì, arriviamo!
¡Ya vamos!
Sim, já vamos!
Hä?
Eh?
¿Eh?
U-Uh... You guys, are you gonna be wearing
that armor during the quest?
Ä... Ähm ...
Wollt ihr etwa die ganze Quest lang in voller Montur rumlaufen?
E-ecco, avete intenzione di affrontare
la missione con quell'equipaggiamento?
¿Vais a llevar puesto todo el equipo
durante la misión?
Estiveram sempre assim vestidas durante
a missão?
Of course we are! I mean, we're going into battle.
Na klar. Wir werden schließlich kämpfen.
Mi pare ovvio! In fondo dovremo combattere!
Pues claro, vamos a luchar.
Claro. Temos que lutar.
You'd better hurry up and
get yourself changed as well!
Zieh dich auch endlich um!
Anche tu faresti meglio a cambiarti d'abito in fretta!
Anda, vístete rápido.
Muda-te rápido tu também!
With your permission,
I'd like to serve as your party leader today.
Also, wenn ihr alle einverstanden seid,
bin ich dann heute der Gruppenleiter.
Mi scuso per l'ardire, ma oggi vorrei che
lasciaste a me il compito di party leader!
Si me lo permitís,
hoy lideraré el grupo.
Apesar de ser presunçoso,
hoje assumo o papel de líder da festa.
During the quest, if our objective, a giant whale,
shows up, please follow my instructions!
Wenn während der Quest der Wal auftaucht,
den wir suchen, befolgt bitte meine Anweisungen.
A metà della quest c'è l'occasione per far uscire
la balena gigante, quindi seguite le mie istruzioni!
Seguid mis ordenes si durante la misión
aparece la ballena gigante.
Se aparecer alguma baleia vocês
obedecem às minhas ordens.
Right!
Jawohl!
Sì!
¡Vale!
Sim!
Someday, I'll express my gratitude psychologically!
Ergebensten Dank.
Mi dimostrerò degno di questa fiducia.
Ojalá pueda devolveros este favor.
Vá, preparem-se e...
All right, everyone. Let's do this!
Also, legen wir uns ins Zeug!
Quindi forza, ragazzi, diamoci da fare!
¡Venga, en marcha!
...vamos a isso!
Yeah!
Ja!
Sì!
¡Adelante!
Oh!
According to these coordinates,
it should be around here...
Laut Koordinaten müsste es hier irgendwo sein.
Secondo le coordinate dovrebbe
essere qui nei dintorni...
Las coordenadas marcan aquí, pero...
As coordenadas indicavam por aqui...
Hey, isn't that it over there?
Ah, ist es das da?
Ah, non sarà laggiù?
Mirad, ¿será allí?
Então não era ali?
All right, I'm going to cast
a Water Breathing spell, okay?
Dann wende ich jetzt den Water Breathing-Zauber an.
Allora userò la magia Water Blessing!
Vale, os lanzaré el hechizo
Bendición Acuática.
Então vou fazer a magia Water Blessing!
(chants)
Ohz Naza Fyor Fiskle Balam Svarl Vaton!
Oos, Naza, Fuyoor, Fiskur, Baram, Svar, Vaton!
¡Os naza fuyol fiskul baram
svual vu aton!
Orth Naza Fuyoru Fisukuru Balam,
Suvu aru Vu Aton!
Leafa?
Lyfa-chan!
Leafa.
Lyfa.
Rifa.
Wow! That's amazing!
Wah, das ist ja beeindruckend.
Uah, fantastico!
Impresionante...
Uau, fixe...
Hey, there's someone there!
Da drüben ist jemand!
Ehi, laggiù c'è qualcuno!
¡Allí hay alguien!
Está ali alguém!
Hey, looks like a quest NPC.
Das wird wohl der Quest-NPC sein.
Penso sia un NPC della quest.
Parece un PNJ.
Parece uma missão NPC.
If we're talking about someone in trouble in the sea,
you know it's got to be a mermaid!
Wenn im Meer jemand in Nöten steckt,
dann ist das in aller Regel eine Meerjungfrau!
Una persona in difficoltà sul fondale marino, eh?
Sento puzza di sirena!
Solo una sirena tendría problemas
en el fondo del mar.
Pessoas no mar a pedir socorro?
Devem ser sereias!
My mermaid damsel,
I'm coming to save you right now!
Fräulein Meerjungfrau, ich komme und rette Euch!
Sto venendo a salvarti, mia bella sirenetta!
¡Al rescate de la hermosa sirena!
Vou já, vou já!
Are you in some kind of trouble, my damsel--
Was bedrückt Euch, mein Fräulei...
Che problema ti affligge, fanciul...
Damisela, ¿estáis en apuros?
Algum coisa, menina...?
...n?!
Mh?
¿Perdón?
Hum?
Looks like it was a grandpa, not a damsel!
Das ist kein Fräulein, sondern ein Opa, was?
Non è una fanciulla, è un vecchietto.
Vaya, era un señor mayor, ¿eh?
Menina não, velho.
What's wrong, old gentleman?
Was ist los, alter Herr?
Che succede, signore?
Noble anciano, ¿qué sucede?
Que foi, velho?
Would you like to start the quest
"The Plunderers of the Deep Sea"?
"Möchtest du die Quest „Plünderer der Tiefsee" annehmen?"
"INIZIA LA QUEST
"I BRIGANTI DELLE PROFONDITÀ MARINE.""
"INICIANDO LA MISIÓN:
SAQUEADOR MARINO"
"COMEÇA A QUEST 'SAQUEADOR...'"
Ah, fairies from the surface!
Will you be so kind as to help this decrepit old man?
Seid gegrüßt, Elfen vom Festland.
Würdet ihr einem tattrigen Alten wie mir helfen?
Ooh, delle fate della superficie.
Siete qui per salvare questo povero vecchio?
Oh, elfos terrestres,
¿ayudaréis a este viejo anciano?
Vocês vieram lá de cima
para ajudar um velho?
What's the matter, Leafa?
Was hast du, Lyfa-chan?
Che succede, Leafa?
¿Pasa algo, Lyfa?
Que foi, Rifa?
Uh... nothing. I just feel like I've seen
that old man's name somewhere before...
Ach, nichts. Mir war nur so,
als hätte ich den Namen des Alten schon mal irgendwo gelesen.
Ah, no, è che il nome di quel vecchietto mi pare
di averlo già visto da qualche parte...
El nombre del anciano...
Me suena de algo.
Ah, nada. Sinto que já ouvi
o nome daquele velho...
Actually,
Ehrlich gesagt,
A dire il vero,
Resulta que...
Na verdade,...
wurde mir von einer Räuberbande,
die sich im Schrein eingenistet hat,
Il dono fattomi da un vecchio amico che era custodito
in questo santuario è stato sottratto da alcuni ladri.
unos ladrones que se refugian en el templo
me han robado un regalo para mi amigo.
...uns ladrõezecos que andam por aqui roubaram
umas lembranças que tinha para uns amigos...
I've been robbed of a souvenir for an old friend of mine
by some thieves who use this temple as their base.
ein Geschenk gestohlen,
das ich einem alten Freund machen wollte.
I wonder if you'd be kind enough to
take it back from them in my place...
Würdet ihr es für mich zurückholen?
Mi chiedevo se poteste recuperarlo per conto mio...
¿Me lo podrías recuperar?
Será que as conseguem recuperar...
Just leave it to us!
Verlassen Sie sich auf uns.
Lasci fare a noi.
¡Eso está hecho!
Deixe conosco!
Ah, I am grateful. I am grateful.
Habt vielen, vielen Dank.
Ah, vi ringrazio infinitamente.
Os lo agradezco mucho.
Obrigado, obrigado...
The souvenir is a pearl about this size.
Bei dem Geschenk handelt es sich um eine
Perle von etwa dieser Größe.
Il dono in questione è
una perla di queste dimensioni.
El regalo es una perla así de grande.
Eram uma pérolas deste tamanho...
That's huge!
Krass!
È enorme!
¡Es enorme!
Que grandes!!
Don't even think about lifting it and selling it off!
Komm ja nicht auf die Idee, sie verkaufen zu wollen!
Guarda che non possiamo
intascarcela e rivenderla...
No la escondas para venderla luego, ¿eh?
Queres é roubar e vendê-las!
I-I wouldn't do such a thing. Not this time!
D... Diesmal ganz bestimmt nicht!
N-non lo farò, stavolta...
Tranquila, esta vez no lo haré.
Não desta vez...
I'm counting on you, my fairies.
Ich danke euch für eure Hilfe, Elfen.
Allora mi affido a voi, fate.
Elfos, cuento con vosotros.
Por favor, peço-vos...
If you succeed in retrieving my pearl,
I'll be sure to reward you handsomely!
Wenn ihr mir die Perle zurückbringt,
werde ich mich über alle Maßen erkenntlich zeigen!
Se mi riporterete la mia bella perla,
saprò ricompensarvi adeguatamente.
Si me devolvéis la perla,
os daré una generosa recompensa.
Se conseguirem dou-vos
uma boa recompensa.
Um, this looks like a search-type quest,
Also, wie es aussieht,
müssen wir für diese Quest etwas suchen.
Ecco, sembra proprio che si
tratti di una quest di ricerca.
Bien, la misión es encontrar un objeto.
Parece que é uma missão de busca...
but there are sure to be
monsters inside that temple.
Im Schrein werden sicher auch Monster sein.
E c'è anche un mostro che
dovrebbe uscire da dentro il tempio.
Seguro que nos sale
algún monstruo en el templo.
Deverão aparecer monstros.
Vanguard, your sword strokes will be slower
in an underwater battle, so watch out.
Die Vorhut sollte vorsichtig sein,
da die Waffen beim Kampf Unterwasser langsamer sind.
L'avanguardia faccia attenzione. Il movimento delle armi
subisce un rallentamento nel combattimento sottomarino.
Cuidado, se hace más lento
atacar con armas dentro del agua.
Tenham cuidado que na água
ficamos mais lentos.
Rearguard, remember that
you can't use lightning-type spells.
Und die Caster sollten darauf achten,
keine Elektro-Zauber zu benutzen.
La retroguardia faccia attenzione a
non usare magie di natura elettrica.
Y los de la retaguardia
que no gasten hechizos eléctricos.
E não usem ataques de eletricidade.
Right!
Alles klar!
Sì!
¡Vale!
Sim.
All right, let's go!
Also dann, wollen wir?
Allora andiamo!
Pues, en marcha.
Então vamos lá!
Hey, Kirito. Underwater battles aren't
Leafa's thing, are they?
Hey, Kirito!
Lyfa-chan hat doch ein Problem mit Unterwasserkämpfen, oder?
Ehi, Kirito, ma Leafa non è tipo negata
per il combattimento sottomarino?
Kirito, a Lyfa no se le da bien
luchar bajo el agua, ¿verdad?
Hei, Kirito. A Rifa não gosta
de lutas na água?
Shouldn't you be looking out for her more?
Sollten wir nicht ein bisschen mehr auf sie Rücksicht nehmen?
Non sarebbe meglio se badassi a lei un po' di più?
¿No deberías cuidarla más?
Não é melhor estarmos atentos?
Are you used to this now?
Hast du dich daran gewöhnt?
Ti sei già abituata?
¿Te has acostumbrado ya?
Que tal?
I know, but...
It's not just when we pair up.
Vielleicht hast du recht.
Wenn wir zu zweit sind, ist es was anderes,
In effetti sì, ma...
Rispetto a quando facevamo coppia,
Ya, pero...
Aunque formemos pareja...
Sim, mas quando fazemos equipas...
When we team up like this in a party,
aber wenn wir wie jetzt eine Gruppe gebildet haben,
weiß ich nicht, wie ich mich verhalten soll.
ora che abbiamo formato un party tutti assieme,
come dire... è come se la complicità si fosse persa.
...nunca sé qué actitud tener con ella.
Sobre todo cuando vamos en grupo.
...torna-se complicado eleger
os membros de cada...
I don't know what it is,
but I just can't figure out how to deal with her.
Oh, come on, you can just be yourself.
Benimm dich doch einfach ganz normal?
Beh, ma mi chiedo se vada bene così.
Tú sé natural y punto.
Não há de ser assim...
You're her big bro, so you gotta
take care of your kid sister!
Als Bruder musst du doch ein Auge auf deine kleine
Schwester haben!
Un bravo fratello maggiore deve prendersi cura
come si deve della sua sorellina, sai?
Debes cuidarla mejor.
Eres su hermano.
És o irmão mais velho,
tens que tomar conta dela.
Yeah, but when I first met her,
I didn't even know--
Aber ich wusste doch am Anfang gar nicht,
dass sie meine Schwester ...
Però sai, dalla prima volta che l'ho incontrata,
più che mia sorella...
Ya, pero no me esperaba que la primera
con la que topase fue mi hermana...
Quando a vi pela primeira vez
não éramos irmãos...
What kind of fool falls right into a visible pit?
Seriously...
Wer fällt denn bitte in eine Fallgrube,
die nicht mal versteckt ist? Also wirklich ...
Eccoli qua, i fessi che cadono in una trappola
perfettamente visibile. Ma guarda tu...
Tiene mérito caer en una trampa
tan evidente...
Caem num buraco à vista...?
To think that this is a former top player
from the Assault Team...
Und die waren mal die Top-Spieler an der Front ...
E quello era il top player nella conquista
dei piani nel vecchio gioco...
¿Y éste es un jugador de la élite?
Estes é que são
os ex-jogadores de topo...?
Don't worry! To me,
it doesn't matter what you've become...
Keine Sorge! Wie blöd sich Kirito-san auch anstellt ...
Non c'è problema!
Comunque sia Kirito, io lo...
No pasa nada.
A mí no me importa que Kirito...
Não há mal...se for o Kirito...
Daddy! Behind you!
Papa, da unten!
Papà, dietro di te!
¡Detrás de ti, Papá!
Papá, atrás de ti!
Is that it? The whale?
I... Ist das der Wal?!
E-È uscita? La balena?!
¡¿Ya ha salido la ballena?!
Quê? Uma baleia?
No... That's no whale,
no matter how you look at it!
Nein, das ist definitiv kein Wal.
No... A guardarlo, direi
che è del tutto diverso.
¡Me temo que no!
Não se parece com uma!
Prepare for battle!
Bereithalten!
Preparatevi a combattere!
¡Preparaos para el combate!
Preparem-se!
It's not taking any damage to the head!
Treffer am Kopf verursachen keinen Schaden!
La testa non subisce danni!
¡En la cabeza no le afecta!
A cabeça não sofre dano!
I'm gonna make it target me,
so attack him from the sides!
Ich lenke ihn ab! Greift ihr von der Flanke an!
Io lo terrò impegnato,
voi colpitelo ai fianchi!
Yo lo distraigo.
Vosotros, atacadle por los flancos.
Ataquem dos lados!
Gotcha!
Auf geht’s!
Ricevuto!
¡Vale!
Vamos!
Leave it to us!
Alles klar!
Lascia fare a noi!
¡Eso está hecho!
Deixa conosco!
Let's go, too!
Lass uns auch gehen!
Andiamo anche noi!
¡Vamos nosotras también!
Vamos também!
Okay!
Ja!
Sì!
¡Vale!
Sim!
Me too!
Ich auch ...
Anch'io...
Yo también...
E eu...
Leafa, I want you and Asuna
to cover us with magic spells!
Lyfa, du und Asuna unterstützt uns mit Magie!
Leafa, occupati del
supporto magico insieme ad Asuna!
¡Lyfa, lanza un hechizo con Asuna!
Rifa, mais a Asuna cubram-nos com magia!
(chants)
Sear Filla Squiena Hagul Hogg Yuhgl Irt!
- Dabei hab ich doch extra mit ihnen geübt …
- Sea, Firra, Skirna, Hagul, Bogg, Yugul, Ilt!
- Però, per quanto mi sia impegnata nell'allenamento speciale...
-¡Sea fila skina hagul, hog yugul ilto!
-Y para esto he entrenado tanto...
Sea firra suki na haguru, hoggu yuguru iruto!
E eu que treinei tanto...
After Asuna and the others went to
all that trouble to coach me...
Thank you, Leafa!
Danke, Lyfa!
Grazie, Leafa!
¡Gracias, Lyfa!
Obrigada Rifa!
But I made up my mind... to go with everyone...
to follow my brother no matter where he took me!
Ich hab doch beschlossen,
immer mit den anderen und meinem Bruder mitzuhalten!
Anche se avevo deciso che sarei andata ovunque
insieme al fratellone e gli altri...
¡Yo que estaba dispuesta
a luchar hasta el final con todos...!
Decidimos ir todos contigo, juntos!
E mesmo assim...
Leafa?
Lyfa-chan?!
Leafa?!
¡¿Lyfa?!
Rifa?
It's all right!
This time, for sure...
Keine Sorge, diesmal schaff ich’s!
Va bene così! Stavolta tocca a me!
¡Tranquila!
¡Ahora sí!
Estou bem! É agora!
Leafa!
Lyfa-chan!
¡Lyfa!
Rifa!
Kirito, Leafa's...
Kirito-san, Lyfa-san ist ...
Kirito, Leafa è...
Kirito, cuidado con Lyfa.
Kirito! A Rifa...
- Kirito!
- Kirito-kun!
¡Kirito!
¡Kiritooo!
-Kirito!
-Kirito!!
Now I remember... When I was little,
I fell into a pond...
Stimmt ja ... Als ich klein war,
bin ich mal in den Teich gefallen ...
È vero... Quand'ero piccola
sono caduta in quello stagno...
Es verdad, me caí dentro de un estanque
cuando era pequeña.
Pois foi, em pequena caí num tanque...
And then what happened, I wonder?
Was war danach passiert?
È così che era andata...
¿Y qué pasó luego?
E depois... como foi?
Sugu!
¡¡Sugu!!
Kazuto!
Onii-chan!
Fratellone...
¡Hermano!
Mano!
Kazuto... You saved me again...
Onii-chan, du hast mich schon wieder gerettet.
Fratellone... Mi hai salvata un'altra volta...
Me has vuelto a salvar, ¿eh?
Mano, ajudaste-me outra vez...
I don't want to see another shrimp
or crab for a good, long time...
Ich kann erst mal keine Garnelen und Krabben mehr sehen ...
Io ancora non ho visto
né un gambero né un granchio...
No quiero volver a ver ni langostas
ni cangrejos en mucho tiempo.
Não quero ver camarões nem caranguejos...
Or a squid, or an octopus, either...
Tintenfische und Oktopusse auch nicht ...
E nemmeno una seppia o un polpo...
Ni pulpos ni calamares...
"Lulas e polvos"
In the end...
Letztlich
Dopotutto...
Después de todo...
Afinal...
It never did show up, huh? That whale...
hat sich kein Wal blicken lassen.
Dovrebbe venire fuori
soltanto all'ultimo, quella balena...
...no ha salido la ballena.
As baleias não apareceram...
But Yui sure looked like she was enjoying herself!
Aber Yui-chan hat es trotzdem viel Spaß gemacht.
Però sembra che Yui si sia proprio divertita!
Pero Yui parece haberse divertido mucho.
Mas a Yui gostou muito!
We've retrieved your souvenir.
Wir haben das Geschenk zurückgebracht.
Le abbiamo riportato il dono.
Aquí le devuelvo el regalo.
Aqui está.
Ah... Now this is, without a doubt...
Oh, wahrhaftig, das ist es!
Ooh... È proprio lui...
Sí... es esto.
É ela sem dúvida...
Those thieves who stole that pearl off that
old man never did show up either, did they?
Die Räuber, die dem Opa die Perle geklaut haben,
sind auch nicht aufgekreuzt.
Però i ladri che avrebbero rubato la perla
al vecchietto mica sono saltati fuori.
Pues no hemos visto
a los ladrones de la perla.
Mas os ladrões nem apareceram...
Now that you mention it...
Jetzt wo du’s sagst ...
Ora che lo dici...
Por cierto...
Por falar nisso...
Kirito... just a second!
Kirito-kun, halt!
Kirito, aspetta!
¡Kirito, espera!
Kirito, espera!
Hey!
H... Hey!
E-ehi.
¡Eh!
Oh, hei.
This isn't a pearl! It's an egg!
Das ist keine Perle! Das ist ein Ei!
Questa non è una perla, è un uovo!
¡Esto no es una perla!
¡Es un huevo!
Isto não é uma pérola, é um ovo!
A-An egg?
E... Ein Ei?!
U-un uovo?!
¿Un huevo?
Ovo?
Could it be that... “The Plunderers of the Deep Sea”
- did that actually mean us?
Macht das etwa uns zu den „Plünderern der Tiefsee"?!
Quindi forse i "briganti delle profondità marine"
della quest... saremmo noi?
¿No me digas que nosotros somos...
los "saqueadores marinos"?
Será... nós é que somos
os saqueadores no mar fundo?
All right, hand that over to me right now.
Los, gib es schnell her!
Forza, ora riconsegnatemelo.
Venga, dámelo ya.
Andem lá, devolvam isso.
If you refuse to hand it over,
then I have no choice, do I?
Du willst es nicht hergeben?
Dann habe ich keine Wahl.
Ma se non volete riconsegnarmelo,
non avrò altra scelta...
No me dejáis otra opción...
Se não o fazem não tenho outra escolha...
Kraken! Demon of the sea from Norse mythology!
Ein Krake! Das Ungeheuer aus der nordischen Mythologie!
È un kraken, il mostro marino
delle leggende scandinave!
¡Es un kraken!
¡Un monstruo de la mitología nórdica!
Kraken...
monstro do mar da mitologia nórdica!
Many thanks, my fairies.
Habt vielen Dank, Elfen!
Vi ringrazio molto, fate.
Os lo agradezco mucho.
Cá vão os agradecimentos!
You did well to extract the egg of the royal child from
that temple guarded by a barrier keeping me out!
Eine Barriere verhinderte, dass ich in den Schrein kam.
Mi avete riportato l'uovo della sacerdotessa dal
santuario protetto dalla barriera che mi respingeva...
Habéis podido sacar el huevo
de la barrera mágica del templo.
Conseguiram tirar o ovo apesar da barreira
que o guardava no templo...
Indem ihr mir das Ei des Prinzen herausgeholt habt,
wart ihr mir sehr hilfreich!
Now then, give it to me!
Los, händigt es mir schon aus!
Su, consegnatemelo, adesso!
¡Entregádmelo!
Vamos oferecê-lo a mim.
We'll do no such thing! We're going back to the temple
to return this egg!
Auf keinen Fall!
Wir werden es in den Schrein zurückbringen!
Assolutamente no! Ora riporteremo
di nuovo quest'uovo nel santuario!
De eso nada.
¡Devolveremos el huevo al templo!
Não! Vamos devolvê-lo ao templo!
You foolish winged parasites!
In that case, you shall find a watery grave!
Ihr törichten Eintagsfliegen!
Ich werde Seetang aus euch machen!
Insetti impudenti... E allora, una morte
in fondo al mare è ciò che vi si addice!
Malditos insectos...
¡Ahora probaréis mi furia!
Chatos! Se é assim então
vão morrer afogados...
Kirito!
¡Kirito!
Daddy, that octopus's status is too high!
Papa, die Stats dieses Kraken sind viel zu hoch!
Papà, le statistiche di
quel polpo sono troppo alte!
¡Papá, el nivel de ese pulpo es enorme!
Papá, o polvo é muito forte!
No floor boss of New Aincrad has stats
that can touch his!
Die Werte übertreffen die der Bosse in
Neu-Aincrad um ein Vielfaches!
I suoi valori eccedono di molto quelli
dei floor boss della nuova Aincrad!
¡Supera mil veces a los jefes
del nuevo Aincrad!
Ultrapassa o boss de Ainkrad por muito!
This spear!
Dieser Dreizack gehört ...!
Ma questa lancia...
¡Esa lanza...!
Esta lança...!
Long time no see, my old friend. I can see that
you still can't stop hatching your foolish plots!
Es ist lange her, alter Freund. Du kannst also immer noch
nicht von deinen heimtückischen Plänen ablassen.
Ci rivediamo, mio vecchio amico. Come al solito
ricorri sempre ai tuoi sporchi trucchetti.
Cuánto tiempo, viejo amigo.
¿Otra vez con tus triquiñuelas?
Há quanto tempo...
Não páras com as tuas brincadeirinhas...
What about you? How long do you plan
to put up with those minions of the Earth Gods?
Und du? Willst du dich ewig damit zufrieden geben,
ein Handlanger der Asen zu sein?!
E allora tu? Per quanto hai intenzione di pendere
dalle dita delle divinità della superficie?
¿Y tú sigues subordinado
a los dioses de Æsir?
Até quando tu estas contente com o
subordinado da raça divina de Earth.
You're a disgrace as the King of the Sea!
Du ziehst den Namen des Meereskönigs in den Dreck!
Stai infangando il titolo di signore dei mari!
Eso es una deshonra para el Rey del Mar.
Até o rei do mar chora!
I happen to be content to be king.
And this is my backyard.
König zu sein, genügt mir vollkommen.
Außerdem ist das hier mein Grund und Boden.
Sono soddisfatto di ciò che sono.
E questo è il mio giardino.
Me siento satisfecho de ser rey
y éste es mi jardín.
Eu fico contente por ser o Rei.
E este é o meu jardim.
Knowing that, do you really wish to fight,
King of the Abyss?
Wünschst du dennoch einen Kampf mit mir, König der Tiefen?
Anche sapendo questo vuoi comunque
combattere, signore dell'abisso?
Aún sabiéndolo,
¿buscas pelea Rey del Abismo?
Ainda assim lutas, rei das profundezas?
I shall withdraw for now.
But listen, my friend... I'm not giving up.
Dies eine Mal will ich mich zurückziehen,
doch ich werde wiederkommen, alter Freund!
Per il momento mi ritirerò. Ma sappi,
caro amico, che io non mi arrendo.
Me retiro, querido amigo.
Aunque no me rindo aún.
Hoje fico-me por aqui, mas meu caro,
não vou parar!
One day, I'll claim the power of The Child for myself,
and take those detestable gods by surprise!
Eines Tages wird die
Macht des Prinzen mein sein und dann werde
Un giorno il potere della sacerdotessa sarà mio, e
anche quei fastidiosi dei tremeranno al mio cospetto!
Algún día el poder de ese huevo será mío
y los dioses me temerán.
Um dia a força será minha... e vocês deuses
serão destruidos... um dia...
ich als unheilbringende Gottheit,
Angst und Schrecken verbreiten!
That is the egg of one who will
someday rule all of the seas and skies.
In diesem Ei schlummert der künftige
Herrscher über alle Himmel und Meere.
Quell'uovo contiene una creatura che
sostiene sia il cielo che il mare.
De ese huevo nacerá el futuro
Señor del Mar y la Tierra.
Esse ovo é a posse da pessoa que
dominará o mar e o ceu.
As I must transfer it to a new resting place,
I'll be taking it back now.
Ich nehme es mir zurück und werde es in eine andere
Krippe umbetten.
Deve essere spostato in un
nuovo territorio sacro, restituitelo.
Devolvédmelo, debo llevarlo
a un nuevo altar.
Vamos devolvê-lo ao seu sítio...
Oh, so now we've cleared the mission?
I have no idea what's going on here...
Das war’s jetzt? Ich blick’s nich’ ...
E così abbiamo finito? È stata un po', come dire...
¿Misión completa?
Pues no sé yo...
Já passámos? Não parece...
I didn't understand a word of
that conversation you had with that octopus.
Ich habe von der Unterhaltung der beiden kein Wort verstanden.
Io della conversazione fra il polpo e
‘sto vecchietto mica ho capito niente...
No he entendido nada
de lo que han dicho estos dos.
Não percebi nada do que
o velho e polvo disseram...
For now, that's fine.
Das spielt jetzt keine Rolle.
Ora è tutto a posto.
Está bien que sea así.
Ainda bem.
Now then, I shall send you back
to your own country, my fairies.
Ich lasse euch in euer Reich zurückbringen, Elfen.
Su, ora vi rimanderò
nel luogo da cui provenite, fate.
Elfos, os regresaré a vuestro reino.
Vou-vos levar até ao vosso país,
meus caros.
S-Send us? But how?
Z... Zurückbringen? Wie denn?
R-rimanderà? E come?
¿C-cómo?
Como é que nos vai levar?
This whale is really, really gigantic!
Der Wal ist ganz ganz groß!
Le balene sono davvero, davvero gigantesche!
¡La ballena es gigante!
Baleia, és tão grande!
INCOMING CALL
SEIJIRO KIKUOKA
"Seijirou Kikuoka"
"CHIAMATA DA SEIJIRO KIKUOKA"
"LLAMADA DE SEIJIROU KIKUOKA"
"CHAMADA SEIJORO KIKUOKA"